<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Misc on Blog | Léo Corporation</title>
        <link>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/tags/misc/</link>
        <description>Recent content in Misc on Blog | Léo Corporation</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 18:17:33 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/tags/misc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>A Year in Review and a Look to the Future</title>
        <link>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/12/a-year-in-review-and-a-look-to-the-future/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 18:17:33 +0100</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/12/a-year-in-review-and-a-look-to-the-future/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/12/a-year-in-review-and-a-look-to-the-future/cover.png" alt="Featured image of post A Year in Review and a Look to the Future" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s been an exciting year at Léo Corporation! We&amp;rsquo;ve been hard at work on a number of projects and we&amp;rsquo;re thrilled to share our updates with you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;a-recap&#34;&gt;A recap&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;experiences-made-for-you&#34;&gt;Experiences made for you&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First, we gave our company a fresh new look with a modern and colorful design. We wanted to bring a fresh, updated feel to our apps and services and we&amp;rsquo;re thrilled with the result.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Next, we released InternetTest Pro, a powerful connection utility for Windows. This tool can help you locate IP addresses, send ping requests, and even recover your WiFi passwords. It&amp;rsquo;s a must-have for anyone who needs to troubleshoot their internet connection.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We also redesigned our blog, with better content and exciting articles. We hope you&amp;rsquo;ve enjoyed reading our updates and learning more about our company and products.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We also released Gavilya 3, a simple game launcher with a redesigned look. This tool makes it easy to launch your favorite games, and the new design gives it a fresh, modern feel.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;focusing-on-developers&#34;&gt;Focusing on developers&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In addition to these updates, we released PeyrSharp, a C# library designed to make developers&amp;rsquo; lives easier. With its handy tools and features, PeyrSharp is a valuable resource for any C# developer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, we released Synethia, a basic C# algorithm that can determine the behavior of a user with an application. This tool is a great resource for developers who want to understand how their users are interacting with their apps.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;whats-next&#34;&gt;What&amp;rsquo;s next&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Looking to the future, Léo Corporation has a number of exciting plans in the works. We&amp;rsquo;re focused on improving our existing apps and services, and we&amp;rsquo;ll be extending the features of Synethia to make it even more powerful. We&amp;rsquo;re also committed to creating new delightful experiences for our users by developing new applications and services. And of course, we&amp;rsquo;ll be evolving our existing apps to reflect our vision for the future.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We can&amp;rsquo;t wait to see what the future holds for Léo Corporation, and we&amp;rsquo;re excited to share our updates with you as we continue to grow and evolve. Stay tuned for more exciting news from us!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>A slight update on our look</title>
        <link>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/07/a-slight-update-on-our-look/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/07/a-slight-update-on-our-look/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/07/a-slight-update-on-our-look/cover.png" alt="Featured image of post A slight update on our look" /&gt;&lt;h2 id=&#34;we-have-a-new-look&#34;&gt;We have a new look!&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As you may have noticed, we’ve updated our font in our logos and websites. We are announcing that we’re ditching the Montserrat font for Hauora Sans. This font gives more personality to our identity, since the old font was one of the most popular sans serif fonts used in apps, websites, and product. The new one is – indeed – like Montserrat, but it adds some small details that makes it better than the old one.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;when-will-this-change-take-effect&#34;&gt;When will this change take effect?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As we said, most of our websites have already received an update. However, our apps haven’t yet. An update should roll out to them this month.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Léo Corporation is always evolving, and we would like to thank our users for taking this journey with us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;image&#34;&gt;Image&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/07/a-slight-update-on-our-look/cover.png&#34;
	width=&#34;3438&#34;
	height=&#34;1146&#34;
	srcset=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/07/a-slight-update-on-our-look/cover_hu11d46245019c0cc4f6837ea1f8635293_782421_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/07/a-slight-update-on-our-look/cover_hu11d46245019c0cc4f6837ea1f8635293_782421_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;The Léo Corporation logo, updated with the new Hauora font.&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;300&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;720px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>We&#39;ve updated our visual identity</title>
        <link>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/01/weve-updated-our-visual-identity/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/01/weve-updated-our-visual-identity/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/01/weve-updated-our-visual-identity/cover.png" alt="Featured image of post We&#39;ve updated our visual identity" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;2021 has been a busy year for Léo Corporation, and 2022 will be focused on how we can improve the user experience across our products.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To start this new year, we’ve slightly updated our visual identity to a more colorful one. You may have seen on our &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://twitter.com/LeoCorpNews&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://www.facebook.com/LeoCorporationSoftwares/&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://www.instagram.com/leocorporation_/&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt; that a more colorful look has been adapted. These colors are – of course – colors of Léo Corporation, but they are also here to bring a more vibrant vibe to our posts. However, we haven’t changed our logo, even though there are now a black and a white variant of it. You will also notice new splash screens that will come to applications that use one on the upcoming weeks.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
