<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Stats on Blog | Léo Corporation</title><link>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/tags/stats/</link><description>Recent content in Stats on Blog | Léo Corporation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 10:38:15 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/tags/stats/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A Look at the Latest Download Trends</title><link>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/02/a-look-at-the-latest-download-trends/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 10:38:15 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/02/a-look-at-the-latest-download-trends/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/02/a-look-at-the-latest-download-trends/cover.png" alt="Featured image of post A Look at the Latest Download Trends" />&lt;h2 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>The Léo Corporation is proud to announce the latest trends in software downloads for our popular applications. In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll take a closer look at the number of downloads for our various software programs between December 2022 and January 2023.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="apps">Apps&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>First up is Gavilya, which saw an impressive increase in downloads, going from 1391 in December 2022 to 1506 in January 2023. This represents a 8.27% increase and is a testament to the growing popularity of this software within the Léo Corporation portfolio.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Gerayis also saw an increase in downloads, with 735 downloads in December 2022 and 743 in January 2023. This 1.09% increase is a positive sign for the continued success of this software.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Passliss had a modest increase in downloads, going from 1251 in December 2022 to 1275 in January 2023. This 1.92% increase is a sign of the steady growth and popularity of this software.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>InternetTest Pro 7 saw a significant increase in downloads, going from 704 in December 2022 to 857 in January 2023. This 21.73% increase is a clear indication of the growing popularity of this software and its increasing importance within the Léo Corporation portfolio.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>ColorPicker 4 also saw an increase in downloads, going from 1234 in December 2022 to 1274 in January 2023. This 3.24% increase is a sign of the continued success of this software and its popularity among our users.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Xalyus Store had a small but steady increase in downloads, going from 325 in December 2022 to 331 in January 2023. This 1.85% increase is a positive sign for the continued success of this software.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Datalya saw a modest increase in downloads, going from 537 in December 2022 to 548 in January 2023. This 2.05% increase is a sign of the steady growth and popularity of this software.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Overall, the total number of software downloads increased from 6177 in December 2022 to 6534 in January 2023, a 5.78% increase. This is a positive sign for the Léo Corporation and indicates the continued success and popularity of our software portfolio.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In conclusion, the Léo Corporation is proud to announce the latest trends in software downloads for our popular applications. The data we&amp;rsquo;ve analyzed shows that there is a continued growth in software downloads, with various software programs within our portfolio seeing increases in downloads. Whether it&amp;rsquo;s a modest increase or a significant jump, every increase is a positive sign for the Léo Corporation and a testament to the growing popularity and importance of our software in the market.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="data">Data&lt;/h2>
&lt;table>
&lt;thead>
&lt;tr>
&lt;th>&lt;strong>Software&lt;/strong>&lt;/th>
&lt;th>December 2022&lt;/th>
&lt;th>January&lt;/th>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;/thead>
&lt;tbody>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>&lt;strong>Gavilya&lt;/strong>&lt;/td>
&lt;td>1391&lt;/td>
&lt;td>1506&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>&lt;strong>Gerayis&lt;/strong>&lt;/td>
&lt;td>735&lt;/td>
&lt;td>743&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>&lt;strong>Passliss&lt;/strong>&lt;/td>
&lt;td>1251&lt;/td>
&lt;td>1275&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>&lt;strong>InternetTest Pro 7&lt;/strong>&lt;/td>
&lt;td>704&lt;/td>
&lt;td>857&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>&lt;strong>ColorPicker 4&lt;/strong>&lt;/td>
&lt;td>1234&lt;/td>
&lt;td>1274&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>&lt;strong>Xalyus Store&lt;/strong>&lt;/td>
&lt;td>325&lt;/td>
&lt;td>331&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>&lt;strong>Datalya&lt;/strong>&lt;/td>
&lt;td>537&lt;/td>
&lt;td>548&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>&lt;/td>
&lt;td>&lt;/td>
&lt;td>&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>&lt;/td>
&lt;td>&lt;/td>
&lt;td>&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>&lt;strong>Total&lt;/strong>&lt;/td>
&lt;td>6177&lt;/td>
&lt;td>6534&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>&lt;strong>Increase Percentage&lt;/strong>&lt;/td>
&lt;td>&lt;/td>
&lt;td>5,779504614&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>&lt;/td>
&lt;td>&lt;/td>
&lt;td>&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>&lt;strong>Gavilya&lt;/strong>&lt;/td>
&lt;td>8,164852255&lt;/td>
&lt;td>8,267433501&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>&lt;strong>Gerayis&lt;/strong>&lt;/td>
&lt;td>5,603448276&lt;/td>
&lt;td>1,088435374&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>&lt;strong>Passliss&lt;/strong>&lt;/td>
&lt;td>4,25&lt;/td>
&lt;td>1,918465228&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>&lt;strong>InternetTest Pro 7&lt;/strong>&lt;/td>
&lt;td>21,79930796&lt;/td>
&lt;td>21,73295455&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>&lt;strong>ColorPicker 4&lt;/strong>&lt;/td>
&lt;td>12,07992734&lt;/td>
&lt;td>3,241491086&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>&lt;strong>Xalyus Store&lt;/strong>&lt;/td>
&lt;td>2,848101266&lt;/td>
&lt;td>1,846153846&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>&lt;strong>Datalya&lt;/strong>&lt;/td>
&lt;td>5,708661417&lt;/td>
&lt;td>2,048417132&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;/tbody>
&lt;/table></description></item></channel></rss>