<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Information on Blog | Léo Corporation</title>
        <link>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/categories/information/</link>
        <description>Recent content in Information on Blog | Léo Corporation</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 12:57:52 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/categories/information/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>Introducing ColorPicker Max</title>
        <link>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/02/introducing-colorpicker-max/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 12:57:52 +0100</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/02/introducing-colorpicker-max/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/02/introducing-colorpicker-max/cover.png" alt="Featured image of post Introducing ColorPicker Max" /&gt;&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ColorPicker Max is the latest version of the popular color picker tool that has been trusted by designers, artists, and developers around the world. As the next major evolution of this application, ColorPicker Max introduces a host of new features and improvements that make it more powerful, flexible, and user-friendly than ever before. In this article, we will take a closer look at the newest features and enhancements that make ColorPicker Max the ultimate choice for anyone who needs to work with color on a daily basis. From the powerful Converter tool to the versatile Gradient generator, we will explore all the ways in which ColorPicker Max can help you work more efficiently and effectively with color. So let&amp;rsquo;s dive in and discover what this amazing tool has to offer!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;selector&#34;&gt;Selector&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/02/introducing-colorpicker-max/1.png&#34;
	width=&#34;950&#34;
	height=&#34;600&#34;
	srcset=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/02/introducing-colorpicker-max/1_hu40ce090efda3d0bc547047c669ce9e1e_201869_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/02/introducing-colorpicker-max/1_hu40ce090efda3d0bc547047c669ce9e1e_201869_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;The selector page of ColorPicker Max&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;158&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;380px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of the most exciting features of ColorPicker Max is its ability to select a specific color using different sliders or from a pixel on the screen. This allows users to easily and accurately pick any color they need for their projects. Additionally, the color detail panel shows all the details of the color, including RGB values, HEX, HSL, HSV, CMYK, XYZ, YIQ, and YUV. Users can also copy any of these values to the clipboard by simply clicking on them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;chromatic-wheel&#34;&gt;Chromatic wheel&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/02/introducing-colorpicker-max/2.png&#34;
	width=&#34;950&#34;
	height=&#34;600&#34;
	srcset=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/02/introducing-colorpicker-max/2_hu927032dbb0fc7cdcb3c0a114f5184951_231174_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/02/introducing-colorpicker-max/2_hu927032dbb0fc7cdcb3c0a114f5184951_231174_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;The Chromatic wheel page of ColorPicker Max&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;158&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;380px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Another great feature of ColorPicker Max is its Chromatic Wheel, which allows users to select a color from the wheel, with the ability to choose different chromatic wheels. The tool also includes a converter that lets users enter a color using a specified color type, and then shows the color converted in all color types, making it easy to find the color you need.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;converter&#34;&gt;Converter&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/02/introducing-colorpicker-max/3.png&#34;
	width=&#34;950&#34;
	height=&#34;600&#34;
	srcset=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/02/introducing-colorpicker-max/3_hu2366bf50cc1e2a015699cfa8ae3dd591_209552_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/02/introducing-colorpicker-max/3_hu2366bf50cc1e2a015699cfa8ae3dd591_209552_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;The Converter page of ColorPicker Max&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;158&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;380px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ColorPicker Max offers several useful tools for manipulating colors, and two of the most powerful are the Converter and Text tools.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Converter tool allows users to easily convert colors between different color types, such as RGB, HEX, HSV, HSL, CMYK, YIQ, XYZ, and YUV. Users can enter a color using a specified color type, and the tool will automatically display the color converted into all other color types in a color detail panel. If the user enters an invalid color, a message will appear to let them know.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For some color types, the Converter tool also displays dedicated textboxes that allow users to enter different values for each variable, such as hue, saturation, and value. The tool also provides a preview of the color specified by the user.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;text-tool&#34;&gt;Text tool&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/02/introducing-colorpicker-max/4.png&#34;
	width=&#34;950&#34;
	height=&#34;600&#34;
	srcset=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/02/introducing-colorpicker-max/4_hu2a35cdb2df6cb3fce550c51ff1e23607_172167_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/02/introducing-colorpicker-max/4_hu2a35cdb2df6cb3fce550c51ff1e23607_172167_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;The Text tool page of ColorPicker Max&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;158&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;380px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Text tool is another powerful feature of ColorPicker Max that allows users to set the font, font size, foreground color, and background color for text. The tool also includes a feature that calculates the contrast ratio between the foreground and background colors and displays it as an arrow on a scale, indicating whether the contrast is sufficient for legibility.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With the Text tool, users can set the color for both regular text and links, and the tool includes a preview of the resulting text as it will appear on a webpage. The ability to set custom font and color styles can be incredibly useful for web designers, graphic designers, and anyone else who needs to manipulate colors and text on a regular basis.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In short, both the Converter and Text tools are powerful and flexible features that can greatly enhance a user&amp;rsquo;s ability to work with and manipulate colors. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a designer, developer, or simply someone who enjoys exploring the world of color, ColorPicker Max has everything you need to get the most out of your work.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;palette-and-gradient&#34;&gt;Palette and Gradient&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/02/introducing-colorpicker-max/5.png&#34;
	width=&#34;950&#34;
	height=&#34;600&#34;
	srcset=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/02/introducing-colorpicker-max/5_hucf0d2f99c8b6a6b35e23d5704db7547b_203459_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/02/introducing-colorpicker-max/5_hucf0d2f99c8b6a6b35e23d5704db7547b_203459_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;The Palette page of ColorPicker Max&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;158&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;380px&#34;
	
&gt;
&lt;img src=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/02/introducing-colorpicker-max/6.png&#34;
	width=&#34;950&#34;
	height=&#34;600&#34;
	srcset=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/02/introducing-colorpicker-max/6_hu3fb44c5e736c2952f11397c679738f21_178427_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/02/introducing-colorpicker-max/6_hu3fb44c5e736c2952f11397c679738f21_178427_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;The Gradient page of ColorPicker Max&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;158&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;380px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ColorPicker Max also offers a variety of tools for creating color palettes and gradients. The palette tool lets users get different shades, brightness, and hues of a specified color, and also provides the ability to bookmark and save the palette for later. The gradient tool allows users to generate a random gradient with two stops, change the rotation of the gradient, and even export the gradient as CSS.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;bookmarks&#34;&gt;Bookmarks&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/02/introducing-colorpicker-max/7.png&#34;
	width=&#34;950&#34;
	height=&#34;600&#34;
	srcset=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/02/introducing-colorpicker-max/7_hub06746961ffc8fd7365d6a1037e43423_216220_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/02/introducing-colorpicker-max/7_hub06746961ffc8fd7365d6a1037e43423_216220_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;The bookmark feature of ColorPicker Max, with the &amp;ldquo;Colors&amp;rdquo; tab selected&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;158&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;380px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ColorPicker Max allows you to bookmark your favorite colors, palettes, and gradients, making it easy to quickly access them later on. You can organize your bookmarks into different categories, such as regular colors, palettes, and gradients, and easily remove individual bookmarks or clear all bookmarks at once.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To add a bookmark, simply navigate to the color, palette, or gradient you&amp;rsquo;d like to save and click the bookmark icon. You can access your bookmarks at any time by clicking on the Bookmarks button in the sidebar, and then selecting the category you&amp;rsquo;d like to view.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bookmarks make it easy to keep track of your favorite color schemes and design elements, allowing you to work more efficiently and effectively.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;modern-experience&#34;&gt;Modern experience&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/02/introducing-colorpicker-max/ColorPickerSynethia.gif&#34;
	width=&#34;1920&#34;
	height=&#34;1080&#34;
	srcset=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/02/introducing-colorpicker-max/ColorPickerSynethia_hua55f41b039613a4f342957e25a05306a_272959_480x0_resize_box.gif 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/02/introducing-colorpicker-max/ColorPickerSynethia_hua55f41b039613a4f342957e25a05306a_272959_1024x0_resize_box.gif 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;The Home dashboard is dynamic and unique for each user&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;177&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;426px&#34;
	
&gt;
The user interface and user experience of ColorPicker Max are both top-notch. The background is a mesh gradient with subtle colors that adapts to the light or dark theme, while the window is resizable and responsive. The tool also includes a dashboard with the most relevant features for the user and a section for least relevant features, making it easy to find what you need.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In conclusion, ColorPicker Max is an excellent tool for developers, designers, and anyone else who needs to work with colors regularly. Its range of features and ease of use make it a must-have for anyone who wants to work with colors more efficiently. &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://tinyurl.com/DownloadColorPickerMax&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;Try ColorPicker Max today&lt;/a&gt; and experience the difference for yourself!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;download&#34;&gt;Download&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To get started with ColorPicker Max, &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://tinyurl.com/DownloadColorPickerMax&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;head to our website and download the installation package&lt;/a&gt;. The app is available for Windows.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once the installation package has finished downloading, double-click it to begin the installation process. Follow the on-screen instructions to complete the installation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once installed, you can launch ColorPicker Max from your applications folder or the Start menu. When you launch the app for the first time, you&amp;rsquo;ll be prompted to choose your default language, theme, and other settings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-to-upgrade-from-colorpicker-4&#34;&gt;How to upgrade from ColorPicker 4?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s important to note that ColorPicker Max is not simply an upgrade to ColorPicker 4. While it does share some similarities with its predecessor, ColorPicker Max is a standalone application that needs to be installed manually. Users of ColorPicker 4 will not be able to upgrade to ColorPicker Max through their current application and will need to download and install ColorPicker Max separately.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Despite the need for a manual installation, we believe that the new features and enhancements offered by ColorPicker Max make it worth the effort. The powerful and flexible new tools, as well as the improved user interface and user experience, are designed to help users work more efficiently and effectively with color. So, if you&amp;rsquo;re ready to take your color work to the next level, we encourage you to &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://tinyurl.com/DownloadColorPickerMax&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;download and install ColorPicker Max today&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;video&#34;&gt;Video&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Check the official trailer for ColorPicker Max.&lt;/p&gt;


  &lt;center&gt;
    &lt;iframe width=&#34;560&#34; height=&#34;315&#34; src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/VRGkiRKs88k&#34; title=&#34;YouTube video player&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; allow=&#34;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share&#34; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
  &lt;/center&gt;

</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>A Look at the Latest Download Trends</title>
        <link>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/02/a-look-at-the-latest-download-trends/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 10:38:15 +0100</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/02/a-look-at-the-latest-download-trends/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/02/a-look-at-the-latest-download-trends/cover.png" alt="Featured image of post A Look at the Latest Download Trends" /&gt;&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Léo Corporation is proud to announce the latest trends in software downloads for our popular applications. In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll take a closer look at the number of downloads for our various software programs between December 2022 and January 2023.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;apps&#34;&gt;Apps&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First up is Gavilya, which saw an impressive increase in downloads, going from 1391 in December 2022 to 1506 in January 2023. This represents a 8.27% increase and is a testament to the growing popularity of this software within the Léo Corporation portfolio.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Gerayis also saw an increase in downloads, with 735 downloads in December 2022 and 743 in January 2023. This 1.09% increase is a positive sign for the continued success of this software.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Passliss had a modest increase in downloads, going from 1251 in December 2022 to 1275 in January 2023. This 1.92% increase is a sign of the steady growth and popularity of this software.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;InternetTest Pro 7 saw a significant increase in downloads, going from 704 in December 2022 to 857 in January 2023. This 21.73% increase is a clear indication of the growing popularity of this software and its increasing importance within the Léo Corporation portfolio.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ColorPicker 4 also saw an increase in downloads, going from 1234 in December 2022 to 1274 in January 2023. This 3.24% increase is a sign of the continued success of this software and its popularity among our users.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Xalyus Store had a small but steady increase in downloads, going from 325 in December 2022 to 331 in January 2023. This 1.85% increase is a positive sign for the continued success of this software.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Datalya saw a modest increase in downloads, going from 537 in December 2022 to 548 in January 2023. This 2.05% increase is a sign of the steady growth and popularity of this software.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Overall, the total number of software downloads increased from 6177 in December 2022 to 6534 in January 2023, a 5.78% increase. This is a positive sign for the Léo Corporation and indicates the continued success and popularity of our software portfolio.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In conclusion, the Léo Corporation is proud to announce the latest trends in software downloads for our popular applications. The data we&amp;rsquo;ve analyzed shows that there is a continued growth in software downloads, with various software programs within our portfolio seeing increases in downloads. Whether it&amp;rsquo;s a modest increase or a significant jump, every increase is a positive sign for the Léo Corporation and a testament to the growing popularity and importance of our software in the market.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;data&#34;&gt;Data&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Software&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;December 2022&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;January&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Gavilya&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1391&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1506&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Gerayis&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;735&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;743&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Passliss&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1251&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1275&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;InternetTest Pro 7&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;704&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;857&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ColorPicker 4&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1234&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1274&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Xalyus Store&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;325&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;331&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Datalya&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;537&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;548&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Total&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;6177&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;6534&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Increase Percentage&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;5,779504614&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Gavilya&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;8,164852255&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;8,267433501&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Gerayis&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;5,603448276&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1,088435374&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Passliss&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;4,25&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1,918465228&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;InternetTest Pro 7&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;21,79930796&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;21,73295455&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ColorPicker 4&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;12,07992734&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;3,241491086&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Xalyus Store&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;2,848101266&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1,846153846&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Datalya&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;5,708661417&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;2,048417132&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Introducing Devyus</title>
        <link>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/01/introducing-devyus/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 18:58:05 +0100</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/01/introducing-devyus/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/01/introducing-devyus/cover.png" alt="Featured image of post Introducing Devyus" /&gt;&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Léo Corporation is excited to announce the launch of Devyus, a new division dedicated to developing products and projects for developers. As technology continues to evolve and the role of developers becomes increasingly critical to businesses and organizations, Devyus is committed to improving the workflow and productivity of developers around the world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At the heart of Devyus are two innovative products - PeyrSharp, a C# library designed to make developers&amp;rsquo; jobs easier, and Synethia, a basic C# algorithm that can determine the behavior of a user with an application. These products are designed to streamline the development process, helping developers work more efficiently and effectively.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PeyrSharp is a comprehensive library that simplifies many of the common tasks developers face on a daily basis. With PeyrSharp, developers can write code faster and with fewer errors, allowing them to focus on more important tasks. And with Synethia, developers can gain valuable insights into how users interact with their applications, allowing them to make data-driven decisions and create unique experiences for each user.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At Devyus, we understand that the role of developers is constantly evolving, and we are committed to staying ahead of the curve. Our team of experts is constantly exploring new technologies and techniques, so that we can bring the best products to market. And because we believe in the power of collaboration, we are always open to feedback and suggestions from the developer community.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So whether you are a seasoned developer or just starting out, Devyus is here to help. With our innovative products, expert team, and commitment to improving the workflow of developers, we are confident that we can make a real difference in the lives of developers everywhere.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We look forward to working with you!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;devyus-products&#34;&gt;Devyus Products&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We already have interesting product for you!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://peyrsharp.leocorporation.dev/&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;PeyrSharp&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://synethia.leocorporation.dev/&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;Synethia&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/01/introducing-devyus/synethia.png&#34;
	width=&#34;1920&#34;
	height=&#34;1080&#34;
	srcset=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/01/introducing-devyus/synethia_hu6eaee102f9b00e1034b723db4d774224_497213_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/01/introducing-devyus/synethia_hu6eaee102f9b00e1034b723db4d774224_497213_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;Synethia is now part of Devyus&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;177&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;426px&#34;
	
&gt;
&lt;img src=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/01/introducing-devyus/ps.png&#34;
	width=&#34;1920&#34;
	height=&#34;1080&#34;
	srcset=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/01/introducing-devyus/ps_hu6eaee102f9b00e1034b723db4d774224_454850_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/01/introducing-devyus/ps_hu6eaee102f9b00e1034b723db4d774224_454850_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;PeyrSharp is now part of Devyus&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;177&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;426px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-does-that-mean-for-léo-corporation&#34;&gt;What does that mean for Léo Corporation?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a subsidiary of Léo Corporation, Devyus will continue to be backed by the resources and expertise of our parent company. This means that all Devyus products, including PeyrSharp and Synethia, will continue to be published under the Léo Corporation name.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However, with Devyus, we aim to streamline our development-focused offerings and create a more cohesive and dedicated platform for developers. Future products developed by Devyus will be published under the Devyus name, further solidifying our commitment to improving the workflow and experience of developers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For current users of PeyrSharp and Synethia, rest assured that nothing has changed. These products will continue to be supported by Léo Corporation and Devyus, ensuring that developers can continue to use them with confidence.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>A Year in Review and a Look to the Future</title>
        <link>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/12/a-year-in-review-and-a-look-to-the-future/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 18:17:33 +0100</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/12/a-year-in-review-and-a-look-to-the-future/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/12/a-year-in-review-and-a-look-to-the-future/cover.png" alt="Featured image of post A Year in Review and a Look to the Future" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s been an exciting year at Léo Corporation! We&amp;rsquo;ve been hard at work on a number of projects and we&amp;rsquo;re thrilled to share our updates with you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;a-recap&#34;&gt;A recap&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;experiences-made-for-you&#34;&gt;Experiences made for you&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First, we gave our company a fresh new look with a modern and colorful design. We wanted to bring a fresh, updated feel to our apps and services and we&amp;rsquo;re thrilled with the result.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Next, we released InternetTest Pro, a powerful connection utility for Windows. This tool can help you locate IP addresses, send ping requests, and even recover your WiFi passwords. It&amp;rsquo;s a must-have for anyone who needs to troubleshoot their internet connection.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We also redesigned our blog, with better content and exciting articles. We hope you&amp;rsquo;ve enjoyed reading our updates and learning more about our company and products.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We also released Gavilya 3, a simple game launcher with a redesigned look. This tool makes it easy to launch your favorite games, and the new design gives it a fresh, modern feel.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;focusing-on-developers&#34;&gt;Focusing on developers&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In addition to these updates, we released PeyrSharp, a C# library designed to make developers&amp;rsquo; lives easier. With its handy tools and features, PeyrSharp is a valuable resource for any C# developer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, we released Synethia, a basic C# algorithm that can determine the behavior of a user with an application. This tool is a great resource for developers who want to understand how their users are interacting with their apps.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;whats-next&#34;&gt;What&amp;rsquo;s next&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Looking to the future, Léo Corporation has a number of exciting plans in the works. We&amp;rsquo;re focused on improving our existing apps and services, and we&amp;rsquo;ll be extending the features of Synethia to make it even more powerful. We&amp;rsquo;re also committed to creating new delightful experiences for our users by developing new applications and services. And of course, we&amp;rsquo;ll be evolving our existing apps to reflect our vision for the future.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We can&amp;rsquo;t wait to see what the future holds for Léo Corporation, and we&amp;rsquo;re excited to share our updates with you as we continue to grow and evolve. Stay tuned for more exciting news from us!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Introducing PeyrSharp</title>
        <link>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/11/introducing-peyrsharp/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 11:36:34 +0100</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/11/introducing-peyrsharp/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/11/introducing-peyrsharp/cover.png" alt="Featured image of post Introducing PeyrSharp" /&gt;&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Léo Corporation has been committed to software development for years and has always learn to evolve and improve. We are developing apps and services in C# .NET, and we know it can be frustrating sometimes. We, as software developers, always had this though: “if only they were a library for this.” Therefore, in March 2020, we published LeoCorpLibrary, which was a C# library that contained useful methods. When we started the development of it, we didn&amp;rsquo;t know where the project will go yet. Over the releases, we&amp;rsquo;ve added more and more methods and new features. However, the meaning and the purpose of LeoCorpLibrary was becoming less clear for everyone; it was becoming a mess. This is why we decided to rather not release it fifth version, but instead, we decided to make a brand-new .NET Library, PeyrSharp.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-peyrsharp&#34;&gt;What is PeyrSharp?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PeyrSharp is a C# written library designed to make developers&amp;rsquo; life easier. We&amp;rsquo;ve all written code that we wish we hadn&amp;rsquo;t. PeyrSharp is here to respond to this need; by implementing useful methods in various domains: Mathematics, Web/HTTP requests, unit converters, extensions, environment-related operations, and more!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;a-new-way-to-use-a-library&#34;&gt;A new way to use a library&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unlike LeoCorpLibrary, PeyrSharp is divided in multiples packages:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Core - the basic methods and features of PeyrSharp&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Env - methods related to the file system and to the current execution environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enums - all enumerations used by PeyrSharp&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exceptions - all exceptions used by PeyrSharp&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensions - extension methods that extends basic types such as string, int, double or arrays (T[]).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;UiHelpers - methods related to Windows Forms or to the Windows Presentation Framework (WPF).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All of these modules are included in PeyrSharp; however, PeyrSharp.UiHelpers is only included if you download the package on Windows.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;compatibility&#34;&gt;Compatibility&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some modules of PeyrSharp are targeting features only available in specific operating systems. Thus, some packages aren&amp;rsquo;t available on all platforms.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Package/Platform&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Windows&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;macOS&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Linux + others&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Core&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;✅&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;✅&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;✅&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Env&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;✅&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;⚠️&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;⚠️&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Enums&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;✅&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;✅&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;✅&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Exceptions&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;✅&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;✅&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;✅&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Extensions&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;✅&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;✅&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;✅&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;UiHelpers&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;✅&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;❌&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;❌&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Caption:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;✅ Full Support&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;⚠️ Partial Support&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;❌ Unsupported platform&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;frameworks&#34;&gt;Frameworks&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PeyrSharp is designed to be a modern library, therefore, we decided to ditch support for .NET Framework and .NET Core in favor of .NET 5, 6 and 7.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Note: .NET Framework and .NET Core are not targeted by PeyrSharp, since they are no longer supported.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;documentation&#34;&gt;Documentation&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PeyrSharp has a documentation, making it easy for developers to use it. &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://peyrsharp.leocorporation.dev/&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;Click here&lt;/a&gt; to check the documentation of PeyrSharp.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;packages&#34;&gt;Packages&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PeyrSharp is available on NuGet and &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://github.com/orgs/Leo-Corporation/packages?repo_name=PeyrSharp&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;GitHub Packages&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://www.nuget.org/packages/PeyrSharp&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;PeyrSharp&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://www.nuget.org/packages/PeyrSharp.Core/&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;PeyrSharp.Core&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://www.nuget.org/packages/PeyrSharp.Enums/&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;PeyrSharp.Enums&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://www.nuget.org/packages/PeyrSharp.Env/&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;PeyrSharp.Env&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://www.nuget.org/packages/PeyrSharp.Exceptions/&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;PeyrSharp.Exceptions&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://www.nuget.org/packages/PeyrSharp.Extensions/&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;PeyrSharp.Extensions&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://www.nuget.org/packages/PeyrSharp.UiHelpers/&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;PeyrSharp.UiHelpers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Introducing Gavilya 3</title>
        <link>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/10/introducing-gavilya-3/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 11:17:28 +0200</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/10/introducing-gavilya-3/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/10/introducing-gavilya-3/cover.png" alt="Featured image of post Introducing Gavilya 3" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Almost two years after its first stable release, we&amp;rsquo;re proud to introduce you Gavilya 3, the next evolution of our game launcher.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;a-new-design&#34;&gt;A new design&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With this new iteration of Gavilya, we decided to improve the user experience alongside with the user interface. Gavilya 3 now features a sidebar where you can find the home page, your games, those you played recently, and also your favorites. You can access you notifications directly from sidebar too. Located on the left side of the app, the sidebar gathers all of Gavilya&amp;rsquo;s features in one place. With the new sidebar, all buttons and menus in the title bar have been removed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/10/introducing-gavilya-3/2.png&#34;
	width=&#34;1913&#34;
	height=&#34;1025&#34;
	srcset=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/10/introducing-gavilya-3/2_hu819e2668b60520cfe33743a1a07197ab_614917_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/10/introducing-gavilya-3/2_hu819e2668b60520cfe33743a1a07197ab_614917_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;The new sidebar&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;186&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;447px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;improved-profiles&#34;&gt;Improved profiles&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Profiles are an important feature of Gavilya. In version 3, the profile experience has been improved; we merged your profile page with the profile switcher, making it easier than ever to create and manage profiles in Gavilya.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/10/introducing-gavilya-3/3.png&#34;
	width=&#34;1913&#34;
	height=&#34;1025&#34;
	srcset=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/10/introducing-gavilya-3/3_hufeeae3064479e206e2eea974655124f7_161502_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/10/introducing-gavilya-3/3_hufeeae3064479e206e2eea974655124f7_161502_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;The profile page&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;186&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;447px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;modern-settings&#34;&gt;Modern settings&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The settings window of Gavilya wasn&amp;rsquo;t really intuitive; therefore, we completely re-imagined the settings experience. Settings can now be access straight from the sidebar, and it will shows up in a new page instead of a window. You can now focus more on what you want to do with the new settings page design: It&amp;rsquo;s simple and intuitive. The design is similar to the one used in our other apps.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/10/introducing-gavilya-3/4.png&#34;
	width=&#34;1913&#34;
	height=&#34;1025&#34;
	srcset=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/10/introducing-gavilya-3/4_huce001343679281f0ca22f9da9a68f6d9_74330_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/10/introducing-gavilya-3/4_huce001343679281f0ca22f9da9a68f6d9_74330_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;The new settings page of Gavilya&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;186&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;447px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;new-card-view&#34;&gt;New card view&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;ve also redesigned a key part of Gavilya: The card view. You will notice that the play button is no longer visible by default: To bring it back, simply hover the card and it will show up again. When hovering a card, you can also now see the name of the game at a glance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/10/introducing-gavilya-3/5.png&#34;
	width=&#34;1913&#34;
	height=&#34;1025&#34;
	srcset=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/10/introducing-gavilya-3/5_hu29fed4cacc38e6931e5bdb2b1db76ad6_1578028_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/10/introducing-gavilya-3/5_hu29fed4cacc38e6931e5bdb2b1db76ad6_1578028_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;The redesigned card view&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;186&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;447px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;sorting-options&#34;&gt;Sorting options&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;ve also added sorting options to Gavilya: You can sort your games by the alphabetical order or not.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;other-improvements&#34;&gt;Other improvements&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;ve also improved the design consistency across all the pages of Gavilya. We made improvements to performances and fixed some issues. You can now disable notifications as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can find the full changelog of this release &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://github.com/Leo-Corporation/Gavilya/releases/tag/3.0.0.2210&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;download&#34;&gt;Download&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://bit.ly/Gavilya&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;Click here&lt;/a&gt; to download Gavilya.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;video&#34;&gt;Video&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Check the official trailer for Gavilya 3.&lt;/p&gt;


  &lt;center&gt;
    &lt;iframe width=&#34;560&#34; height=&#34;315&#34; src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/kDGLLng3lCE&#34; title=&#34;YouTube video player&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; allow=&#34;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture&#34; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
  &lt;/center&gt;

</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Introducing InternetTest Pro</title>
        <link>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/08/introducing-internettest-pro/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2022 11:19:43 +0200</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/08/introducing-internettest-pro/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/08/introducing-internettest-pro/cover.png" alt="Featured image of post Introducing InternetTest Pro" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;We are excited to introduce you the next generation of the InternetTest application; it is called InternetTest Pro!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;InternetTest is one of our oldest products still maintained and has evolved during all those years, from a simple utility to check if your internet connection is working as expected, to an app that helps you to locate an IP address, check if websites are working or not, and more.
We are experience creators, and we are more than happy to share with you the pioneer of a new era, InternetTest Pro.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;a-new-and-improved-user-interface&#34;&gt;A new and improved user interface&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/08/introducing-internettest-pro/home.png&#34;
	width=&#34;1260&#34;
	height=&#34;711&#34;
	srcset=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/08/introducing-internettest-pro/home_hu2c7366a6a4a4f9eca05e2adf08b4862a_155819_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/08/introducing-internettest-pro/home_hu2c7366a6a4a4f9eca05e2adf08b4862a_155819_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;The &amp;ldquo;Home&amp;rdquo; dashboard of InternetTest&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;177&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;425px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;InternetTest Pro, also called InternetTest 7, offers a new user interface; you will notice a brand-new side bar with “pinned” actions and different menus. You can access your favorite functionalities using this new side bar, or by using the “Home” dashboard; it is a place specially made for you where you can quickly find useful actions and features. We have added subtle animations as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/08/introducing-internettest-pro/dark_ping.png&#34;
	width=&#34;925&#34;
	height=&#34;572&#34;
	srcset=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/08/introducing-internettest-pro/dark_ping_huf57da0f3ee95b9c25608874b497d475b_377156_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/08/introducing-internettest-pro/dark_ping_huf57da0f3ee95b9c25608874b497d475b_377156_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;The dark theme of InternetTest Pro&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;161&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;388px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are also introducing an improved light and dark theme; the background of the window is no longer white: Instead, there is a subtle mesh gradient with different colors. The accent color is also more used in different part of the app. Finally, you will notice that there are less shades of gray, and more shades of blue used everywhere in InternetTest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;an-experience-conceived-for-you&#34;&gt;An experience conceived for you&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/08/introducing-internettest-pro/gif.gif&#34;
	width=&#34;1920&#34;
	height=&#34;1080&#34;
	srcset=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/08/introducing-internettest-pro/gif_hu0bfa102810c46a57b06a55741c09d3bb_505742_480x0_resize_box.gif 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/08/introducing-internettest-pro/gif_hu0bfa102810c46a57b06a55741c09d3bb_505742_1024x0_resize_box.gif 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;A GIF that shows different Synethia configurations&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;177&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;426px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We want our users to have the best experience possible when they use our apps. We believe that our products should adapt to their needs, and that our users should not have to adapt to the limitations of our applications. Therefore, we want to introduce you Synethia, an algorithm that can understand your habits and which features you’d like to use. When you are using InternetTest Pro, Synethia will collect data on how you spent time with each feature, and which interactions you have made. The data is then analyzed, and this how the “Home” dashboard shows you recommended actions and features. The more you use InternetTest Pro, the more Synethia will be able to understand your needs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now, we are aware that this feature will raise privacy concerns about the data collected, and we want to be fully transparent with you. The data is stored on your device anonymously and is NOT send to Léo Corporation. It is NOT used by any third-party application or company other than InternetTest itself. You have full control over your data; you can reset it or erase it completely. You can, at any time, disable Synethia in the Settings. Synethia cannot interact with other apps or program.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;a-new-set-of-features&#34;&gt;A new set of features&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;InternetTest Pro has all the features included in InternetTest 6, which are: Connection Status, Down Detector, My IP, and Locate an IP. With this new version we are introducing three new features: Ping, IP Config, and WiFi Passwords (recovery).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;ping&#34;&gt;Ping&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/08/introducing-internettest-pro/ping.png&#34;
	width=&#34;1259&#34;
	height=&#34;707&#34;
	srcset=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/08/introducing-internettest-pro/ping_hu853d6b890bcc3dc740451ed783f201ac_168588_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/08/introducing-internettest-pro/ping_hu853d6b890bcc3dc740451ed783f201ac_168588_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;The ping page&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;178&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;427px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Ping feature allows you to send a ping request to specified IP address or URL. It works exactly like the “ping” command in Windows. You can get useful information when you make a ping, such as the maximum/minimum and average duration of each request, the number of packages sent, received, or lost, and the IP address if you provided an URL.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;ip-config&#34;&gt;IP Config&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/08/introducing-internettest-pro/ipconfig.png&#34;
	width=&#34;1263&#34;
	height=&#34;710&#34;
	srcset=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/08/introducing-internettest-pro/ipconfig_hubd67f62cf47da7ae3206913f38c55a6a_154361_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/08/introducing-internettest-pro/ipconfig_hubd67f62cf47da7ae3206913f38c55a6a_154361_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;The new IP Config feature&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;177&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;426px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The IP Config feature works the same as the “ipconfig” command available in the Windows command prompt. You will be able to get a list of all the network interfaces registered on your system. By default, only the connected interfaces details are expanded. You can copy the information of each interface. This information contains: Status (connected/disconnected), the DNS Suffix, the local IPv4 and IPv6 address, the subnet mask, and the default gateway IP address (in IPv4 and IPv6).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;wifi-passwords&#34;&gt;WiFi Passwords&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/08/introducing-internettest-pro/wifi.png&#34;
	width=&#34;1261&#34;
	height=&#34;707&#34;
	srcset=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/08/introducing-internettest-pro/wifi_huf1d30c9a5728e99bb39cb108a1f38ea4_139280_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/08/introducing-internettest-pro/wifi_huf1d30c9a5728e99bb39cb108a1f38ea4_139280_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;The new WiFi Passwords recovery feature&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;178&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;428px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This feature allows you to recover all passwords of all the WiFi networks you have already been connected to. By default, the page is empty for security reasons, you will need to click on the “Get locally stored networks” button to see all registered networks on your device. You can then expand each network details to learn more about the encryption algorithm, the authentication mode, the connection type/mode, and most importantly, the network key. The key is hidden by default; click on the “eye” icon next to it to show the key.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;a-new-history&#34;&gt;A new history&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/08/introducing-internettest-pro/history.png&#34;
	width=&#34;1260&#34;
	height=&#34;711&#34;
	srcset=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/08/introducing-internettest-pro/history_hu68096e7bd2dd89c1e7c35690166843f7_139422_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/08/introducing-internettest-pro/history_hu68096e7bd2dd89c1e7c35690166843f7_139422_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;The history page of InternetTest Pro&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;177&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;425px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are also glad to announce a unified history page. On this page you will be able to see the results of each test made using the “Status” or “Down Detector” feature. You can erase the history at any time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;simplified-settings&#34;&gt;Simplified settings&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are also committed to improvements of the settings page: Some sections are gone because we grouped them in a single category. For example, the default test website and the default HTTP protocol are now in the same “Web” category. The update system has also been reworked, so you can quickly see if InternetTest Pro is up to date or not. The theme and the default page picker have all been simplified.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/08/introducing-internettest-pro/settings.png&#34;
	width=&#34;1262&#34;
	height=&#34;708&#34;
	srcset=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/08/introducing-internettest-pro/settings_huae478a23d0c943eb1125d3ede91da570_110040_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/08/introducing-internettest-pro/settings_huae478a23d0c943eb1125d3ede91da570_110040_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;The settings of InternetTest Pro&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;178&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;427px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-next-for-internettest-6&#34;&gt;What is next for InternetTest 6?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The support for InternetTest 6 will end; it won’t receive new features anymore. InternetTest Pro will not be offered as an upgrade of InternetTest 6 because we consider it as a different product. We will let our users choose whether they want to upgrade or not.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;download&#34;&gt;Download&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://tinyurl.com/DownloadITP7&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;Click here&lt;/a&gt; to explore your new experience with InternetTest Pro.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;video&#34;&gt;Video&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Check the official trailer for InternetTest Pro.&lt;/p&gt;


  &lt;center&gt;
    &lt;iframe width=&#34;560&#34; height=&#34;315&#34; src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/wXTGEAYaRh4&#34; title=&#34;YouTube video player&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; allow=&#34;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture&#34; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
  &lt;/center&gt;

</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Our New Blog</title>
        <link>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/08/our-new-blog/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 09:33:41 +0200</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/08/our-new-blog/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Today, we are releasing a huge update to our blog: We are switching from Blogger to Hugo, a static website generator. This change will give us more control over our content and makes it easier to publish new and exciting articles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-new&#34;&gt;What is new?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The blog is now using a modern responsive theme that support both light and dark mode. We are introducing “Categories”; it is a new way to sort articles. There is now a table of content in every article, you can also see the estimated reading time next to the date. We have added links to our socials as well, and a brand new About page too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-gone&#34;&gt;What is gone?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With this new update, we have decided it is the best time to move on, so our older articles from 2018 to 2020, are no longer available, but they still are on the old blog which will stay accessible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-next&#34;&gt;What is next?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We hope that you will like the modern design; we are excited to post new and better articles on this blog, as a big announcement is coming soon.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>A slight update on our look</title>
        <link>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/07/a-slight-update-on-our-look/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/07/a-slight-update-on-our-look/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/07/a-slight-update-on-our-look/cover.png" alt="Featured image of post A slight update on our look" /&gt;&lt;h2 id=&#34;we-have-a-new-look&#34;&gt;We have a new look!&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As you may have noticed, we’ve updated our font in our logos and websites. We are announcing that we’re ditching the Montserrat font for Hauora Sans. This font gives more personality to our identity, since the old font was one of the most popular sans serif fonts used in apps, websites, and product. The new one is – indeed – like Montserrat, but it adds some small details that makes it better than the old one.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;when-will-this-change-take-effect&#34;&gt;When will this change take effect?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As we said, most of our websites have already received an update. However, our apps haven’t yet. An update should roll out to them this month.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Léo Corporation is always evolving, and we would like to thank our users for taking this journey with us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;image&#34;&gt;Image&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/07/a-slight-update-on-our-look/cover.png&#34;
	width=&#34;3438&#34;
	height=&#34;1146&#34;
	srcset=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/07/a-slight-update-on-our-look/cover_hu11d46245019c0cc4f6837ea1f8635293_782421_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/07/a-slight-update-on-our-look/cover_hu11d46245019c0cc4f6837ea1f8635293_782421_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;The Léo Corporation logo, updated with the new Hauora font.&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;300&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;720px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>We&#39;ve updated our visual identity</title>
        <link>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/01/weve-updated-our-visual-identity/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/01/weve-updated-our-visual-identity/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/01/weve-updated-our-visual-identity/cover.png" alt="Featured image of post We&#39;ve updated our visual identity" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;2021 has been a busy year for Léo Corporation, and 2022 will be focused on how we can improve the user experience across our products.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To start this new year, we’ve slightly updated our visual identity to a more colorful one. You may have seen on our &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://twitter.com/LeoCorpNews&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://www.facebook.com/LeoCorporationSoftwares/&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://www.instagram.com/leocorporation_/&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt; that a more colorful look has been adapted. These colors are – of course – colors of Léo Corporation, but they are also here to bring a more vibrant vibe to our posts. However, we haven’t changed our logo, even though there are now a black and a white variant of it. You will also notice new splash screens that will come to applications that use one on the upcoming weeks.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Introducing the new Status page</title>
        <link>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/08/introducing-new-status-page/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/08/introducing-new-status-page/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/08/introducing-new-status-page/cover.png" alt="Featured image of post Introducing the new Status page" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Software development is often punctuated with bugs, issues and incidents that may impact our users. It might be hard for them to understand why is one our software, service, isn’t working, or why they can’t access our website anymore for instance. We often inform our users of any issues impacting our services on our Twitter account &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://twitter.com/LeoCorpNews&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;@LeoCorpNews&lt;/a&gt;, but some people aren’t aware of the existence of this account, or don’t use Twitter. This is why we’ve created a new website dedicated to “status monitoring”.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This new website is available at &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://status.leocorporation.dev&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;status.leocorporation.dev&lt;/a&gt; and is updated every day. You can quickly see which system is operating normally, and those who don’t. If you are having an issue with one of our services that depend on others, such as our update system, Gavilya’s integration with RAWG, you can come to this website and see if everything is working correctly or not.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We hope that this website helps you to get informed when an issue is occurring.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Introducing Datalya</title>
        <link>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/07/introducing-datalya/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/07/introducing-datalya/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/07/introducing-datalya/cover.png" alt="Featured image of post Introducing Datalya" /&gt;&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Last year, we’ve launched two products: GestionBiblio X and GestionPerso X. They were specialized database management tools. They provided a brand new and modern user interface at the time. The goal was to rewrite the codebase from Visual Basic to C#, to introduce new features and a new design language. However, these two softwares were only available in French, not in English, and they weren’t receiving updates as much as other Léo Corporation’s softwares. This is why we are today introducing the next generation of database management at Léo Corporation: Datalya.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/07/introducing-datalya/cover.png&#34;
	width=&#34;1100&#34;
	height=&#34;650&#34;
	srcset=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/07/introducing-datalya/cover_hu585b845bac6b9b98f4e385dce7b37f4b_23177_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/07/introducing-datalya/cover_hu585b845bac6b9b98f4e385dce7b37f4b_23177_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;The home page of Datalya.&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;169&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;406px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;whats-datalya&#34;&gt;What&amp;rsquo;s Datalya?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Datalya is a modern and yet simple database management software for Windows. The main innovation of Datalya is Blocks. Blocks are different types of input for a user. For instance, you can have a simple text input, to a checkbox input, without forgetting the dropdown input. These Blocks are customizable, you can name theme, add choices, and more. You can even export your Blocks as a Template, so you can reuse them quickly in other databases. In a nutshell, Blocks are used to create your Database.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can find Blocks in the “Creator” part. Talking about parts, Datalya is divided into two parts: The Creator part, and the Database part. We’ve talked about the Creator part already, so let’s move on to the Database part.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/07/introducing-datalya/2.png&#34;
	width=&#34;1100&#34;
	height=&#34;650&#34;
	srcset=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/07/introducing-datalya/2_hu2eef5c95aec75c556b3140a77e649b6b_53904_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/07/introducing-datalya/2_hu2eef5c95aec75c556b3140a77e649b6b_53904_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;The Creator part of Datalya.&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;169&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;406px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Database part is where the database is. You’ll notice a ribbon UI at the top, and the database’s content filling the rest of the window. By default, it’s empty: Indeed, we need to add an item to the database first. You can go to “Edit” tab in the ribbon, and then click on “Add”. You’ll see that a window with your Blocks has appeared, and in this window, you can fill the fields and then add the item.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/07/introducing-datalya/3.png&#34;
	width=&#34;1100&#34;
	height=&#34;650&#34;
	srcset=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/07/introducing-datalya/3_hue7a0290966fbba52ed17248da6e91028_30750_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/07/introducing-datalya/3_hue7a0290966fbba52ed17248da6e91028_30750_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;The Database part of Datalya.&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;169&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;406px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once you’ve added the item, you can edit it, delete it, etc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The other new feature is the possibility to export a database to an Excel spreadsheet. You can go to the “Export” tab of the ribbon and click on “Export to Excel”. Note that Datalya only supports .xlsx files.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/07/introducing-datalya/4.png&#34;
	width=&#34;1100&#34;
	height=&#34;650&#34;
	srcset=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/07/introducing-datalya/4_hu585b845bac6b9b98f4e385dce7b37f4b_23177_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/07/introducing-datalya/4_hu585b845bac6b9b98f4e385dce7b37f4b_23177_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;The home page of Datalya.&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;169&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;406px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When launching Datalya, you’ll see the home screen, this is where all your recent files are shown for you to jump into a database quickly. You can even pin your most important databases if you have a lot of them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Datalya is also customizable: it is available in English and French, and it has a dark mode! You can also change update settings and reset them anytime.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/07/introducing-datalya/5.png&#34;
	width=&#34;1100&#34;
	height=&#34;650&#34;
	srcset=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/07/introducing-datalya/5_huad7e4adbac23ae106fcf61238f387534_36323_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/07/introducing-datalya/5_huad7e4adbac23ae106fcf61238f387534_36323_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;The dark theme of Datalya.&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;169&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;406px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is still a lot of features that we didn’t covered in this article, but we will let you discover them by yourself. We’ve been working on Datalya for a few months now, and we focused on the design and on the user experience with the product, to deliver you an enjoyable experience while working on a database.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As always, Datalya will be free and Open-Source.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;whats-next-for-gestionbiblio-x-and-gestionperso-x&#34;&gt;What’s next for GestionBiblio X and GestionPerso X&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The release of Datalya also means that our old GestionBiblio X and GestionPerso X softwares are now deprecated, and we recommend that the users of theses products switch to Datalya. If you are a user of one of these products, you can create a new database in Datalya by selecting ether the “Books” template or the “People” template.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;website&#34;&gt;Website&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://datalya.leocorporation.dev/&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;Click here&lt;/a&gt; to go the website of Datalya.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;download&#34;&gt;Download&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://tinyurl.com/DownloadDatalya&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;Click here&lt;/a&gt; to download Datalya.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The next chapter for Educ&#39;Maths</title>
        <link>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/07/the-next-chapter-for-educmaths/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/07/the-next-chapter-for-educmaths/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Educ’Maths was a game to test your knowledge in math. It was developed back in 2018, and was released under the name “Educ’Maths”, and later renamed “Educ’Maths 2018”. At the time, Educ’Maths was one of our first and biggest software we’ve ever released. Then, Educ’Maths became a series of games: Educ’Maths 2019, 2020, and finally, 2021. For each edition, we tried to push the limit of the previous one, and we went from a simple quiz game to an interactive and fun game in 2021. In June 2021, 23% of downloaded softwares were Educ’Maths games.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However, we have decided to end the Educ’Maths series here.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In previous blog articles, we told you that 2021 is going to be a big year for Léo Corporation, and indeed, we’ve release in 2021 more softwares and software updates than ever. Our vision has through the years evolved, and today, we want to focus on software creation, not games. This doesn’t mean that we will never release games again, but for now, we want to follow a new path for Léo Corporation. This path is impacted by global changes: We are living in an era where computers are now the center of our lives. The vision of Léo Corporation is to improve people’s productivity. We are doing this by releasing each year, new softwares and new experiences.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This means that there won’t be an “Educ’Maths 2022”, and the support of Educ’Maths games is going end sooner.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For players of Educ’Maths 2020, the end of support date is unchanged: On the 1st of December 2021, the support will end. This implies that Educ’Maths 2020 will no longer receive any updates, or patches.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are also a player of Educ’Maths 2021, the end of support has changed, and it will be the same as Educ’Maths 2020’s, the 1st of December 2021, a year earlier. Like Educ’Maths 2020, Educ’Maths 2021 will no longer receive any updates or patches, but you will still be able to play the game of course.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The end of support also means that you will no longer be able to download Educ’Maths from our website, or from Xalyus Store. About Xalyus Store, the “Games” category is also going away.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We would like to thank again everyone who played Educ’Maths games.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Introducing The new Xalyus Store</title>
        <link>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/05/introducing-new-xalyus-store/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/05/introducing-new-xalyus-store/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/05/introducing-new-xalyus-store/cover.png" alt="Featured image of post Introducing The new Xalyus Store" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Last year, we have launched the successor of the “Léo Corporation Store”, Xalyus Store. It came out with a brand-new design and brand features. Today, we are happy to introduce the next evolution of Xalyus Store.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When we started creating softwares, we always wanted a place where people could download them. We thought making a website was great, and we did so. But we also wanted a place on desktop, where we could showcase and display our apps. Therefore, we create a software called “Store”. With it, you could download any of our softwares directly from your computer. Then, we wanted to have a complete redesign of this app, and so we decided to modernize it by building a brand-new one: Xalyus Store.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Xalyus Store was our redesigned tore, with the same concepts but more polished. However, we encountered the same problem with the “Store”: If we want to add new softwares, update any informations, we needed to update Xalyus Store, which isn’t a great way of distributing new softwares. This is why we are here today, introducing the second major version of Xalyus Store.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;completely-autonomous&#34;&gt;Completely autonomous&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/05/introducing-new-xalyus-store/cover.png&#34;
	width=&#34;1200&#34;
	height=&#34;700&#34;
	srcset=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/05/introducing-new-xalyus-store/cover_hu7f09eeae559180f24b6b08c0accbe99d_69880_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/05/introducing-new-xalyus-store/cover_hu7f09eeae559180f24b6b08c0accbe99d_69880_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;The &amp;ldquo;Home&amp;rdquo; page of Xalyus Store&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;171&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;411px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This next evolution of Xalyus Store is complete autonomous: You don’t have to update it to check if new softwares are available, everything is automatic! You may not see a lot of changes compared to the first version, but they are massive since it is about an entire new infrastructure and delivering system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;modern-design&#34;&gt;Modern design&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/05/introducing-new-xalyus-store/2.png&#34;
	width=&#34;1200&#34;
	height=&#34;700&#34;
	srcset=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/05/introducing-new-xalyus-store/2_huf051724bd68539e5d868d511866d11f8_69473_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/05/introducing-new-xalyus-store/2_huf051724bd68539e5d868d511866d11f8_69473_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;The &amp;ldquo;Apps&amp;rdquo; page of Xalyus Store&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;171&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;411px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To keep our softwares consistent, the new Xalyus Store has a new and modern user interface, alongside with new themes. You can choose between light and dark theme or stick to your system’s default theme if you are using Windows 10.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;trust-and-secure&#34;&gt;Trust and secure&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As you may now, most of our softwares are Open-Source on GitHub. This means that the code of our softwares is available to anyone, even malicious people who may try to inject malicious code in our softwares and distribute an infected copy to you. Xalyus Store is one of our trusted sources for downloading softwares, the risk of having a virus using it, is almost inexistent.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;upgrading&#34;&gt;Upgrading&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The new Xalyus Store is not an update of the first version of Xalyus Store, you’ll need to remove the old Xalyus Store and download the new one.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;download&#34;&gt;Download&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://tinyurl.com/DownloadXalyusStore&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;Click here&lt;/a&gt; to download Xalyus Store.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>New website</title>
        <link>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/05/new-website/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/05/new-website/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/05/new-website/cover.png" alt="Featured image of post New website" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Starting today, leocorp.fr will no longer be our main website, and will be replace by leocorporation.dev.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After a few years using a Wix website, we have made the decision to stop using Wix services and build instead our own website ourselves. We wanted a more personal website that entirely belongs to us, and this is now the case.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For a few weeks now, we have been working on a new website using GitHub Pages for the hosting. You could access the website by entering the “https://leo-corporation.github.io/Leo-Corporation-Web/” URL, but you can now access it by typing “leocorporation.dev” in your browser.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You will notice that the forum is no longer present.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With this change, we also changed the blog URL, you can type “blog.leocorporation.dev” to access the blog quicker.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The new website is – of course – &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://github.com/Leo-Corporation/Leo-Corporation-Web&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;Open-Source&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As we said earlier, this year is going to be a big one for Léo Corporation, so stay tuned for more exciting announcements in the next months, and thanks to everyone supporting Léo Corporation.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Introducing ColorPicker 3</title>
        <link>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/04/introducing-colorpicker-3/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/04/introducing-colorpicker-3/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/04/introducing-colorpicker-3/cover.png" alt="Featured image of post Introducing ColorPicker 3" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;A year ago, we have announced the second major version of ColorPicker, which was a big step forward for ColorPicker. Today, we are proud to announce the third version of ColorPicker, with a new design and new features.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ColorPicker was the first software for developers. Its goal was to empower a part of the development and/or design process: Color selection. Sometimes, when you want to use a color in a project, and you do not know any information about it, like the RGB values, or the HEX color code, it is very frustrating. Therefore, we created ColorPicker. ColorPicker’s main goal was to solve this problem. Using your mouse pointer, you could point a place on your screen, and get information about the color, at the time, you could only get RGB values. Then, we have released ColorPicker 2, with a new design and new features, like the new manual color-picking tool, and the possibility to get HEX color code. With ColorPicker 3, we wanted to put all this features you love, and make them even better.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-new&#34;&gt;What is new?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ColorPicker 3 introduces a brand-new design like &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/02/introducing-passliss.html&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;Passliss’&lt;/a&gt; design, with a navigation bar on the left, and the content on the other side. This minimalist approach is aiming to improve the user experience overall.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/04/introducing-colorpicker-3/cover.png&#34;
	width=&#34;800&#34;
	height=&#34;450&#34;
	srcset=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/04/introducing-colorpicker-3/cover_hu6d49e402343e0aa203165af3337feeff_37446_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/04/introducing-colorpicker-3/cover_hu6d49e402343e0aa203165af3337feeff_37446_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;The &amp;ldquo;Picker&amp;rdquo; page of ColorPicker&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;177&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;426px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ColorPicker 3 also adds a new “Converter” page, to help you convert different color types easier. For instance, you can convert a RGB color to HEX and HSV.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/04/introducing-colorpicker-3/2.png&#34;
	width=&#34;800&#34;
	height=&#34;450&#34;
	srcset=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/04/introducing-colorpicker-3/2_huec19de53eabf445f82e1e5f5c1aa50b6_38186_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/04/introducing-colorpicker-3/2_huec19de53eabf445f82e1e5f5c1aa50b6_38186_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;The &amp;ldquo;Converter&amp;rdquo; page of ColorPicker&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;177&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;426px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ColorPicker 1 was only available in light mode, ColorPicker 2 was only available in dark mode, and ColorPicker is available in both. You can now set in ColorPicker’s settings if you want to use light or dark mode.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/04/introducing-colorpicker-3/3.png&#34;
	width=&#34;800&#34;
	height=&#34;450&#34;
	srcset=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/04/introducing-colorpicker-3/3_hu53e4d7e9ab39922d2f2e2ef1d202128d_40172_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/04/introducing-colorpicker-3/3_hu53e4d7e9ab39922d2f2e2ef1d202128d_40172_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;The dark mode of ColorPicker&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;177&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;426px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;open-source&#34;&gt;Open Source&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With this third version, we have decided to open-source ColorPicker 3, and the Git repository is – of course – available on &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://github.com/Leo-Corporation/ColorPicker&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;GitHub&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;upgrading&#34;&gt;Upgrading&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ColorPicker 3 is not an update and will not be proposed as an update of ColorPicker 2. If you want to upgrade to ColorPicker 3, you will need to download and install ColorPicker 3. Also, ColorPicker 2’s support will end soon, so no more updates will be delivered to it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;download&#34;&gt;Download&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://tinyurl.com/DownloadColorPicker&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;Click here&lt;/a&gt; to download ColorPicker 3.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Introducing InternetTest 5</title>
        <link>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/03/introducing-internettest-5/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/03/introducing-internettest-5/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/03/introducing-internettest-5/cover.png" alt="Featured image of post Introducing InternetTest 5" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Approximately a year ago, we have announced the fourth version of InternetTest. Today, we are proud to announce the InternetTest 5, the next evolution of the utility.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;InternetTest was one of our first software and is also one of the first open-sourced project that we have published on GitHub. InternetTest main purpose was to enable users to check if they are connected to Internet. Why? Because even if you can check it directly by looking to the icon in the Windows system tray, this icon can sometimes be misleading, and therefore we have created InternetTest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today, InternetTest features have diversified and now, you can also localize IPs, check if a website is down, and you can also customize features, such as dark theme and the default test site.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;version-5-codename-syghroni&#34;&gt;Version 5 (Codename Syghroni)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As you lately saw, we are redesigning a lot of our current software, and we are not done yet! InternetTest is now exception, and this fifth version does not include brand new features, but focuses on the user experience and user interface, to make you love InternetTest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As you can see in the pictures below, the new design follows the same guidelines that Passliss or Gerayis uses.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/03/introducing-internettest-5/cover.png&#34;
	width=&#34;800&#34;
	height=&#34;450&#34;
	srcset=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/03/introducing-internettest-5/cover_hu6af9ea77f70ccf042c79c7fbd9e100f3_34252_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/03/introducing-internettest-5/cover_hu6af9ea77f70ccf042c79c7fbd9e100f3_34252_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;The main window of InternetTest 5&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;177&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;426px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/03/introducing-internettest-5/cover.png&#34;
	width=&#34;800&#34;
	height=&#34;450&#34;
	srcset=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/03/introducing-internettest-5/cover_hu6af9ea77f70ccf042c79c7fbd9e100f3_34252_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/03/introducing-internettest-5/cover_hu6af9ea77f70ccf042c79c7fbd9e100f3_34252_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;The main window of InternetTest 5, in dark theme&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;177&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;426px&#34;
	
&gt;
&lt;img src=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/03/introducing-internettest-5/cover.png&#34;
	width=&#34;800&#34;
	height=&#34;450&#34;
	srcset=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/03/introducing-internettest-5/cover_hu6af9ea77f70ccf042c79c7fbd9e100f3_34252_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/03/introducing-internettest-5/cover_hu6af9ea77f70ccf042c79c7fbd9e100f3_34252_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;The Locate IP page of InternetTest 5&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;177&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;426px&#34;
	
&gt;
&lt;img src=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/03/introducing-internettest-5/cover.png&#34;
	width=&#34;800&#34;
	height=&#34;450&#34;
	srcset=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/03/introducing-internettest-5/cover_hu6af9ea77f70ccf042c79c7fbd9e100f3_34252_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/03/introducing-internettest-5/cover_hu6af9ea77f70ccf042c79c7fbd9e100f3_34252_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;The DownDetector page of InternetTest 5&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;177&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;426px&#34;
	
&gt;
&lt;img src=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/03/introducing-internettest-5/cover.png&#34;
	width=&#34;800&#34;
	height=&#34;450&#34;
	srcset=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/03/introducing-internettest-5/cover_hu6af9ea77f70ccf042c79c7fbd9e100f3_34252_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/03/introducing-internettest-5/cover_hu6af9ea77f70ccf042c79c7fbd9e100f3_34252_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;The settings of InternetTest 5&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;177&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;426px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;InternetTest 5 is also using darker colors for dark theme.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;upgrading&#34;&gt;Upgrading&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Be aware that InternetTest 5 will not be proposed as an update of InternetTest 4, if you want to upgrade, you will have to do it manually by downloading InternetTest 5. After installing InternetTest 5, you can remove InternetTest 4, since no updates will be delivered to it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;download&#34;&gt;Download&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://tinyurl.com/DownloadInternetTest&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;Click here&lt;/a&gt; to download InternetTest 5.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Introducing Gerayis</title>
        <link>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/03/introducing-gerayis/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/03/introducing-gerayis/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/03/introducing-gerayis/cover.png" alt="Featured image of post Introducing Gerayis" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;We are starting this month with the release of a new software: Gerayis. Gerayis is the next evolution of Bar Code Generator 2.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s been a few years already since we&amp;rsquo;ve released the first version of Bar Code Generator (at the time, named in french &amp;ldquo;Générateur de codes barre&amp;rdquo;). Then, last year, 2020, we&amp;rsquo;ve released Bar Code Generator 2, with a brand new design, and the possibility to generate QR Codes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The second version main purpose was to deliver to our users, a brand new user experience, while also adding new features.
Gerayis is the next of evolution of Bar Code Generator, with a design and user experience similar to &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/02/introducing-passliss.html&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;Passliss&lt;/a&gt;&#39;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/03/introducing-gerayis/cover.png&#34;
	width=&#34;800&#34;
	height=&#34;450&#34;
	srcset=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/03/introducing-gerayis/cover_hu0b071e93705d6c2f85cb089c7ad7697e_32262_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/03/introducing-gerayis/cover_hu0b071e93705d6c2f85cb089c7ad7697e_32262_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;The &amp;ldquo;Bar Code&amp;rdquo; page of Gerayis&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;177&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;426px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;features&#34;&gt;Features&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Gerayis has the same features than Bar Code Generator 2, but they are improved, like the QR Code generator which is using a different library than Bar Code Generator 2: &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://www.nuget.org/packages/QRCoder&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;QRCoder&lt;/a&gt;.
Gerayis also includes an improved dark theme and an updated language system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/03/introducing-gerayis/2.png&#34;
	width=&#34;800&#34;
	height=&#34;450&#34;
	srcset=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/03/introducing-gerayis/2_huda3afdd284a24668dc6717a232a58de1_34035_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/03/introducing-gerayis/2_huda3afdd284a24668dc6717a232a58de1_34035_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;The &amp;ldquo;QR Code&amp;rdquo; page of Gerayis&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;177&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;426px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;open-source&#34;&gt;Open Source&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Gerayis is Open-Source, and you can check the GitHub repo by &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://github.com/Leo-Corporation/Gerayis&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;clicking here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;download&#34;&gt;Download&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://bit.ly/DownloadGerayis&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;Click here&lt;/a&gt; to download Gerayis.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Password Generator 3: The last release is out</title>
        <link>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/03/password-generator-3-last-release-is-out/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/03/password-generator-3-last-release-is-out/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The release of Password Generator 3 is out, and it&amp;rsquo;s the version 3.7.1.2103.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;changelog&#34;&gt;Changelog&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;new&#34;&gt;New&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added a link to download Passliss&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added a message to download Passliss&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;updated&#34;&gt;Updated&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Updated version and copyright&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Updated logo&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;download&#34;&gt;Download&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://www.mediafire.com/file/jkgl5tsmf4us0x1/G%C3%A9n%C3%A9rateur&amp;#43;de&amp;#43;mots&amp;#43;de&amp;#43;passe&amp;#43;3&amp;#43;Setup.msi/file&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;Click here&lt;/a&gt; to download Password Generator 3.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://www.mediafire.com/file/ohcs00n2nv6zocn/PasslissSetup.exe/file&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;Click here&lt;/a&gt; to download Passliss.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Introducing Passliss</title>
        <link>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/02/introducing-passliss/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/02/introducing-passliss/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/02/introducing-passliss/cover.png" alt="Featured image of post Introducing Passliss" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;After a month of developpment, Passliss, the successor of Password Generator 3 is out and generaly available for the public.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Password Generator is part of our most popular softwares since the launch of the third version. This third version was designed to be built on a more modern platform (C# - Windows Forms) and also to deliver a more modern UI (Guna.UI) For Passliss, we chose to focus on one thing: innovation. Passliss is our second software to be built using WPF, and our first software to use our new design guidelines, which mainely focus on User eXperience (UX) but also on User Interface (UI). Thanks to this guidelines, Passliss is offering to our users an intuitive and modern experience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/02/introducing-passliss/cover.png&#34;
	width=&#34;800&#34;
	height=&#34;450&#34;
	srcset=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/02/introducing-passliss/cover_huffb5f60309ff2ea485e3f5e3b98d2e90_38472_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/02/introducing-passliss/cover_huffb5f60309ff2ea485e3f5e3b98d2e90_38472_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;Passliss&amp;rsquo; main window&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;177&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;426px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;features&#34;&gt;Features&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Passliss offers a few useful features to make password generation easier. Let&amp;rsquo;s start with the password generation customization system, the main page. You an easily customize the password that isgoing to be generated, you can choose if the password will include lower case, upper case, numbers and special caracters. You can also choose the length of the password. You can save your configuration by using Password Configurations, which allows you to save a specific password generation configuration.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/02/introducing-passliss/2.png&#34;
	width=&#34;800&#34;
	height=&#34;450&#34;
	srcset=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/02/introducing-passliss/2_huf93430e73d63529cf08e5a397cb6c34a_44478_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/02/introducing-passliss/2_huf93430e73d63529cf08e5a397cb6c34a_44478_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;Passliss&amp;rsquo; Password configuration feature&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;177&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;426px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Passliss can also evaluate the strenght of a password. There is multiples levels of strenght:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Low, you should change your password&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Medium, adding more complexity to your password would be a nice addition&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good, you can safely use this password&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent, the chances of someone finding your password are near inexistant.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Passliss also has an auto-update system and a dark mode!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/02/introducing-passliss/3.png&#34;
	width=&#34;800&#34;
	height=&#34;450&#34;
	srcset=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/02/introducing-passliss/3_hua77fc20e2ccb0faeebea776ab6a1568e_42317_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/02/introducing-passliss/3_hua77fc20e2ccb0faeebea776ab6a1568e_42317_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;Passliss, in dark mode&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;177&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;426px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;open-source&#34;&gt;Open Source&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Passliss is also Open Source on &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://github.com/Leo-Corporation/Passliss&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;GitHub&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;download&#34;&gt;Download&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://tinyurl.com/Passliss&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;Click here&lt;/a&gt; to download Passliss.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>A new look</title>
        <link>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/02/a-new-look/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/02/a-new-look/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/02/a-new-look/cover.png" alt="Featured image of post A new look" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;2021 is going to be a big year for Léo Corporation. And one of the big announcement this year is our new graphic identity. You may notice, but we&amp;rsquo;ve got a new logo and a new &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://leocorporation.dev/&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;website&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/02/a-new-look/cover.png&#34;
	width=&#34;1920&#34;
	height=&#34;1080&#34;
	srcset=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/02/a-new-look/cover_hu3fa0d624947acb53576bf457d0684c1d_54799_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/02/a-new-look/cover_hu3fa0d624947acb53576bf457d0684c1d_54799_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;Our new logo&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;177&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;426px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is a part of our new direction for this year. The new logo is more coloful than the older one, and has a new font that we are starting to roll out to our customers: Montserrat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But this is not only this. We&amp;rsquo;ve also updated some icons of our softwares:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/02/a-new-look/2.png&#34;
	width=&#34;1000&#34;
	height=&#34;1000&#34;
	srcset=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/02/a-new-look/2_hu5e5743b854f82d16a5f0c05765f4eab5_236801_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/02/a-new-look/2_hu5e5743b854f82d16a5f0c05765f4eab5_236801_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;Bar Code Generator 2 Logo&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;100&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;240px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/02/a-new-look/3.png&#34;
	width=&#34;1000&#34;
	height=&#34;1000&#34;
	srcset=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/02/a-new-look/3_hua143cc6c98a4e9a9609db0061ab0decc_131706_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/02/a-new-look/3_hua143cc6c98a4e9a9609db0061ab0decc_131706_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;ColorPicker 2 Logo&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;100&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;240px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/02/a-new-look/4.png&#34;
	width=&#34;1000&#34;
	height=&#34;1000&#34;
	srcset=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/02/a-new-look/4_hud74d484df1a19483567eb4f95c2386e0_194777_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/02/a-new-look/4_hud74d484df1a19483567eb4f95c2386e0_194777_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;InternetTest Logo&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;100&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;240px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/02/a-new-look/5.png&#34;
	width=&#34;2000&#34;
	height=&#34;2000&#34;
	srcset=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/02/a-new-look/5_hu5325c5e40b6fa01ba016a035212ae06a_78519_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/02/a-new-look/5_hu5325c5e40b6fa01ba016a035212ae06a_78519_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;Passliss Logo&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;100&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;240px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/02/a-new-look/6.png&#34;
	width=&#34;1000&#34;
	height=&#34;1000&#34;
	srcset=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/02/a-new-look/6_hu6ea7d05127779493a3b07ef85ea17abc_264783_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/02/a-new-look/6_hu6ea7d05127779493a3b07ef85ea17abc_264783_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;Xalyus Store Logo&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;100&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;240px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/02/a-new-look/7.png&#34;
	width=&#34;1000&#34;
	height=&#34;1000&#34;
	srcset=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/02/a-new-look/7_hu5254a9c7ffc4bdcc763c54643b1fbfc0_178940_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/02/a-new-look/7_hu5254a9c7ffc4bdcc763c54643b1fbfc0_178940_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;Xalyus Updater Logo&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;100&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;240px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These new logos are going to roll out progressively to our users.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The end of the &#34;Tooly Suite&#34;</title>
        <link>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/02/the-end-of-tooly-suite/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 07 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/02/the-end-of-tooly-suite/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Despite many attempts to create the concept of &amp;ldquo;Suite&amp;rdquo;, we annonce that starting the end of Febuary 2021, the Tooly Suite will no longer be maintained or supported.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;a-look-back&#34;&gt;A look back&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We created the concept of &amp;ldquo;Suite&amp;rdquo; back in 2019, a vision to regroup our different softwares inside a &amp;ldquo;Hub&amp;rdquo;. There was two suite at the time: &amp;ldquo;Essential&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Gestion&amp;rdquo;. The &amp;ldquo;Hub&amp;rdquo; is similar to an app launcher. The first attempt failed, and so did the second. It failed because mainly of this two reasons:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bad UI/UX (User Interface/User eXperience)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Not enough promotion&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is why, during summer 2020, we recreated completely the Essential suite under a new name, the Tooly Suite. This third version was shiped along a brand new design and user experience. Unfortunately, this third attempt also failed, mainly because there wasn&amp;rsquo;t a lot of updates, and also because the concept wasn&amp;rsquo;t being promoted. This third attempt will be our last one as Leo Corporation is going in a new direction.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-does-the-end-of-support-means&#34;&gt;What does the end of support means?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It means that there won&amp;rsquo;t be any updates anymore, and you won&amp;rsquo;t be able to download the Tooly Suite.
It will be removed from our website and Xalyus Store later this month.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;does-this-mean-that-i-wont-be-able-to-use-tooly-suite&#34;&gt;Does this mean that I won&amp;rsquo;t be able to use Tooly Suite?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No. You can still continue to use it, but some features may not work in the future, like the auto-update system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;are-you-going-to-open-source-tooly-suite&#34;&gt;Are you going to Open Source Tooly Suite?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is no plans yet to do so.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;moving-forward&#34;&gt;Moving forward&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We acknowledge the failure of this concept, and we hope that we will learn from the mistakes made so this won&amp;rsquo;t reproduce in the future again.
Thank you to everyone who supported this project.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Introducing Gavilya</title>
        <link>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2020/12/introducing-gavilya/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2020/12/introducing-gavilya/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2020/12/introducing-gavilya/cover.png" alt="Featured image of post Introducing Gavilya" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;ve been working on a new project for a few months, and if you follow us on GitHub, you may already know what it is, but let&amp;rsquo;s introduce what Gavilya is.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Gavilya is a software that brings all your video games together in one place. Today, there is a lot of game launcher that you need to use depending on the game you wanna play. This is often annoying and this is why we created Gavilya.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;integrations-and-features&#34;&gt;Integrations and Features&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Gavilya uses the RAWG.io video games database to get all your games informations automatically. Gavilya uses the RAWG API to get the background image of a game, the game&amp;rsquo;s description and even on wich platforms the game is available on. If you think that the game found by Gavilya in the RAWG database is wrong, you can change the associated game in the &amp;ldquo;Edit&amp;rdquo; window.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can also know which games you played recently, or even know how long you&amp;rsquo;ve played a specific game. Gavilya uses a system that can detect if you are playing a game and count the time you&amp;rsquo;ve been playing it. Sometimes this system doesn&amp;rsquo;t works with games that have a different process name than it&amp;rsquo;s executable file (like Minecraft). This is why you can manually set the process to look for (for Minecraft it&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;javaw&amp;rdquo;).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;open-source&#34;&gt;Open Source&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Gavilya is also one of our open-source projects. You can contribute to the code, report issues and bugs with Gavilya and more. Click here to go to the GitHub repo.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;download&#34;&gt;Download&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://bit.ly/Gavilya&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;Click here&lt;/a&gt; to download Gavilya.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;screenshots&#34;&gt;Screenshots&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2020/12/introducing-gavilya/cover.png&#34;
	width=&#34;960&#34;
	height=&#34;610&#34;
	srcset=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2020/12/introducing-gavilya/cover_hu31c6bb9887c2453f9b181d6f4b8f0637_198112_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2020/12/introducing-gavilya/cover_hu31c6bb9887c2453f9b181d6f4b8f0637_198112_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;The &amp;ldquo;Your Games&amp;rdquo; page of Gavilya.&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;157&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;377px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2020/12/introducing-gavilya/2.png&#34;
	width=&#34;960&#34;
	height=&#34;610&#34;
	srcset=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2020/12/introducing-gavilya/2_hu1956a95ffff0923f57af8ca295105d09_344354_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2020/12/introducing-gavilya/2_hu1956a95ffff0923f57af8ca295105d09_344354_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;The &amp;ldquo;Game Information&amp;rdquo; page of Gavilya.&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;157&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;377px&#34;
	
&gt;
&lt;img src=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2020/12/introducing-gavilya/3.png&#34;
	width=&#34;960&#34;
	height=&#34;610&#34;
	srcset=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2020/12/introducing-gavilya/3_hu1956a95ffff0923f57af8ca295105d09_205061_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2020/12/introducing-gavilya/3_hu1956a95ffff0923f57af8ca295105d09_205061_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;The &amp;ldquo;Games recently played&amp;rdquo; page of Gavilya.&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;157&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;377px&#34;
	
&gt;
&lt;img src=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2020/12/introducing-gavilya/4.png&#34;
	width=&#34;960&#34;
	height=&#34;610&#34;
	srcset=&#34;https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2020/12/introducing-gavilya/4_hu1956a95ffff0923f57af8ca295105d09_264185_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2020/12/introducing-gavilya/4_hu1956a95ffff0923f57af8ca295105d09_264185_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;The &amp;ldquo;Your Games - List&amp;rdquo; page of Gavilya.&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;157&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;377px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
