<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Information on Blog | Léo Corporation</title><link>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/categories/information/</link><description>Recent content in Information on Blog | Léo Corporation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 10:00:27 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/categories/information/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Introducing InternetTest Pro 9</title><link>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2025/08/introducing-internettest-pro-9/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 10:00:27 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2025/08/introducing-internettest-pro-9/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2025/08/introducing-internettest-pro-9/cover.png" alt="Featured image of post Introducing InternetTest Pro 9" />&lt;h2 id="project-overview">Project Overview&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>InternetTest Pro 9 marks a major milestone in the evolution of the application. This release is the result of a complete rewrite, moving to a modern MVVM architecture in WPF and adopting a new design language that fits naturally into Windows 11. The legacy code has been retired in favor of a cleaner, more maintainable structure that will make the project more reliable and future-proof.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>At the visual level, every page has been redesigned. The application now uses a MicaWindow style, giving it a modern, lightweight look that integrates with the system theme and wallpaper. The overall navigation has been streamlined, and the interface is more consistent across features.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="new-features">New Features&lt;/h2>
&lt;h3 id="home-page">Home page&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2025/08/introducing-internettest-pro-9/1.png"
width="950"
height="600"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2025/08/introducing-internettest-pro-9/1_hu732a672af5fa6209d0501d582c67a4d9_51980_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2025/08/introducing-internettest-pro-9/1_hu732a672af5fa6209d0501d582c67a4d9_51980_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="The new Home page dashboard"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="158"
data-flex-basis="380px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>One of the most significant changes in InternetTest Pro 9 is the introduction of the new Home page. This redesigned entry point now provides all the key information about your current connection at a glance. It shows your connection status, WiFi network name, IP address, ISP details, DNS configuration, and speed. In addition, a recent activity section makes it possible to quickly review the last actions performed in the app, which is why the History page has been removed. The Home page is no longer just a landing screen; it is a complete dashboard that centralizes everything you need when launching the app.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="unified-wifi-tools">Unified WiFi Tools&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2025/08/introducing-internettest-pro-9/2.png"
width="950"
height="600"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2025/08/introducing-internettest-pro-9/2_huae4a41c1999bd437e7d6409aa49b75e3_44725_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2025/08/introducing-internettest-pro-9/2_huae4a41c1999bd437e7d6409aa49b75e3_44725_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="The WiFi Tools page"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="158"
data-flex-basis="380px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The WiFi experience has also been improved. In earlier versions, WiFi networks and WiFi password recovery were separate pages. They are now combined into a single page, offering a clearer and more coherent experience for managing wireless connections and recovering saved passwords.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="new-design">New design&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2025/08/introducing-internettest-pro-9/3.png"
width="950"
height="600"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2025/08/introducing-internettest-pro-9/3_hu4d6dfd55d1b69b4e0338e8cab8e252c4_51906_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2025/08/introducing-internettest-pro-9/3_hu4d6dfd55d1b69b4e0338e8cab8e252c4_51906_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="The redesigned Traceroute page"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="158"
data-flex-basis="380px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>All other tools have been modernized as well. The DNS Tool, Traceroute, Ping, and IPConfig pages have been redesigned with a more accessible interface, offering the same depth of information in a cleaner layout. These changes reflect an overall effort to unify the experience while keeping the functionality users rely on.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="retired-features">Retired Features&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>Some features have also been retired in this version. Synethia is no longer included, and support for Windows 7, 8, and 8.1 has been dropped. InternetTest Pro is now focused on Windows 10 and Windows 11, ensuring compatibility with modern technologies while allowing development to move forward without legacy constraints.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="retrospective">Retrospective&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2025/08/introducing-internettest-pro-9/4.png"
width="462"
height="269"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2025/08/introducing-internettest-pro-9/4_hu95d69e76a89e90be32be11ead964fce4_32924_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2025/08/introducing-internettest-pro-9/4_hu95d69e76a89e90be32be11ead964fce4_32924_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="The first version of InternetTest, back in 2018"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="171"
data-flex-basis="412px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>InternetTest has come a long way since its first release. The project started as a simple utility for testing whether your internet connection was working or not. Over time, more tools were added: DNS lookups, traceroute, ping, IP geolocation, and eventually WiFi utilities. Each version expanded its scope, gradually transforming InternetTest into a complete connectivity toolkit for Windows.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>With InternetTest Pro, the application entered a new phase, providing not just isolated tools but a unified platform with a polished design and extended features. Version 9 represents another turning point, as the project undergoes its most ambitious rewrite to date. It brings together everything learned from previous versions into a refined experience that is faster, cleaner, and built for the future.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="download-and-learn-more">Download and Learn More&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>InternetTest Pro 9 will be available for Windows 10 and Windows 11. To learn more about the project and its features, visit the &lt;a class="link" href="https://leocorporation.dev/store/internettest" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>official website&lt;/a> or explore the source code on &lt;a class="link" href="https://github.com/Leo-Corporation/InternetTest" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>GitHub&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>This release is more than just an update. It is the foundation for the next chapter of InternetTest, with a modern architecture, a unified design, and a focus on clarity and usability. Whether you are troubleshooting, monitoring, or simply exploring your connection, InternetTest Pro 9 provides the tools to understand and optimize your internet experience.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Introducing Qrix 3</title><link>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2025/07/introducing-qrix-3/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 13:54:51 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2025/07/introducing-qrix-3/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2025/07/introducing-qrix-3/cover.png" alt="Featured image of post Introducing Qrix 3" />&lt;p>We&amp;rsquo;re excited to unveil Qrix v3, a major release that marks the beginning of a new era for our app. This version isn&amp;rsquo;t just an update — it&amp;rsquo;s a complete rebuild, leveraging the power of the new Next.js App Router. By adopting this modern framework, we&amp;rsquo;ve dramatically improved performance, routing capabilities, and flexibility throughout the entire application.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="whats-new-in-qrix-v3">What&amp;rsquo;s New in Qrix v3&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2025/07/introducing-qrix-3/1.png"
width="2533"
height="1417"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2025/07/introducing-qrix-3/1_hu5b638facaaaa6541fa5d19a2e654acc8_184762_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2025/07/introducing-qrix-3/1_hu5b638facaaaa6541fa5d19a2e654acc8_184762_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="The new Home page of Qrix v3"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="178"
data-flex-basis="429px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>With this release, Qrix introduces a brand new Home page and Settings page, both redesigned from the ground up. The new Home page offers a clearer layout and a smoother user experience, welcoming you with a modern design that puts your most-used features front and center. The Settings page has also been rethought, making configuration easier to navigate and more intuitive, with new options like language selection, theme customization, and a cleaner overall structure.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2025/07/introducing-qrix-3/2.png"
width="2534"
height="1417"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2025/07/introducing-qrix-3/2_hub6e394cbd9786d6f53efce499c8c03e8_148578_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2025/07/introducing-qrix-3/2_hub6e394cbd9786d6f53efce499c8c03e8_148578_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="The new Settings page of Qrix v3"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="178"
data-flex-basis="429px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Another standout feature in Qrix v3 is the new sidebar, built to improve navigation and clarity. It now includes indicators for the current page, better support for accessibility, and a more compact, focused design that works seamlessly across both desktop and mobile devices. Combined with our updated layout system, these changes make Qrix feel faster, more responsive, and more user-friendly at every turn.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="enhanced-features">Enhanced Features&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Under the hood, this release includes dozens of improvements: a fresh theme, localization support, a new versioning system, a smoother mobile layout, and the migration to Radix UI and shadcn/ui for more consistent and accessible components. We&amp;rsquo;ve also added a History page, QR code and Barcode tools, and a host of new utilities that improve the overall experience without getting in your way.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="try-qrix-v3-today">Try Qrix v3 Today&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;a class="link" href="https://qrix.leocorporation.dev" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Try it now&lt;/a> and explore the new experience. As always, we&amp;rsquo;d love your feedback.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="changelog">Changelog&lt;/h2>
&lt;h3 id="new">New&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Initialized new Qrix app with App Router (#100)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added assets&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added main layout (#1001)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added Components&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added new sidebar (#1002)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added Settings hooks&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added components (#1003)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added barcode types&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added new version system&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added fonts&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added new theme (#1003)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added locale service&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added new settings page (#1003)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added the possibility to change language&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added useHistory hook for managing barcode history&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added missing font&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added calendar and contact interfaces&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added Barcode page (#1001)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added QR Code page (#1001)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added shadcn/ui table and drawer&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added History Element component&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added History page (#1001)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added indicator for current page in sidebar (#1002)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Improved theme switcher (#1003)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added Prettier config with Tailwind CSS plugin&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added locales&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added Badge component&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added new Home page&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added Welcome message&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Improved mobile layout&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added placeholder&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="fixed">Fixed&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Fixed an issue with useSettings hook&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Fixed wrong primary color&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Fixed @typescript-eslint/no-explicit-any&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Fixed some UI issues&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Fixed TypeScript errors&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="updated">Updated&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Migrated RadixUI&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item><item><title>Introducing Passliss 5</title><link>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2025/04/introducing-passliss-5/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 18:49:27 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2025/04/introducing-passliss-5/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2025/04/introducing-passliss-5/cover.png" alt="Featured image of post Introducing Passliss 5" />&lt;p>Passliss 5 marks a significant evolution in password management. Built from the ground up with security and user experience in mind, this new version brings together cutting-edge technology and thoughtful design to help you generate, test, and manage strong passwords more efficiently than ever before.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="smarter-passwords-with-ai">Smarter Passwords with AI&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2025/04/introducing-passliss-5/1.png"
width="2560"
height="1440"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2025/04/introducing-passliss-5/1_hub578ff35f295644e48841f1f18b0caf6_151612_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2025/04/introducing-passliss-5/1_hub578ff35f295644e48841f1f18b0caf6_151612_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="The new AI-powered password generation system"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="177"
data-flex-basis="426px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>One of the standout features in Passliss 5 is the new AI-powered password generation system. You can now create strong and unique passwords simply by typing a prompt. Thanks to the integration of OpenAI’s GPT-4o-mini, Passliss can understand your intent and generate passwords that are both secure and context-aware, offering a more intuitive approach to digital protection.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="improved-strength-analysis">Improved Strength Analysis&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2025/04/introducing-passliss-5/2.png"
width="2560"
height="1440"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2025/04/introducing-passliss-5/2_hu750bf8e180af7fe8d375ab2ceed3f20f_114966_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2025/04/introducing-passliss-5/2_hu750bf8e180af7fe8d375ab2ceed3f20f_114966_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="The new Strength page"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="177"
data-flex-basis="426px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The strength analysis tool has been completely redesigned. With a clearer interface and deeper insights, the new Strength page helps you understand not just how strong your password is, but why. Detailed suggestions and real-time feedback guide you toward creating more secure credentials for all your accounts.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="more-control-on-the-generate-page">More Control on the Generate Page&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2025/04/introducing-passliss-5/3.png"
width="2560"
height="1440"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2025/04/introducing-passliss-5/3_hub578ff35f295644e48841f1f18b0caf6_151612_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2025/04/introducing-passliss-5/3_hub578ff35f295644e48841f1f18b0caf6_151612_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="The new Generate page"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="177"
data-flex-basis="426px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The Generate page in Passliss 5 has been expanded with more control and flexibility. You can now toggle between a simplified interface for quick generation and an advanced section for fine-tuning every aspect of your password. There&amp;rsquo;s also support for generating multiple passwords at once and exporting them as CSV, making it ideal for managing several accounts.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="robust-encryption-and-hashing">Robust Encryption and Hashing&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2025/04/introducing-passliss-5/4.png"
width="2560"
height="1440"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2025/04/introducing-passliss-5/4_hu4d4f0ba6fc9b568e0e05fcec5be466c2_91868_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2025/04/introducing-passliss-5/4_hu4d4f0ba6fc9b568e0e05fcec5be466c2_91868_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="The new Encryption page"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="177"
data-flex-basis="426px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Security goes beyond passwords. With the enhanced Encryption page, you can now encrypt and decrypt any string using trusted algorithms like AES and Triple-DES. Passliss 5 also introduces a new hashing section, allowing you to hash sensitive data directly within the app.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="full-customization-and-personalization">Full Customization and Personalization&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2025/04/introducing-passliss-5/5.png"
width="2560"
height="1440"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2025/04/introducing-passliss-5/5_huac0384c0d91a62c2b7b424d87e4b01a0_171295_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2025/04/introducing-passliss-5/5_huac0384c0d91a62c2b7b424d87e4b01a0_171295_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="The new Settings page"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="177"
data-flex-basis="426px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Passliss 5 gives you full control over your environment. From changing the language and theme to setting default values for password length and encryption algorithms, everything is customizable. You can also export and import your preferences, or reset everything to default in a few clicks.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="a-streamlined-and-modern-experience">A Streamlined and Modern Experience&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2025/04/introducing-passliss-5/6.png"
width="2560"
height="1440"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2025/04/introducing-passliss-5/6_hu225fc28fad27f9a6f5a43ddf750b6563_161137_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2025/04/introducing-passliss-5/6_hu225fc28fad27f9a6f5a43ddf750b6563_161137_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="The new Home page"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="177"
data-flex-basis="426px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>With a completely redesigned interface, Passliss 5 offers a clean, modern look that adapts to any screen size. Powered by Next.js, React, and TypeScript, the app is fast, responsive, and reliable. The navigation has been refined to make every feature easy to find and use, and performance has been optimized across the board.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Passliss 5 isn’t just an update — it’s a complete rethinking of what password tools can be. From powerful new components to thoughtful UI improvements, it brings together everything you need to stay safe in a digital world without compromising on ease of use. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re managing a single account or hundreds, Passliss 5 provides the tools and intelligence to do it securely and efficiently.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="launch">Launch&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Passliss 5 is available now. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re discovering it for the first time or upgrading from a previous version, this release is built to meet your needs with precision and care. Step into the future of password management with Passliss 5.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a class="link" href="https://passliss.leocorporation.dev/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Click here&lt;/a> to launch Passliss in your web browser.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="learn-more">Learn more&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;a class="link" href="https://leocorporation.dev/store/passliss" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Click here&lt;/a> to learn more about Passliss&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="changelog">Changelog&lt;/h2>
&lt;h3 id="new">New&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Added basic components&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added locale system&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added assets&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added home page components&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added new components&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added Install App button&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added navbar layout&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added password generation methods&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added shadcn/ui components&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added new browser utilities&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added locales&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added OpenAI&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added Prompt Item&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added Password Item&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added Generate page&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added new navigation system&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added strength suggestion item&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added strength page&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added Select component&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added Encryption page&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added Alert dialog component&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added global version system&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added Theme System&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added locale switcher system&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added Settings page&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added Popover component&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added Activity Item component&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added Timeline component&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added Activity page&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added Checkbox component&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added Preset Item&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added Presets page&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added new Encrypt section&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added new Decrypt section&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added new Hash section&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added Encryption algo field&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added Sonner&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Redesigned Activity Overview section&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added Progress component&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added locales for Strength suggestions&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added new Password Strength system&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added new Strength page&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added locales for Generate page&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added new Simple Section in Generate&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added Advanced Section in Generate page&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added the possibility to generate multiple passwords&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added the possibility to export passwords as CSV&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added new AI section&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added PWA support&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added dev container file&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Improved presets dialog&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Redesigned Preset Editor&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added new components&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Redesigned Strength Dialog&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added new Dashboard Card design&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added new Home page&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="fixed">Fixed&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Fixed button colors&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Fixed navbar style issue&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Fixed icons alignment&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Fixed ts compiler issue&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Fixed several compilation issues&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Fixed scrolling issue&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Fixed typo in default numbers config&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Fixed Activity items is null error&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Fixed typescript issues&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Fixed some UI issues&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Fixed type error&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Fixed layout issue on Chrome&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Fixed scroll issue&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="updated">Updated&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Unified password utils&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Updated ring input color&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Updated dependencies&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Minor UI tweaks&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Simplified password generation process&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Changed default AI model to GPT 4o-mini&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Removed legacy components&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Removed hard coded colors&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Removed old password vision component&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Improved icon size&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item><item><title>Quick Update on the future of Léo Corporation</title><link>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2024/09/quick-update-on-the-future-of-l%C3%A9o-corporation/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2024 15:04:55 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2024/09/quick-update-on-the-future-of-l%C3%A9o-corporation/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2024/09/quick-update-on-the-future-of-l%C3%A9o-corporation/cover.png" alt="Featured image of post Quick Update on the future of Léo Corporation" />&lt;p>Dear Léo Corporation Community,&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I want to share an important update with all of you. As some of you may know, I recently began my university studies, which has been an exciting new chapter in my life. However, this means I now have less time to dedicate to Léo Corporation and its projects.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="what-does-this-mean">What Does This Mean?&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>While Léo Corporation isn’t going anywhere, you’ll notice fewer updates and new releases in the coming years. I will still work on bug fixes and important updates when I can, but my focus will be primarily on my studies. The pace of development will slow, but the quality of our products will remain the same.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="thank-you-for-your-support">Thank You for Your Support&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>I want to sincerely thank all of you for your continued support and enthusiasm. Your feedback and passion have been the driving force behind Léo Corporation’s growth, and I look forward to returning with fresh ideas and updates in the future.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In the meantime, stay connected through our usual channels, and I’ll continue to provide updates as often as I’m able.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Thank you for your understanding!&lt;br>
&lt;strong>Léo Peyronnet&lt;/strong>&lt;br>
Founder, Léo Corporation&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Introducing InternetTest CLI</title><link>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2024/07/introducing-internettest-cli/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 14:24:19 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2024/07/introducing-internettest-cli/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2024/07/introducing-internettest-cli/cover.png" alt="Featured image of post Introducing InternetTest CLI" />&lt;h2 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>InternetTest CLI is a versatile command line interface that extends the robust capabilities of InternetTest Pro to your terminal. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a network administrator, a developer, or simply a tech enthusiast, InternetTest CLI empowers you with powerful network diagnostic tools at your fingertips. From locating IP addresses to sending ping requests, retrieving DNS information, and more, this tool is designed to enhance your network troubleshooting and management tasks.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="features">Features&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>InternetTest CLI offers the same comprehensive set of features delivered by InternetTest Pro to meet your network diagnostic needs:&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Locate IP addresses&lt;/strong>: Quickly find the geographical location of IP addresses.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Send ping requests&lt;/strong>: Test the reachability of a host on an IP network.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Get DNS information&lt;/strong>: Retrieve detailed DNS records for any domain.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Check if a website is down&lt;/strong>: Verify the status of websites.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Retrieve public IP address information&lt;/strong>: Get information about your public IP address.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Execute traceroutes&lt;/strong>: Trace the path that packets take to reach a destination.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Retrieve saved WiFi passwords&lt;/strong>: Access your stored WiFi passwords (&lt;em>Windows only&lt;/em>).&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="installation">Installation&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Getting started with InternetTest CLI is straightforward. Download the latest release by choosing your platform below:&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;a class="link" href="https://www.mediafire.com/file/ryyi06667u4kwzc/itcli-win-x64.zip/file" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Windows (x64) - ZIP file&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;a class="link" href="https://www.mediafire.com/file/pv6dg8e62xd1wzm/itcli-osx-x64.zip/file" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>macOS (x64) - ZIP file&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;a class="link" href="https://www.mediafire.com/file/rflhxkb1xubgl1x/itcli-linux-x64.tar/file" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Linux (x64) - TAR file&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>Once you have downloaded and extracted the file, you can run the CLI in a terminal. Please note that you may have to grant permissions or execute the program as administrator depending on your local security policy and platform.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="usage">Usage&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Once installed, using InternetTest CLI is simple. The general syntax for commands is:&lt;/p>
&lt;div class="highlight">&lt;div class="chroma">
&lt;table class="lntable">&lt;tr>&lt;td class="lntd">
&lt;pre tabindex="0" class="chroma">&lt;code>&lt;span class="lnt">1
&lt;/span>&lt;span class="lnt">2
&lt;/span>&lt;/code>&lt;/pre>&lt;/td>
&lt;td class="lntd">
&lt;pre tabindex="0" class="chroma">&lt;code class="language-sh" data-lang="sh">&lt;span class="line">&lt;span class="cl">itcli &lt;span class="o">[&lt;/span>options&lt;span class="o">]&lt;/span>
&lt;/span>&lt;/span>&lt;span class="line">&lt;span class="cl">itcli &lt;span class="o">[&lt;/span>command&lt;span class="o">]&lt;/span> &lt;span class="o">[&lt;/span>...&lt;span class="o">]&lt;/span>
&lt;/span>&lt;/span>&lt;/code>&lt;/pre>&lt;/td>&lt;/tr>&lt;/table>
&lt;/div>
&lt;/div>&lt;p>You can learn more on the &lt;a class="link" href="https://github.com/Leo-Corporation/InternetTestCLI" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>official GitHub&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="conclusion">Conclusion&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>InternetTest CLI brings powerful network diagnostic tools to your command line, enhancing your ability to manage and troubleshoot network issues effectively. Explore its features, report any bugs, request new features, and stay updated with the latest releases through the GitHub repository.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>What's next for Léo Corporation</title><link>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2024/06/whats-next-for-l%C3%A9o-corporation/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 14:49:18 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2024/06/whats-next-for-l%C3%A9o-corporation/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2024/06/whats-next-for-l%C3%A9o-corporation/cover.png" alt="Featured image of post What's next for Léo Corporation" />&lt;p>You may have noticed that since May 2024, Léo Corporation has been a bit quiet on the update front. If you&amp;rsquo;ve been wondering why our stream of new features and enhancements seemed to pause, you&amp;rsquo;re not alone. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re here to share what&amp;rsquo;s next for Léo Corporation.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="why-updates-are-paused">Why updates are paused&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>We didn&amp;rsquo;t released new updates to Léo Corporation&amp;rsquo;s products mostly because we were busy on other projects, like the development of Synapsy products, and also because of a lack of time. But don&amp;rsquo;t worry! This doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean that our apps won&amp;rsquo;t receive any new updates; actually, there&amp;rsquo;s a lot coming next month, as we plan to resume the update cycle!&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="whats-next-big-things-are-coming">What&amp;rsquo;s Next? Big Things Are Coming!&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Now, for the exciting part. We&amp;rsquo;re thrilled to announce that starting in July, Léo Corporation will be back with a bang!&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="upcoming-updates">Upcoming Updates&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Enhanced Features: We’re adding new functionalities to our existing products that will improve usability and performance. Expect smoother interfaces, faster processes, and more intuitive user experiences.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Bug Fixes and Improvements: We&amp;rsquo;ve been listening to your feedback and addressing issues to make our products more reliable and efficient.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="new-products-on-the-horizon">New Products on the Horizon&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>But that&amp;rsquo;s not all! Alongside our updates, we will introduce new apps and programs, notably related to InternetTest Pro, as we have bigger ambitions for this product. We are not going to reveal everything in this article, but stay tuned!&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="a-thank-you-to-our-community">A Thank You to Our Community&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>We want to take a moment to thank you – our incredible community of users. Your patience, support, and continued engagement mean the world to us. We are excited about what the future holds and are committed to delivering products and updates that exceed your expectations.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In conclusion, while we have been on a brief hiatus, this pause has been crucial for our growth and innovation. Come July, we promise it will be worth the wait. Stay tuned for announcements and get ready to explore a new era of Léo Corporation.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Thank you for being part of our journey. The best is yet to come!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Introducing Passliss 4</title><link>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2024/03/introducing-passliss-4/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 11:15:09 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2024/03/introducing-passliss-4/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2024/03/introducing-passliss-4/cover.png" alt="Featured image of post Introducing Passliss 4" />&lt;p>In an era where cybersecurity threats are becoming increasingly sophisticated, the importance of robust password management cannot be overstated. With each passing day, we entrust more of our personal and professional lives to the digital realm, necessitating the need for strong, unique passwords to safeguard our sensitive information. This fourth major version of Passliss is here to answer new needs when it comes to password generation. Let&amp;rsquo;s see what&amp;rsquo;s new!&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="introducing-presets">Introducing Presets&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2024/03/introducing-passliss-4/2.png"
width="1793"
height="992"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2024/03/introducing-passliss-4/2_huc5106c705e529479274fac5c1c15d7f7_450889_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2024/03/introducing-passliss-4/2_huc5106c705e529479274fac5c1c15d7f7_450889_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="The new Presets page"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="180"
data-flex-basis="433px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>With Passliss for the Web 4, we are thrilled to introduce a groundbreaking new feature: Presets. Presets revolutionize the password generation experience by allowing users to create default configurations that align with their specific preferences and security needs. Gone are the days of manually adjusting settings for each password generation session—Presets streamline the process, ensuring that users can generate passwords tailored to their exact specifications with just a few clicks.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="customization-made-easy">Customization Made Easy&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2024/03/introducing-passliss-4/3.png"
width="1790"
height="997"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2024/03/introducing-passliss-4/3_hu2eb21bc5f8bc1be8a1148155228875b0_140160_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2024/03/introducing-passliss-4/3_hu2eb21bc5f8bc1be8a1148155228875b0_140160_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="The new Presets creation assistant"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="179"
data-flex-basis="430px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Presets empower users to customize every aspect of their password generation process, from the inclusion of uppercase and lowercase letters to the incorporation of numbers and special characters. Want a password that includes uppercase letters and numbers but excludes special characters? No problem. With Presets, users can effortlessly define their desired configuration, eliminating the need for repetitive adjustments.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="fine-tuned-control">Fine-Tuned Control&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2024/03/introducing-passliss-4/4.png"
width="1784"
height="995"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2024/03/introducing-passliss-4/4_hud49d5a65d7d29857b58fe3d280629412_145791_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2024/03/introducing-passliss-4/4_hud49d5a65d7d29857b58fe3d280629412_145791_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="You can customize and adjust each setting when creating a preset."
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="179"
data-flex-basis="430px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>What sets Presets apart is its granular level of control over password generation parameters. For each character type—uppercase, lowercase, numbers, and special characters—users can set both a minimum and maximum number of characters to include in their passwords. This level of flexibility ensures that users can strike the perfect balance between complexity and memorability, catering to their individual preferences and security requirements.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="target-length-setting">Target Length Setting&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2024/03/introducing-passliss-4/5.png"
width="1795"
height="998"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2024/03/introducing-passliss-4/5_hu369f427d7ebdd9206a53335757875371_131632_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2024/03/introducing-passliss-4/5_hu369f427d7ebdd9206a53335757875371_131632_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="You can now select a preset when generating a password"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="179"
data-flex-basis="431px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In addition to specifying the minimum and maximum character counts for each character type, Presets also allow users to set a target length for their passwords. Whether you prefer shorter, more concise passwords or longer, more robust ones, you can easily define your desired password length with a single setting. Presets then intelligently adjust the distribution of characters within the password to meet your specified target length, ensuring that each generated password is optimized for both security and usability.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="effortless-password-generation">Effortless Password Generation&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2024/03/introducing-passliss-4/1.png"
width="1789"
height="990"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2024/03/introducing-passliss-4/1_hu1edd7fa184e62952f2d6088bed4ed4d7_468454_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2024/03/introducing-passliss-4/1_hu1edd7fa184e62952f2d6088bed4ed4d7_468454_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="Once you created a preset, you can use it effortlessly in the Generate page."
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="180"
data-flex-basis="433px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>With Presets, generating secure passwords has never been easier. Once users have configured their desired preset settings, they can simply select their preferred preset from the dropdown menu when generating a new password. Passliss for the Web 4 will then automatically apply the preset configuration, instantly generating a password that aligns with the user&amp;rsquo;s specifications. This streamlined process saves time and eliminates the guesswork, allowing users to focus on what matters most—keeping their online accounts secure.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="other-improvements">Other improvements&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>We also took time to improve some areas of the app and improve existing features. This fourth major version isn&amp;rsquo;t a complete revolution, but rather focuses on improving the user experience across the app.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="launch">Launch&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;a class="link" href="https://passliss.leocorporation.dev/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Click here&lt;/a> to launch Passliss in your web browser.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="learn-more">Learn more&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;a class="link" href="https://leocorporation.dev/store/passliss" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Click here&lt;/a> to learn more about Passliss&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Introducing ColorPicker Max 6</title><link>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2024/02/introducing-colorpicker-max-6/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2024/02/introducing-colorpicker-max-6/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2024/02/introducing-colorpicker-max-6/cover.png" alt="Featured image of post Introducing ColorPicker Max 6" />&lt;h2 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Last year, we&amp;rsquo;ve introduce the next iteration of ColorPicker: ColorPicker Max (v5). The goal was to create a more advanced tool for developers, designers and artists by introducing a new set of features. With ColorPicker Max 6, this goal remains almost the same: We added several new features while providing at the same time a better user experience across the app. Let&amp;rsquo;s see all the new features introduces by this 6th major version of ColorPicker.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="redesigned-dashboard">Redesigned dashboard&lt;/h2>
&lt;h3 id="new-cards">New cards&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2024/02/introducing-colorpicker-max-6/1.png"
width="950"
height="600"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2024/02/introducing-colorpicker-max-6/1_hu3b96c2176be6426c108dad96f31069f9_190148_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2024/02/introducing-colorpicker-max-6/1_hu3b96c2176be6426c108dad96f31069f9_190148_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="The new dashboard of ColorPicker Max 6"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="158"
data-flex-basis="380px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We are introducing a brand-new design for page cards in the dashboard: They look more modern and interactive, which enhances at the same time the experience new users will have when they first launch the app.
With a clean and intuitive layout, navigating through the Home page is now a visually stimulating experience, inviting you to explore the endless possibilities of color manipulation.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="quick-actions">Quick Actions&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>In our quest to make color exploration more intuitive, we&amp;rsquo;ve introduced a brand-new Quick Actions system right at your fingertips. Say goodbye to endless clicks and complicated menus – with Quick Actions, performing common tasks is now just a tap away.&lt;/p>
&lt;h4 id="select-a-color">Select a Color&lt;/h4>
&lt;p>Need to pinpoint that perfect shade of blue or capture the essence of a vibrant sunset? Simply select the &amp;ldquo;Select a Color&amp;rdquo; Quick Action, and our intuitive color picker tool will empower you to choose one from your screen.&lt;/p>
&lt;h4 id="contrast-ratio">Contrast Ratio&lt;/h4>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2024/02/introducing-colorpicker-max-6/2.png"
width="950"
height="600"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2024/02/introducing-colorpicker-max-6/2_hu3b96c2176be6426c108dad96f31069f9_196145_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2024/02/introducing-colorpicker-max-6/2_hu3b96c2176be6426c108dad96f31069f9_196145_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="The &amp;ldquo;Contrast Ratio&amp;rdquo; quick action"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="158"
data-flex-basis="380px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Ensuring accessibility is essential in design, and with the &amp;ldquo;Contrast Ratio&amp;rdquo; Quick Action, you can effortlessly evaluate the legibility of text against different background colors. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re fine-tuning the typography of a website or crafting an attention-grabbing poster, achieving optimal contrast has never been simpler.&lt;/p>
&lt;h4 id="random-palette">Random Palette&lt;/h4>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2024/02/introducing-colorpicker-max-6/3.png"
width="950"
height="600"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2024/02/introducing-colorpicker-max-6/3_hu3b96c2176be6426c108dad96f31069f9_180383_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2024/02/introducing-colorpicker-max-6/3_hu3b96c2176be6426c108dad96f31069f9_180383_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="The &amp;ldquo;Random Palette&amp;rdquo; quick action"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="158"
data-flex-basis="380px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Need some inspiration? You can now generate color palettes thanks to the &amp;ldquo;Random Palette&amp;rdquo; Quick Action, which generates a harmonious array of colors at the click of a button. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re seeking inspiration for your next project or simply want to explore new color combinations, this feature promises to spark your creativity and ignite your imagination.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="redesigned-color-details-window">Redesigned Color Details window&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2024/02/introducing-colorpicker-max-6/4.png"
width="950"
height="600"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2024/02/introducing-colorpicker-max-6/4_hu20fe492b66de74f98d3225bf014a0b50_189637_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2024/02/introducing-colorpicker-max-6/4_hu20fe492b66de74f98d3225bf014a0b50_189637_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="The redesigned Color Details window"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="158"
data-flex-basis="380px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We also took time to redesign the Color Details window, bringing a clear and more intuitive user interface. We added new hover effects, and improve the content alignment, making it more easy for you to work with this feature.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="image-color-extractor">Image Color Extractor&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2024/02/introducing-colorpicker-max-6/5.png"
width="950"
height="600"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2024/02/introducing-colorpicker-max-6/5_huf0501c4528c137fd395e625398366033_252005_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2024/02/introducing-colorpicker-max-6/5_huf0501c4528c137fd395e625398366033_252005_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="The new Image Color Extractor page"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="158"
data-flex-basis="380px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In our latest update, ColorPicker Max introduces an exciting new feature: Image Color Extraction. Now, unlocking the palette of colors from your favorite images is just a click away. With a range of customizable options, this tool puts the power of color exploration directly into your hands.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="import-images-with-ease">Import Images with Ease&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>Gone are the days of manual color picking. With the ability to import images directly into ColorPicker Max, you can effortlessly extract the vibrant hues from your chosen visuals.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="color-analysis">Color Analysis&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>With the Image Color Extractor can you retrieve all colors present in an image, but you can also view their frequencies, providing valuable insights into the dominant tones at play.
Plus, you can fine-tune the color extraction process with precision settings, allowing you to adjust the level of detail to suit your needs. Please note that if you use large images, the more precise the extraction is, the longer the process will take.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="export-the-extracted-data">Export the extracted data&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>Seamlessly export your extracted colors to a CSV file for further analysis or integration into your projects. With support for both comma and semicolon formats, sharing and collaborating with colleagues has never been easier.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="contrast-grid">Contrast Grid&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2024/02/introducing-colorpicker-max-6/6.png"
width="950"
height="1039"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2024/02/introducing-colorpicker-max-6/6_hu0cf43f25caa9b778dbe729be34bb5428_315563_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2024/02/introducing-colorpicker-max-6/6_hu0cf43f25caa9b778dbe729be34bb5428_315563_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="The new contrast grid feature"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="91"
data-flex-basis="219px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>ColorPicker Max 6 brings a new feature to the app: The Contrast Grid, which is designed to revolutionize your color selection process. With a focus on accessibility and efficiency, this tool provides invaluable insights into the contrast ratios of your chosen colors, empowering you to make informed design decisions effortlessly.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="visualize-contrast-with-ease">Visualize Contrast with Ease&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>With the Contrast Grid feature, gaining a comprehensive understanding of color contrast has never been simpler. By generating a grid that showcases the contrast ratios between your selected color and a range of background hues, you can visualize how your color choices impact readability and accessibility across various contexts.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="optimize-accessibility">Optimize Accessibility&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2024/02/introducing-colorpicker-max-6/7.gif"
width="1080"
height="1080"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2024/02/introducing-colorpicker-max-6/7_hu2835ed094198e3090ec8d6236870962d_274670_480x0_resize_box_1.gif 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2024/02/introducing-colorpicker-max-6/7_hu2835ed094198e3090ec8d6236870962d_274670_1024x0_resize_box_1.gif 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="The different grid obtains by selecting different scores"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="100"
data-flex-basis="240px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Incorporating accessibility principles into your design workflow is crucial, and the Contrast Grid feature makes it easier than ever. By identifying the best contrast scores, you can ensure that your content is easily legible for all users, regardless of their visual abilities. You can get more details about each color by right-clicking one in the grid.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="new-customization-options">New customization options&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>With the latest update to ColorPicker Max, users now have the option to customize their HEX value formatting to either uppercase or lowercase by default. This small yet significant enhancement allows for a more personalized experience, taking into account your individual preferences and streamlining workflow efficiency.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="how-to-upgrade-from-colorpicker-max-5">How to upgrade from ColorPicker Max 5?&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>This new version doesn&amp;rsquo;t introduce breaking changes, therefore you will be able to upgrade directly through the app by checking for updates in the Settings page. However, please note that ColorPicker Max 6 requires the .NET 8 Windows Runtime to be installed on your system. If the .NET 8 Windows Runtime is not installed, ColorPicker will ask you to install it. Finally, if you use the portable version, you will have to download the app executable file again, but your settings will remain unchanged.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="download-the-app">Download the app&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;a class="link" href="https://tinyurl.com/DownloadColorPickerMax" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Click here&lt;/a> to download ColorPicker Max.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a class="link" href="https://leocorporation.dev/store/colorpickermax" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Learn More&lt;/a> about ColorPicker Max.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="full-changelog">Full changelog&lt;/h2>
&lt;h3 id="new">New&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Added new navigation system (#369)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added new navigation style (#369)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Redesigned Color window (#370)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Redesigned page card (#371)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added &amp;ldquo;Select a Color&amp;rdquo; quick action (#372)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added contrast quick action (#372)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added palette quick action (#372)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added the possibility to expand code areas in Gradient page (#373)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added header in Quick Actions (#372)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Created Image Extractor page (#374)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added translations (#374)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added Image Item (#374)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added Color Frequence Item (#374)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added the possibility to get all colors and their frequencies of an image (#375)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Limited amount of colors to display (#375)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added the possibility to set precision in Image Extractor (#376)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added the possibility to delete an image (#374)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added the possibility to clear images (#374)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added border for Color Displayer (#374)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added the possibility to export all colors to a CSV File (#377)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added the possibility to import multiple images (#378)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added the possibility to show a maximum number of colors (#379)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added the possibility to sort colors by their frequencies (#380)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added placeholder (#374)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added the possibility to get color details in Color Extractor (#374)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Created Contrast Grid page (#381)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added the possibility to input a color (#381)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added Color Grid item (#382)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added the possibility to get the contrast grid of a color (#382)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added translations (#383)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added the possibility to only show the best scores (#383)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added the possibility to get details of a color (#384)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added the possibility to use upper cases or lower cases for HEX (#385)&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="fixed">Fixed&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Fixed missing style issue&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Fixed alignment issue&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Fixed an issue with dark mode&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Fixed toggle issue&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="updated">Updated&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Updated translations (#372)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Improved CheckBox style&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Image area is hidden when there is no image (#374)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Upgraded to .NET 8&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Applied .NET 8 Coding style&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Removed Action Card&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item><item><title>Introducing InternetTest Pro 8</title><link>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2024/01/introducing-internettest-pro-8/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2024/01/introducing-internettest-pro-8/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2024/01/introducing-internettest-pro-8/cover.png" alt="Featured image of post Introducing InternetTest Pro 8" />&lt;h2 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>In 2018, we introduced InternetTest as a straightforward utility designed to check your internet connection. Since then, the app has undergone significant enhancements, embracing both new features and sleek designs.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The 2020 release, InternetTest 4, marked a notable milestone by incorporating advanced functionalities such as the IP Locator and Down Detector. Subsequently, in the following year, InternetTest 5 was unveiled, representing a major leap forward with a modernized codebase that laid the foundation for version 6.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The pinnacle of our journey arrived in 2022 with the launch of InternetTest Pro 7 – a revolutionary iteration that set itself apart from its predecessors. This version introduced groundbreaking features, including a WiFi password recovery utility, a fresh design, and a user-centric approach.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Today, we are thrilled to present the latest advancement in the InternetTest series: InternetTest Pro 8. This iteration elevates your experience to unprecedented heights, building upon the legacy of its predecessors and delivering a seamless blend of cutting-edge features and user-friendly design.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="features">Features&lt;/h2>
&lt;h3 id="new-dashboard">New dashboard&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2024/01/introducing-internettest-pro-8/1.png"
width="950"
height="600"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2024/01/introducing-internettest-pro-8/1_hue7d9d5dff824412dd4b279896d4435bf_231185_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2024/01/introducing-internettest-pro-8/1_hue7d9d5dff824412dd4b279896d4435bf_231185_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="The new dashboard of InternetTest Pro 8"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="158"
data-flex-basis="380px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We are proud to unveil the new InternetTest Pro 8 dashboard: We turned the home page of InternetTest to a place where you can quickly get the information your need at a glance. Indeed, we added a new information section where you can check the status of your connection, your network&amp;rsquo;s name and your public IP address. Furthermore, we decided to rethink the &amp;ldquo;Suggested actions&amp;rdquo; section by replacing it with &amp;ldquo;Quick action&amp;rdquo;: You can now easily run a speed test, recover lost WiFi passwords and connect to a network in just a few clicks. Alongside with these improvements you will also notice that we decided to improve the design of the feature cards, adding more depth to the app&amp;rsquo;s interface.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>However, you will notice that some of the features added to the dashboard were previously available in the &amp;ldquo;Status&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;My IP&amp;rdquo; page, and this is why we made the decision to remove theses two pages from the app. This change will make the app less crowded with basic pages that only included a single feature.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="redesigned-downdetector-page">Redesigned DownDetector page&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2024/01/introducing-internettest-pro-8/2.png"
width="950"
height="600"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2024/01/introducing-internettest-pro-8/2_hu2743643dc44fa41dc3380701191b20e8_199058_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2024/01/introducing-internettest-pro-8/2_hu2743643dc44fa41dc3380701191b20e8_199058_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="The redesigned DownDetector page of InternetTest Pro 8"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="158"
data-flex-basis="380px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Previously, the DownDetector page posed challenges for new users due to its less-than-intuitive design, characterized by a cluttered UI with numerous elements. Recognizing the need for improvement, we took a fresh approach to this feature with the release of InternetTest Pro 8.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In our redesign, we have streamlined the user experience by introducing a more user-friendly interface. Now, you&amp;rsquo;ll find a designated box where you can input the URL of a website for inclusion in the verification process. This allows you to compile a list of websites that will undergo testing when you click the &amp;ldquo;Test all websites&amp;rdquo; button. On the left side, a new &amp;ldquo;Scheduled Tests&amp;rdquo; section has been incorporated, enabling you to efficiently schedule tests at specified intervals for seamless execution. With these enhancements, monitoring website performance has never been more straightforward and accessible.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="new-customization-options">New customization options&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2024/01/introducing-internettest-pro-8/3.png"
width="950"
height="600"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2024/01/introducing-internettest-pro-8/3_hu2743643dc44fa41dc3380701191b20e8_156790_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2024/01/introducing-internettest-pro-8/3_hu2743643dc44fa41dc3380701191b20e8_156790_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="The settings page of InternetTest Pro 8, with new options expanded"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="158"
data-flex-basis="380px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>With the features previously mentioned, we decided to add new customization options. In the settings of the app, you can now provide a default time interval to use when using scheduled tests in the DownDetector page. In addition, we also added the possibility to hide by default disabled network adapters in the WiFi Networks page.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="instant-theme-switching">Instant theme switching&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2024/01/introducing-internettest-pro-8/4.gif"
width="1920"
height="1080"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2024/01/introducing-internettest-pro-8/4_huf3c03b556b46d4ddc37885d531ed1c89_407232_480x0_resize_box_1.gif 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2024/01/introducing-internettest-pro-8/4_huf3c03b556b46d4ddc37885d531ed1c89_407232_1024x0_resize_box_1.gif 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="Changing the theme no longer requires a restart of the application, and is done instantly"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="177"
data-flex-basis="426px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>InternetTest Pro 8 also brings a brand new theming system that is more flexible and dynamic. Indeed, you can now change the theme of the app without having to restart it. Speaking of theme, you will also notice that we updated to background mesh gradient for the main window. Plus, we redesigned some styles of navigation button making them more consistent with the rest of the app.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="improved-codebase">Improved codebase&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>When InternetTest Pro was launched in 2022, a standout addition was the incorporation of Synethia into the dashboard. Synethia, an algorithm designed to analyze user preferences within the app, utilized collected data&lt;a href="#note-1">&lt;sup>(1)&lt;/sup>&lt;/a> to craft a personalized dashboard. This tailored interface suggested the most relevant features based on individual usage patterns. Initially, the integration was manually executed without the official package, which is now offered by Devyus, the creators of Synethia.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In this 8th major version, we dedicated time to completely reworking the Synethia implementation, now leveraging the official Synthia package. It&amp;rsquo;s important to note that upgrading from InternetTest Pro 7 will result in the loss of previously collected data.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Additionally, we invested effort in addressing numerous issues and bugs within the app, resulting in improved overall stability. These enhancements contribute to a more seamless and reliable user experience.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="portable-mode">Portable mode&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>Introducing a new level of flexibility, InternetTest Pro 8 now offers users the choice between two distinct versions: Setup and Portable. The Setup version involves a traditional installation process, while the Portable option provides a convenient alternative, allowing users to run the app without the need for installation through a portable executable file. It&amp;rsquo;s important to note that while Portable mode delivers heightened convenience, some features, such as automatic updates, are not available. For users opting for Portable mode, updating the application requires redownloading the updated portable executable file to ensure access to the latest enhancements. This choice empowers users to tailor their experience based on their preferences and usage requirements.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="get-the-app">Get the app&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>InternetTest Pro is available on Windows and requires the .NET 6 Windows Desktop Runtime. Please note that in the future, we plan to upgrade to the .NET 8 Windows Desktop Runtime which will be needed to execute the app.&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;a class="link" href="https://tinyurl.com/DownloadITP7" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Click here&lt;/a> to get the &lt;strong>Setup&lt;/strong> version of InternetTest Pro&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;a class="link" href="https://tinyurl.com/DownloadITPP" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Click here&lt;/a> to get the &lt;strong>Portable&lt;/strong> version of InternetTest Pro&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>&lt;sup id="note-1">(1)&lt;/sup>: Synethia operates by collecting and storing data anonymously on your computer. It&amp;rsquo;s essential to underscore that no data is transmitted to Léo Corporation or any third-party entities.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>2023 - The biggest year ever for Léo Corporation</title><link>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/12/2023-the-biggest-year-ever-for-l%C3%A9o-corporation/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 17:58:28 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/12/2023-the-biggest-year-ever-for-l%C3%A9o-corporation/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/12/2023-the-biggest-year-ever-for-l%C3%A9o-corporation/cover.png" alt="Featured image of post 2023 - The biggest year ever for Léo Corporation" />&lt;p>Last year, we concluded 2022 by telling you that 2023 was going to be super exciting - which is exactly what happened! This year has been a fantastic journey to be part of, and as the founder of the Léo Corporation, I can not express how I am grateful to you for this. I have personally never imagined that this project will come to this point, but here we are I guess. As the year ends, let&amp;rsquo;s take a look back at the major events and releases!&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="the-creation-of-the-peyronnet-group">The creation of the Peyronnet Group&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>In early 2023, Léo Corporation decided to create a specific branch for its developer-aimed products and libraies called Devyus. This subsidiary of Léo Corporation was intended to create and develop useful libraries for developers. Thanks to Devyus, our approach with LeoCorpLibrary evolved into PeyrSharp, and has also allowed a public release of our Synethia algorithm. But with the creation of Devyus, the internal organization of the Léo Corporation was becoming messy at a point where the following question arose: What is the goal of Léo Corporation? What do we create? The answer of this question could seem obvious at first - we create apps - but with Devyus, we were now also in charge of creating libraries for developers which are a different target from our apps&amp;rsquo;.
This is why the Peyronnet Group was created: To provide a clear separation and definition of which entity&amp;rsquo;s goal was; Devyus is making developer tools, while Léo Corporation is creating applications and experiences. (&lt;em>Fun fact&lt;/em>: Léo Corporation was supposed to be rebranded Léo&amp;rsquo;s Apps; however, the idea was abandoned for the simple reason that I thought the current name was already great)&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Since the creation of the Peyronnet Group, Léo Corporation has released many new products and applications, which proves that the change was also necessary to improve our productivity by removing some of the barriers that were previously in place. Let&amp;rsquo;s now take a look at these apps!&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="new-applications">New applications&lt;/h2>
&lt;h3 id="colorpicker-max">ColorPicker Max&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>In 2022, we released our most advanced app we ever made: InternetTest Pro. In 2023, we decided to do the same thing with ColorPicker by creating a powerful and advanced version of the app: ColorPicker Max. This version of ColorPicker is using the same UI as InternetTest Pro while bringing several tools for artists, designers, developers, and everyone who needs to manipulate colors. Today, ColorPicker Max is reliable tool and is one of our most popular app.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="daybar">DayBar&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>DayBar is a simple app released during the summer to help you keep track of your time by displaying in your taskbar the percentage of the day that has passed. You can quickly check at a glance if you are productive enough. Currently, the app doesn&amp;rsquo;t have a lot of features, but we already have plans for a v2 version that will come in 2024 hopefully.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="permatop">PermaTop&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>It is often frustrating when managing multiple windows and you wish that one of them could stay on top of another one, but you can&amp;rsquo;t. With PermaTop, you can quickly pin any window so it stays on top of all other opened windows, which allows you to maximize your productivity by dismissing the need to switch between two different windows. This simple app was also released on summer and has received some updates to allow you to completely manage your windows using the app. If we have new ideas on how to improve the app, we will definitely release new updates to it next year.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="gavilya-4">Gavilya 4&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>Gavilya 4 is not really a new application since it doesn&amp;rsquo;t bring major new features or design compared to the last one, but this fourth major version is in fact a complete rewrite of the app from the ground up. Gavilya was the first WPF C# application I&amp;rsquo;ve made and the code base was getting old and also horrible to maintain. With the rewrite, the app is much faster and consumes less resources, which will definitely improve your experience.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="web-experiences">Web experiences&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>As you may have noticed, we didn&amp;rsquo;t talk about Passliss and Qrix in the previous section - this is because they are a new type of apps for us: Web applications. For the first time, we decided to abandon a Windows-only app for a cross-platform web application.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="passliss">Passliss&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>Passliss is a simple password generator, but the following observation was made: If you want to generate a password, why install an app when alternatives already exist on the web? This is why we decided to stop the development of Passliss for Windows: To replace the app with a web app available on all devices. Despite some troubles while making the app, it is today very reliable and efficient, with new features and design. Passliss was one of our least popular app on GitHub - with the new strategy, it gained many stars, making it one of our most starred repo this year.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="qrix">Qrix&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>The same story also applies to Qrix (formerly known as Gerayis). We found absurd the need to install an app just to generate a QR Code, so we decided to create a web application that does the exact same thing the desktop version did, but better. We also brought a brand new design to make the app usable on any device.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="conclusion">Conclusion&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>To round things up, 2023 was unlike any other and one of our biggest year so far with so many new innovations and novelties. I would like to conclude this year by thanking everyone who starred and contributed to our Open-Sourced projects on GitHub; without you some of the greatest apps and features would not have been possible. 2024 will be a year where we will focus on improving our products and I hope it will be as exciting as this year!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Thank you for being onboard with us on this journey,&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Léo, Founder of Léo Corporation.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Introducing Gavilya 4</title><link>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/08/introducing-gavilya-4/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 14:19:15 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/08/introducing-gavilya-4/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/08/introducing-gavilya-4/cover.png" alt="Featured image of post Introducing Gavilya 4" />&lt;p>Greetings, gaming enthusiasts! We&amp;rsquo;re thrilled to unveil a monumental evolution in the world of game launchers - the much-awaited Gavilya 4. This latest version marks a significant turning point, as it arrives with a complete rewrite of the original codebase, bringing forth a host of enhancements that promise to redefine your gaming experience. Developed by Léo Corporation, Gavilya has always been dedicated to simplifying your gaming routine, and this new iteration takes that commitment to unprecedented heights.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="a-new-era-unfolds-from-the-ground-up">A New Era Unfolds: From the Ground Up&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/08/introducing-gavilya-4/1.png"
width="1185"
height="700"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/08/introducing-gavilya-4/1_hu9cece1284b34ee4c12f1d42a4a73813c_346720_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/08/introducing-gavilya-4/1_hu9cece1284b34ee4c12f1d42a4a73813c_346720_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="The new Game Details page"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="169"
data-flex-basis="406px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Gavilya 4 isn&amp;rsquo;t just an update; it&amp;rsquo;s a complete reimagining of the entire game launcher. Three years since the inception of the original Gavilya, we&amp;rsquo;ve embarked on an ambitious journey to create a platform that lays the groundwork for seamless future expansions. This rewrite is more than just lines of code; it&amp;rsquo;s a testament to our dedication to delivering an unparalleled gaming experience.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="speeding-into-the-future-performance-improvements">Speeding into the Future: Performance Improvements&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/08/introducing-gavilya-4/2.png"
width="1185"
height="700"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/08/introducing-gavilya-4/2_hu463ef275b433e592011c1d502c7891c7_195071_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/08/introducing-gavilya-4/2_hu463ef275b433e592011c1d502c7891c7_195071_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="The new Game Edition page"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="169"
data-flex-basis="406px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>One of the most exciting aspects of Gavilya 4 is the remarkable performance enhancement it brings to the table. With loading times now up to 5 times faster, you&amp;rsquo;ll spend less time waiting and more time playing. We&amp;rsquo;ve also worked tirelessly to optimize RAM usage, ensuring that your gaming experience is smoother and more responsive than ever before. Say goodbye to those frustrating moments when your system&amp;rsquo;s resources were stretched thin.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="elegance-in-simplicity-redefined-user-interface">Elegance in Simplicity: Redefined User Interface&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/08/introducing-gavilya-4/3.png"
width="1185"
height="700"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/08/introducing-gavilya-4/3_hu582937139ab88c993dd22fe93c72e98f_85076_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/08/introducing-gavilya-4/3_hu582937139ab88c993dd22fe93c72e98f_85076_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="The new simplified Profile page"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="169"
data-flex-basis="406px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Change is inevitable, but we&amp;rsquo;ve ensured that Gavilya 4&amp;rsquo;s UI maintains its core essence while embracing a sleeker and more intuitive design. While you may notice some subtle changes, the user-friendly approach that Gavilya is known for remains intact. We understand the importance of familiarity, and Gavilya 4 strikes the perfect balance between modernity and your well-loved gaming routine. We also took the opportunity of this major version to remove irrelevant features, such as the integrated notification center, the &amp;ldquo;Badges&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Favorites&amp;rdquo; section of the profile page.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="under-the-hood-codebase-refinement">Under the Hood: Codebase Refinement&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>One of the most profound advantages of this rewrite is the substantial improvement in the codebase&amp;rsquo;s maintainability. Our developers have meticulously crafted a foundation that&amp;rsquo;s not only robust but also more adaptable to future innovations. This means that as the gaming landscape evolves, Gavilya will be ready to accommodate new features and functionalities with unmatched efficiency.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="seamless-transition-upgrading-to-gavilya-4">Seamless Transition: Upgrading to Gavilya 4&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>For our dedicated Gavilya users, upgrading to version 4 is a breeze. While you&amp;rsquo;ll encounter some changes in the UI, the transition won&amp;rsquo;t disrupt your gaming routine. To make the shift, you&amp;rsquo;ll need to reimport your games using the migration installer that will open automatically upon starting the app. This process ensures that your game library remains intact and seamlessly accessible in the new version.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="a-future-full-of-promise">A Future Full of Promise&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>As we introduce Gavilya 4, we&amp;rsquo;re not just unveiling a game launcher; we&amp;rsquo;re presenting a commitment to innovation, performance, and your unparalleled gaming experience. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a casual gamer or a dedicated enthusiast, Gavilya 4 is poised to revolutionize the way you interact with your gaming library.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Join us as we step into this exciting new era of gaming convenience and sophistication. &lt;a class="link" href="https://tinyurl.com/DownloadGavilya" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Download Gavilya 4&lt;/a> today and rediscover your games like never before. Your journey into the future of gaming starts now!&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="website">Website&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;a class="link" href="https://gavilya.leocorporation.dev" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Click here&lt;/a> to go to the official website of Gavilya.
&lt;a class="link" href="https://tinyurl.com/DownloadGavilya" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Click here&lt;/a> to download Gavilya.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>How we use social media to connect with you</title><link>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/07/how-we-use-social-media-to-connect-with-you/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 13:18:35 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/07/how-we-use-social-media-to-connect-with-you/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/07/how-we-use-social-media-to-connect-with-you/cover.png" alt="Featured image of post How we use social media to connect with you" />&lt;h2 id="how-we-use-social-media-to-connect-with-you">How we use social media to connect with you&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Léo Corporation is a company that creates and maintains applications for Windows and the web. We are passionate about creating experiences that will make you more productive. We have a portfolio of apps that range from password generators to game launchers, from color pickers to database managers, and more. You can find all our projects on our website: &lt;a class="link" href="https://leocorporation.dev" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>https://leocorporation.dev&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>But we are not only about creating apps. We are also about connecting with you, our users, and sharing our vision, updates, tips and tricks, and more. That&amp;rsquo;s why we are present on various social media platforms, where we showcase our apps and engage with our community. Here are some of the ways we use social media to communicate with you:&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="tiktok">TikTok&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>TikTok is a popular platform for short-form videos, where users can express their creativity, humor, talent, and more. We use TikTok to create short tutorials and videos about our apps, showing how they work, what features they have, and how they can help you in your daily tasks. For example, you can watch a video on how to use Passliss, a web app that allows you to generate secure passwords and test the strength of existing ones. Or you can watch a video on how to use InternetTest, a modern connection utility for Windows that can locate IP addresses, send ping requests, recover your WiFi passwords, and more. You can follow us on TikTok here: &lt;a class="link" href="https://www.tiktok.com/@leocorporation_/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>https://www.tiktok.com/@leocorporation_/&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="x-twitter">X (Twitter)&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>Twitter or X is a platform for sharing short messages, news, opinions, and more. We use Twitter to post updates about our apps, such as new releases, bug fixes, feature requests, and more. You can also interact with us on Twitter by asking questions, giving feedback, or just saying hi. We are always happy to hear from you and respond to your queries. You can follow us on Twitter here: &lt;a class="link" href="https://twitter.com/LeoCorpNews" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>https://twitter.com/LeoCorpNews&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="instagram-and-facebook">Instagram and Facebook&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>Instagram and Facebook are platforms for sharing photos, videos, stories, and more. We use Instagram and Facebook to post updates about our apps as well, but also to share behind-the-scenes glimpses of our development process, team members, events, and more. You can also see some of the screenshots and previews of the apps that we are working on or improving. You can follow us on Instagram here: &lt;a class="link" href="https://www.instagram.com/leocorporation_/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>https://www.instagram.com/leocorporation_/&lt;/a> and on Facebook here: &lt;a class="link" href="https://www.facebook.com/LeoCorporationSoftwares" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>https://www.facebook.com/LeoCorporationSoftwares&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="conclusion">Conclusion&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>As you can see, we are very active on social media and love to connect with you. If you are interested in our apps or want to learn more about them, you can follow us on any of these platforms or visit our website. You can also check out our GitHub page where we host our source code and documentation: &lt;a class="link" href="https://github.com/Leo-Corporation" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>https://github.com/Leo-Corporation&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We hope the content we create will please you!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Introducing PermaTop – Your Ultimate Windows Utility for Keeping Windows in Focus</title><link>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/07/introducing-permatop-your-ultimate-windows-utility-for-keeping-windows-in-focus/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 11:47:47 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/07/introducing-permatop-your-ultimate-windows-utility-for-keeping-windows-in-focus/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/07/introducing-permatop-your-ultimate-windows-utility-for-keeping-windows-in-focus/cover.png" alt="Featured image of post Introducing PermaTop – Your Ultimate Windows Utility for Keeping Windows in Focus" />&lt;h2 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Are you tired of constantly switching between windows and losing focus on your essential tasks? Look no further! We are thrilled to introduce PermaTop, the ultimate Windows utility designed to enhance your productivity by keeping windows always on top of each other.
In our fast-paced digital world, multitasking is the norm. But with so many open windows, it&amp;rsquo;s easy to lose focus and become overwhelmed. PermaTop is here to change that. This powerful tool allows you to pin any window, ensuring it stays on top of all others. No more burying important information beneath a pile of applications – keep your essential tools and resources visible and accessible at all times!&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="features">Features&lt;/h2>
&lt;h3 id="pin-windows">Pin Windows&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/07/introducing-permatop-your-ultimate-windows-utility-for-keeping-windows-in-focus/1.png"
width="800"
height="450"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/07/introducing-permatop-your-ultimate-windows-utility-for-keeping-windows-in-focus/1_hu89e23e4a05cec04948150d9b2471b4b6_98337_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/07/introducing-permatop-your-ultimate-windows-utility-for-keeping-windows-in-focus/1_hu89e23e4a05cec04948150d9b2471b4b6_98337_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="The Pin windows feature"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="177"
data-flex-basis="426px"
>
PermaTop empowers you with the ability to pin any window, be it an application, document, or browser, to ensure it remains in the foreground at all times. No more juggling between windows or losing track of critical information!&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="favorites-for-instant-pinning">Favorites for Instant Pinning&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/07/introducing-permatop-your-ultimate-windows-utility-for-keeping-windows-in-focus/2.png"
width="800"
height="450"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/07/introducing-permatop-your-ultimate-windows-utility-for-keeping-windows-in-focus/2_hu7d12b8302f65dd8419790dfef1f0ee1c_105495_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/07/introducing-permatop-your-ultimate-windows-utility-for-keeping-windows-in-focus/2_hu7d12b8302f65dd8419790dfef1f0ee1c_105495_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="The favorite feature"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="177"
data-flex-basis="426px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Say goodbye to repetitive pinning tasks! PermaTop allows you to mark your favorite windows, which will be automatically pinned each time you launch the app. With just one click, your essential tools and resources are instantly at your disposal.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="customization-at-your-fingertips">Customization at Your Fingertips&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/07/introducing-permatop-your-ultimate-windows-utility-for-keeping-windows-in-focus/3.png"
width="800"
height="450"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/07/introducing-permatop-your-ultimate-windows-utility-for-keeping-windows-in-focus/3_hu2370e4eb471fc3fb23deaea6203cd8f8_105725_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/07/introducing-permatop-your-ultimate-windows-utility-for-keeping-windows-in-focus/3_hu2370e4eb471fc3fb23deaea6203cd8f8_105725_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="The Settings page of PermaTop"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="177"
data-flex-basis="426px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>PermaTop goes beyond a one-size-fits-all approach. It offers a plethora of customization options, allowing you to tailor the utility to suit your specific workflow and preferences. From pinning behavior to visual styles, PermaTop adapts to you.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="seamless-user-experience">Seamless User Experience&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/07/introducing-permatop-your-ultimate-windows-utility-for-keeping-windows-in-focus/4.png"
width="800"
height="450"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/07/introducing-permatop-your-ultimate-windows-utility-for-keeping-windows-in-focus/4_hucd305ee1a88a5bcfd8530be91556181e_185508_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/07/introducing-permatop-your-ultimate-windows-utility-for-keeping-windows-in-focus/4_hucd305ee1a88a5bcfd8530be91556181e_185508_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="The Pin windows feature of PermaTop in dark mode"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="177"
data-flex-basis="426px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Using PermaTop is as simple as it gets. Upon launching the application, a list of opened windows is displayed, enabling you to effortlessly pin any window with a single click. No complex setup or learning curve, just pure productivity at your fingertips.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="boost-productivity-streamline-workflows">Boost Productivity, Streamline Workflows&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>With PermaTop in your arsenal, you can wave goodbye to the frustration of window management. Stay focused, switch between tasks seamlessly, and elevate your productivity to new heights.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="try-permatop-today">Try PermaTop Today&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Ready to take control of your Windows experience? &lt;a class="link" href="https://tinyurl.com/PermaTop" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Download PermaTop&lt;/a> now and unlock a world of productivity possibilities. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a multitasking enthusiast, a professional handling multiple projects, or someone who values efficiency, PermaTop is your ticket to an optimized workflow.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Don&amp;rsquo;t let windows obscure your path to success. Embrace PermaTop and witness the transformation in your productivity today!&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="video">Video&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Learn more about PermaTop and see it in action in this video!&lt;/p>
&lt;center>
&lt;iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/zTJTOfc0KI4" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen>&lt;/iframe>
&lt;/center></description></item><item><title>Introducing Qrix – A powerful Bar Code and QR Code generator</title><link>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/07/introducing-qrix-a-powerful-bar-code-and-qr-code-generator/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 13:39:42 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/07/introducing-qrix-a-powerful-bar-code-and-qr-code-generator/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/07/introducing-qrix-a-powerful-bar-code-and-qr-code-generator/cover.png" alt="Featured image of post Introducing Qrix – A powerful Bar Code and QR Code generator" />&lt;h2 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Welcome to Qrix, the web app that lets you create and customize bar codes and QR codes with ease. Qrix is designed to be simple, fast, and user-friendly. You can generate codes in various formats, such as Code128, Code11, UPC-A, ISBN, and more. You can also adjust the foreground and background colors of your codes and save or copy them for later use. Qrix supports light and dark themes and is available in English and French.
In this blog post, we will introduce you to some of the features of Qrix and show you how to use it. Whether you need to create codes for personal or professional purposes, Qrix can help you do it in a few clicks.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="features">Features&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>With its array of powerful features, Qrix is set to become your go-to tool for all your code generation needs.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="diverse-code-types">Diverse Code Types&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>Qrix offers an extensive range of bar code types to cater to your specific requirements. Whether you need a Code128, Code11, UPC-A, ISBN, or any other bar code format, Qrix has you covered. By supporting various code types, Qrix ensures that you can generate the right code for your products, documents, or any other data.
Currently these types are available:&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Code128&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Code11&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Code39&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Code49&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Code93&lt;/li>
&lt;li>EAN-13&lt;/li>
&lt;li>EAN-2&lt;/li>
&lt;li>EAN-5&lt;/li>
&lt;li>EAN-8&lt;/li>
&lt;li>UPC-A&lt;/li>
&lt;li>MSI&lt;/li>
&lt;li>ISBN&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="customization-options">Customization Options&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/07/introducing-qrix-a-powerful-bar-code-and-qr-code-generator/1.jpeg"
width="2428"
height="1222"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/07/introducing-qrix-a-powerful-bar-code-and-qr-code-generator/1_hu24cad951a2da604de168417ef2f6dcd4_78938_480x0_resize_q75_box.jpeg 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/07/introducing-qrix-a-powerful-bar-code-and-qr-code-generator/1_hu24cad951a2da604de168417ef2f6dcd4_78938_1024x0_resize_q75_box.jpeg 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="The QR Code generator feature with custom colors selected."
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="198"
data-flex-basis="476px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Personalization is key when it comes to branding and visual appeal. Qrix acknowledges this and offers a wide range of customization options for your codes. You can easily adjust the foreground and background colors to match your brand&amp;rsquo;s identity or aesthetic preferences. Qrix also provides a real-time preview, allowing you to fine-tune the appearance of your codes before saving or copying them.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="saving-and-copying-codes">Saving and Copying Codes&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/07/introducing-qrix-a-powerful-bar-code-and-qr-code-generator/2.jpeg"
width="2428"
height="1222"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/07/introducing-qrix-a-powerful-bar-code-and-qr-code-generator/2_huf5e5f4f96347fafbb35161b8c1ba27d8_83945_480x0_resize_q75_box.jpeg 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/07/introducing-qrix-a-powerful-bar-code-and-qr-code-generator/2_huf5e5f4f96347fafbb35161b8c1ba27d8_83945_1024x0_resize_q75_box.jpeg 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="The Bar Code generator page."
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="198"
data-flex-basis="476px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Qrix provides flexible options for saving and sharing your generated codes. You can conveniently save your codes as PNG/JPG/BMP files, ensuring compatibility across various platforms and applications. Additionally, with a simple click, you can copy the codes directly to your clipboard, enabling swift integration into documents, presentations, or websites.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="history-feature">History Feature&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/07/introducing-qrix-a-powerful-bar-code-and-qr-code-generator/3.jpeg"
width="2428"
height="1222"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/07/introducing-qrix-a-powerful-bar-code-and-qr-code-generator/3_hu1fd2d62f6dc9d249558630017fbfe915_98122_480x0_resize_q75_box.jpeg 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/07/introducing-qrix-a-powerful-bar-code-and-qr-code-generator/3_hu1fd2d62f6dc9d249558630017fbfe915_98122_1024x0_resize_q75_box.jpeg 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="The History page showing the recently generated Bar Codes."
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="198"
data-flex-basis="476px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Keeping track of your generated codes is made effortless with Qrix&amp;rsquo;s history feature. Every code you generate is automatically saved within the app, ensuring easy access and retrieval whenever you need it. This feature eliminates the hassle of manually managing files or searching for previously created codes, allowing you to focus on your tasks without interruption.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="theme-and-language-customization">Theme and Language Customization&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/07/introducing-qrix-a-powerful-bar-code-and-qr-code-generator/4.jpeg"
width="2428"
height="1222"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/07/introducing-qrix-a-powerful-bar-code-and-qr-code-generator/4_hu545bbed2659d36c9a3b0b51e2e655f2d_97517_480x0_resize_q75_box.jpeg 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/07/introducing-qrix-a-powerful-bar-code-and-qr-code-generator/4_hu545bbed2659d36c9a3b0b51e2e655f2d_97517_1024x0_resize_q75_box.jpeg 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="Qrix when dark mode is enabled."
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="198"
data-flex-basis="476px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Qrix understands the importance of user preferences. It offers a choice between light and dark themes, allowing you to create a visually comfortable environment that suits your needs. Moreover, Qrix supports multiple languages, including English and French, ensuring a seamless experience for users from different linguistic backgrounds.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="cross-device-compatibility">Cross-Device Compatibility&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>Qrix is designed to be highly accessible, enabling you to generate codes from any device with a web browser. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re using a desktop computer, laptop, tablet, or smartphone, Qrix adapts responsively to different screen sizes and orientations. This versatility allows you to use Qrix wherever and whenever you need it, whether you&amp;rsquo;re at your desk or on the go.
Qrix revolutionizes the way you generate bar codes and QR codes. With its diverse code types, customization options, history feature, and cross-device compatibility, Qrix empowers you to create codes quickly, efficiently, and with unmatched convenience.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="how-to-use-qrix">How to use Qrix&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Using Qrix is very easy. Here are the steps to follow:&lt;/p>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>Go to &lt;a class="link" href="https://qrix.leocorporation.dev" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>https://qrix.leocorporation.dev&lt;/a> and click on the &amp;ldquo;Bar Code&amp;rdquo; or “QR Code” option.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Select the type of code you want to generate from the dropdown menu.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Enter the data for your code in the input field. For example, if you want to generate a QR code for a website, enter the URL of the website.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Choose the foreground and background colors for your code from the color picker. You can also use the default colors if you prefer.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Click on the &amp;ldquo;Generate&amp;rdquo; button and see your code appear on the screen.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>If you are satisfied with your code, you can save it as a PNG file by clicking on the &amp;ldquo;Save&amp;rdquo; button or copy it to your clipboard by clicking on the &amp;ldquo;Copy&amp;rdquo; button.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;h2 id="conclusion">Conclusion&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Qrix is a web app that lets you create and customize bar codes and QR codes with ease. It is simple, fast, and user-friendly. It has many features that make it a great app for generating codes for personal or professional purposes. You can access it from any device that has a web browser.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>If you want to try Qrix for yourself, go to &lt;a class="link" href="https://qrix.leocorporation.dev" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>https://qrix.leocorporation.dev&lt;/a> and start creating your own codes today. You will be amazed by how easy and fun it is to use Qrix.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Thank you for reading this blog post. I hope you found it informative and helpful. If you have any questions or feedback about Qrix, feel free to leave a comment below or &lt;a class="link" href="https://leocorporation.dev/contact" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>contact us&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="whats-next-for-gerayis">What’s next for Gerayis?&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>After careful consideration and in line with our commitment to providing the best user experience possible, we have made the decision to discontinue support for Gerayis for Windows. Gerayis will still work but we won’t bring any new updates to it. For new features, users can migrate to Qrix. To get started with it, simply access it through your preferred web browser. The best part is that Qrix can also be installed as a Progressive Web App (PWA) on your Windows device. This means you can have the convenience of a dedicated app-like experience while still benefiting from the versatility of a web-based solution.
By transitioning to Qrix, you will gain access to all the features and functionality you enjoyed with Gerayis, and more.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We understand that change can sometimes be challenging, but we are confident that Qrix will exceed your expectations and become your go-to solution for code generation. Our team is dedicated to providing continuous support and updates for Qrix, ensuring that you have the best possible experience while using our app.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>As we move forward, we encourage all Windows users to transition from Gerayis to Qrix. We appreciate your understanding and are excited to embark on this new chapter with you. Should you have any questions or need assistance during the transition, our support team is available to help.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="video">Video&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Watch the official trailer for Qrix on our YouTube channel&lt;/p>
&lt;center>
&lt;iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/JYvrxzkLnS4" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen>&lt;/iframe>
&lt;/center></description></item><item><title>Introducing DayBar: Revolutionizing Time Management with a Passion for Productivity</title><link>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/07/introducing-daybar-revolutionizing-time-management-with-a-passion-for-productivity/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 11:03:40 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/07/introducing-daybar-revolutionizing-time-management-with-a-passion-for-productivity/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/07/introducing-daybar-revolutionizing-time-management-with-a-passion-for-productivity/cover.png" alt="Featured image of post Introducing DayBar: Revolutionizing Time Management with a Passion for Productivity" />&lt;h2 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>In a world filled with constant distractions and endless to-do lists, effective time management has become more crucial than ever. Introducing DayBar, a remarkable time tracking tool that was born out of a deep-rooted desire to help individuals optimize their time, increase productivity, and achieve their goals. In this blog post, we will not only explore the exceptional features of DayBar but also delve into the inspiring backstory that led to its creation.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="the-inspiration">The Inspiration&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>At the heart of DayBar lies the vision of Léo Corporation, a software development company committed to creating innovative and user-friendly applications. Driven by a passion for productivity and time management, the team at Léo Corporation observed the challenges individuals faced in keeping track of their progress throughout the day. They recognized the need for a simple yet powerful tool that could provide a tangible representation of time, foster time awareness, and enable users to make informed decisions about their daily activities.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="the-journey-of-creation">The Journey of Creation&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>With this mission in mind, the dedicated team at Léo Corporation embarked on a journey to bring DayBar to life. Countless hours of brainstorming, designing, and coding were invested in crafting an intuitive and versatile time tracking solution. The team tirelessly researched and tested various features, ensuring that DayBar would cater to a wide range of user needs and preferences.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="empowering-time-management">Empowering Time Management&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>DayBar was meticulously developed to empower users to take control of their time. The team understood that effective time management is essential for personal and professional success. By visualizing the passing of time and providing a clear representation of progress, DayBar aims to foster greater awareness and enable users to make conscious decisions about how they allocate their time.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="features">Features&lt;/h2>
&lt;h3 id="time-visualization">Time Visualization&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/07/introducing-daybar-revolutionizing-time-management-with-a-passion-for-productivity/1.png"
width="800"
height="450"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/07/introducing-daybar-revolutionizing-time-management-with-a-passion-for-productivity/1_hu9e03a74a8140347b4c4865132f9cbe4f_33235_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/07/introducing-daybar-revolutionizing-time-management-with-a-passion-for-productivity/1_hu9e03a74a8140347b4c4865132f9cbe4f_33235_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="The home page of DayBar"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="177"
data-flex-basis="426px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>DayBar provides a visual representation of your progress throughout the day or work hours. Placed conveniently in the system tray, it offers a quick and intuitive glance at the percentage of time that has elapsed. This visual feedback empowers you to stay aware of your productivity and make real-time adjustments to your workflow, ultimately leading to more focused and effective time management.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="customizable-work-hours">Customizable Work Hours&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>DayBar recognizes that everyone&amp;rsquo;s schedule is unique. With its customizable work hours feature, you can define your preferred time blocks for focused work. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re an early riser, a night owl, or need specific periods for different activities, DayBar allows you to tailor your time tracking to align with your individual workflow and maximize your productivity during your most productive hours.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="personalized-themes">Personalized Themes&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/07/introducing-daybar-revolutionizing-time-management-with-a-passion-for-productivity/3.png"
width="800"
height="450"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/07/introducing-daybar-revolutionizing-time-management-with-a-passion-for-productivity/3_hu8a7c4b822790238e76789076ab5aa168_35883_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/07/introducing-daybar-revolutionizing-time-management-with-a-passion-for-productivity/3_hu8a7c4b822790238e76789076ab5aa168_35883_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="The home page of DayBar with dark theme enabled"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="177"
data-flex-basis="426px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>DayBar understands the importance of a visually pleasing and personalized experience. Choose from a variety of themes to customize the appearance of the application. Whether you prefer a light and minimalistic interface for a clean look or a dark theme to reduce eye strain during late-night work sessions, DayBar lets you create an environment that suits your style and enhances your overall user experience.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="intelligent-notifications">Intelligent Notifications&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/07/introducing-daybar-revolutionizing-time-management-with-a-passion-for-productivity/2.png"
width="800"
height="450"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/07/introducing-daybar-revolutionizing-time-management-with-a-passion-for-productivity/2_hu031b11eeb88522f427cc03315f8dbe30_23091_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/07/introducing-daybar-revolutionizing-time-management-with-a-passion-for-productivity/2_hu031b11eeb88522f427cc03315f8dbe30_23091_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="The &amp;ldquo;Notifications&amp;rdquo; page of DayBar"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="177"
data-flex-basis="426px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>To help you stay on track and make the most of your time, DayBar offers customizable notifications. Set intervals that align with your workflow, and receive gentle reminders to assess your progress and evaluate your task management. These notifications serve as valuable nudges, keeping you motivated, focused, and accountable to your goals throughout the day.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="multilingual-support">Multilingual Support&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/07/introducing-daybar-revolutionizing-time-management-with-a-passion-for-productivity/4.png"
width="800"
height="450"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/07/introducing-daybar-revolutionizing-time-management-with-a-passion-for-productivity/4_huaa6d3a152d2d64f71788da6de9104131_24860_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/07/introducing-daybar-revolutionizing-time-management-with-a-passion-for-productivity/4_huaa6d3a152d2d64f71788da6de9104131_24860_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="The about page of DayBar"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="177"
data-flex-basis="426px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In a globalized world, language should never be a barrier to productivity. DayBar ensures inclusivity and accessibility by providing support for multiple languages. Choose between English and French to seamlessly navigate and utilize the application in your preferred language, enhancing your overall user experience and ensuring a smooth interaction with DayBar&amp;rsquo;s features.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="conclusion">Conclusion&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Time management is a fundamental skill for success and personal well-being. DayBar revolutionizes the way we track and optimize our time, providing a comprehensive set of features that empower individuals to make the most of every moment. From visualizing your progress to customizing work hours, personalizing themes, receiving intelligent notifications, and supporting multiple languages, DayBar is a game-changer in the realm of time tracking tools. Embrace DayBar as your ultimate time management companion and unlock your potential for enhanced productivity, improved work-life balance, and greater overall satisfaction. Embrace the power of DayBar and embark on a journey towards mastering your time and achieving your goals.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="download-today">Download today!&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;a class="link" href="https://tinyurl.com/DayBar" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Click here&lt;/a> to download DayBar for Windows.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="trailer">Trailer&lt;/h2>
&lt;center>
&lt;iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/QO01T_Fb9RM" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen>&lt;/iframe>
&lt;/center></description></item><item><title>Xalyus Store is shutting down</title><link>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/06/xalyus-store-is-shutting-down/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 13:21:42 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/06/xalyus-store-is-shutting-down/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/06/xalyus-store-is-shutting-down/cover.png" alt="Featured image of post Xalyus Store is shutting down" />&lt;h2 id="xalyus-store-is-shutting-down">Xalyus Store is shutting down&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Hello everyone,&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We have some important news to share with you today. After more than two years of providing you with a variety of software products, we have decided to &lt;strong>shut down Xalyus Store&lt;/strong>.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>This was not an easy decision to make, but we believe it is the best one for our company and our users. We want to &lt;strong>unify the methods to get our apps&lt;/strong> and make them more accessible and convenient for you.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>From now on, you can still download safely all of our apps on our &lt;a class="link" href="https://leocorporation.dev/store" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>&lt;strong>official store website&lt;/strong>&lt;/a>. There, you will find the latest versions of our products.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We want to thank you for your support and loyalty over the years. You have been an amazing community and we are grateful for your feedback and suggestions. We hope you will continue to enjoy our apps and follow us on our social media channels.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>If you have any questions or concerns, please feel free to &lt;a class="link" href="https://leocorporation.dev/contact" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>contact us&lt;/a>. We will be happy to assist you.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Thank you for choosing Léo Corporation!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;em>- The Léo Corporation Team&lt;/em>&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Introducing Passliss for the Web – The Ultimate Password Generator</title><link>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/03/introducing-passliss-for-the-web-the-ultimate-password-generator/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 13:07:30 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/03/introducing-passliss-for-the-web-the-ultimate-password-generator/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/03/introducing-passliss-for-the-web-the-ultimate-password-generator/cover.png" alt="Featured image of post Introducing Passliss for the Web – The Ultimate Password Generator" />&lt;h2 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Are you tired of struggling to come up with strong and unique passwords for all of your accounts? Look no further than Passliss for the Web, the latest and greatest iteration of Léo Corporation&amp;rsquo;s simple yet powerful password generator.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="new-features">New features&lt;/h2>
&lt;h3 id="the-new-home-page">The new Home page&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/03/introducing-passliss-for-the-web-the-ultimate-password-generator/1.jpeg"
width="1788"
height="865"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/03/introducing-passliss-for-the-web-the-ultimate-password-generator/1_hu3f93ebbcd400ebec1e0c6a5c8406f433_64655_480x0_resize_q75_box.jpeg 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/03/introducing-passliss-for-the-web-the-ultimate-password-generator/1_hu3f93ebbcd400ebec1e0c6a5c8406f433_64655_1024x0_resize_q75_box.jpeg 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="The new Home dashboard"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="206"
data-flex-basis="496px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>With Passliss for the Web, you can generate a strong password with just a click of a button. The home dashboard allows for quick generation, giving you the option to generate a password as soon as you load the page or by clicking a button. Plus, with the recommended features displayed as cards, you can easily explore and customize your password to fit your needs.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="introducing-activities">Introducing Activities&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/03/introducing-passliss-for-the-web-the-ultimate-password-generator/2.jpeg"
width="1788"
height="865"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/03/introducing-passliss-for-the-web-the-ultimate-password-generator/2_hufb664a14f03bfa947ed6f6be6e018650_114503_480x0_resize_q75_box.jpeg 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/03/introducing-passliss-for-the-web-the-ultimate-password-generator/2_hufb664a14f03bfa947ed6f6be6e018650_114503_1024x0_resize_q75_box.jpeg 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="The new Activity page"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="206"
data-flex-basis="496px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The Activity page in Passliss for the Web allows you to keep track of all the passwords you&amp;rsquo;ve generated so far. This feature provides you with a list of your recently generated passwords along with their strength ratings. With this information at your fingertips, you can quickly identify which passwords are weak and need to be updated.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="generate-passwords-easily">Generate passwords easily&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/03/introducing-passliss-for-the-web-the-ultimate-password-generator/3-1.jpeg"
width="1788"
height="865"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/03/introducing-passliss-for-the-web-the-ultimate-password-generator/3-1_hu73a1c59f7c341ddc1524d99d15ac0549_51203_480x0_resize_q75_box.jpeg 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/03/introducing-passliss-for-the-web-the-ultimate-password-generator/3-1_hu73a1c59f7c341ddc1524d99d15ac0549_51203_1024x0_resize_q75_box.jpeg 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="The Simple section of Generate page"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="206"
data-flex-basis="496px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The Generate page in Passliss for the Web is designed to make password generation easy and customizable. The basic view allows you to generate a password by strength, where you can select the desired strength with a slider and generate and copy buttons. The password strength rating is displayed in real-time, allowing you to adjust the strength slider to your desired level.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/03/introducing-passliss-for-the-web-the-ultimate-password-generator/3-2.jpeg"
width="1788"
height="865"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/03/introducing-passliss-for-the-web-the-ultimate-password-generator/3-2_hufbc807ecc39d1351bd4360a314c6d3cf_51893_480x0_resize_q75_box.jpeg 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/03/introducing-passliss-for-the-web-the-ultimate-password-generator/3-2_hufbc807ecc39d1351bd4360a314c6d3cf_51893_1024x0_resize_q75_box.jpeg 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="The Advanced section of Generate page"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="206"
data-flex-basis="496px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>However, if you want more control over your passwords, the advanced view is where you should be. Here, you can customize the password characters to your liking, including uppercases, lowercases, numbers, and special characters. You can even input custom characters to create unique passwords. Additionally, you can choose the length of the password and generate multiple passwords at once. Whether you want a quick and easy password or a fully customized one, Passliss for the Web has you covered.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="ensure-your-safety">Ensure your safety&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/03/introducing-passliss-for-the-web-the-ultimate-password-generator/4.jpeg"
width="1788"
height="865"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/03/introducing-passliss-for-the-web-the-ultimate-password-generator/4_hub479d3db51f55e1a5be65d55a32a64cd_58551_480x0_resize_q75_box.jpeg 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/03/introducing-passliss-for-the-web-the-ultimate-password-generator/4_hub479d3db51f55e1a5be65d55a32a64cd_58551_1024x0_resize_q75_box.jpeg 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="The Strength page"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="206"
data-flex-basis="496px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>But Passliss for the Web doesn&amp;rsquo;t just stop at password generation. The strength page allows you to estimate the strength of your current passwords and provides you with a detailed view of their strength with different colors. With this feature, you can identify weak passwords and take action to make them stronger. Passliss for the Web reminds you that the strength estimation is just an estimate, so you should always use your best judgment when creating and using passwords.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="encrypt-your-secrets">Encrypt your secrets&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/03/introducing-passliss-for-the-web-the-ultimate-password-generator/5.jpeg"
width="1788"
height="865"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/03/introducing-passliss-for-the-web-the-ultimate-password-generator/5_huef9dcdd5bf6f0c2e431667560bd62158_64094_480x0_resize_q75_box.jpeg 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/03/introducing-passliss-for-the-web-the-ultimate-password-generator/5_huef9dcdd5bf6f0c2e431667560bd62158_64094_1024x0_resize_q75_box.jpeg 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="The Encrypt page"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="206"
data-flex-basis="496px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Passliss also has another great feature: The encryption page. It allows you to encrypt and decrypt strings using different encryption algorithms, including AES and Triple-DES. These are widely recognized as some of the most secure and reliable encryption algorithms available today.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>AES, or Advanced Encryption Standard, is a symmetric-key encryption algorithm that is used to protect sensitive data. It is widely considered to be one of the most secure encryption algorithms available, and is used by governments, financial institutions, and other organizations to secure their data.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Triple-DES, or Triple Data Encryption Standard, is another symmetric-key encryption algorithm that uses three individual keys for increased security. While it is not as widely used as AES, it is still a reliable encryption algorithm that provides strong protection for your data.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="customize-your-experience">Customize your experience&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/03/introducing-passliss-for-the-web-the-ultimate-password-generator/6.jpeg"
width="1788"
height="865"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/03/introducing-passliss-for-the-web-the-ultimate-password-generator/6_hu0e407c0baf7ad9f1dc2ffd2deb849c62_78304_480x0_resize_q75_box.jpeg 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/03/introducing-passliss-for-the-web-the-ultimate-password-generator/6_hu0e407c0baf7ad9f1dc2ffd2deb849c62_78304_1024x0_resize_q75_box.jpeg 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="The new Settings page"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="206"
data-flex-basis="496px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Passliss for the Web also comes with a settings page, allowing you to set your preferred theme, language, default random length, list of characters, and even your default encryption algorithm. And with the ability to export and import settings, you can easily transfer your preferences to other devices.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="built-using-innovative-technologies">Built using innovative technologies&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>Built using NextJS, TypeScript, and Shadcn/ui with TailwindCSS and RadixUI, Passliss for the Web is also a progressive web application available for both desktop and mobile devices. Plus, the responsive UI ensures a seamless experience across all devices.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="launch-now">Launch now!&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Don&amp;rsquo;t settle for weak and easily hackable passwords. Upgrade to Passliss for the Web and secure your online presence today!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a class="link" href="https://passliss.leocorporation.dev" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Click here&lt;/a> to launch Passliss in your browser.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="trailer">Trailer&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Watch the trailer!&lt;/p>
&lt;center>
&lt;iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/ac-83iKkJlU" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen>&lt;/iframe>
&lt;/center>
&lt;h2 id="qna">QnA&lt;/h2>
&lt;h3 id="whats-the-future-of-passliss-desktop">What’s the future of Passliss Desktop?&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>Passliss Desktop is going to be discontinued in favor of Passliss for the Web. This means that users will need to use the new web experience to generate and manage their passwords. Passliss for the Web offers more features, more security, and more convenience than Passliss Desktop.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>However, users can still enjoy a desktop-like experience by installing Passliss for the Web as a progressive web application (PWA). This will allow them to access Passliss for the Web from their desktop or mobile device without opening a browser. To install Passliss for the Web as a PWA, users simply need to &lt;a class="link" href="https://passliss.leocorporation.dev/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>visit the website&lt;/a> and follow the instructions on their device.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We hope that users will enjoy using Passliss for the Web and appreciate its benefits over Passliss Desktop. We thank them for their support and feedback over the years and look forward to providing them with the best password generator possible.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="can-i-upgrade-directly-from-passliss-desktop-to-passliss-for-the-web">Can I upgrade directly from Passliss Desktop to Passliss for the Web?&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>No, you cannot upgrade from Passliss Desktop to Passliss Web because they are two different products. Passliss Desktop is a standalone application that runs on Windows and generates passwords locally. Passliss Web is a web-based application that runs on any device with a browser and generates passwords online. They have different features, settings, and interfaces.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>However, you can still use both products if you wish. You can keep using Passliss Desktop until it is discontinued and then switch to Passliss Web. Or you can start using Passliss Web right away and enjoy its benefits over Passliss Desktop. The choice is yours.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="is-passliss-for-the-web-free">Is Passliss for the Web free?&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>Yes, Passliss for the Web is free and open source. You can use it without paying anything or registering anything. You can also access the source code and contribute to the development of Passliss for the Web on &lt;a class="link" href="https://github.com/Leo-Corporation/Passliss" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>GitHub&lt;/a>. We believe in making password security accessible and transparent for everyone.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Introducing ColorPicker Max</title><link>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/02/introducing-colorpicker-max/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 12:57:52 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/02/introducing-colorpicker-max/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/02/introducing-colorpicker-max/cover.png" alt="Featured image of post Introducing ColorPicker Max" />&lt;h2 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>ColorPicker Max is the latest version of the popular color picker tool that has been trusted by designers, artists, and developers around the world. As the next major evolution of this application, ColorPicker Max introduces a host of new features and improvements that make it more powerful, flexible, and user-friendly than ever before. In this article, we will take a closer look at the newest features and enhancements that make ColorPicker Max the ultimate choice for anyone who needs to work with color on a daily basis. From the powerful Converter tool to the versatile Gradient generator, we will explore all the ways in which ColorPicker Max can help you work more efficiently and effectively with color. So let&amp;rsquo;s dive in and discover what this amazing tool has to offer!&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="selector">Selector&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/02/introducing-colorpicker-max/1.png"
width="950"
height="600"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/02/introducing-colorpicker-max/1_hu40ce090efda3d0bc547047c669ce9e1e_201869_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/02/introducing-colorpicker-max/1_hu40ce090efda3d0bc547047c669ce9e1e_201869_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="The selector page of ColorPicker Max"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="158"
data-flex-basis="380px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>One of the most exciting features of ColorPicker Max is its ability to select a specific color using different sliders or from a pixel on the screen. This allows users to easily and accurately pick any color they need for their projects. Additionally, the color detail panel shows all the details of the color, including RGB values, HEX, HSL, HSV, CMYK, XYZ, YIQ, and YUV. Users can also copy any of these values to the clipboard by simply clicking on them.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="chromatic-wheel">Chromatic wheel&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/02/introducing-colorpicker-max/2.png"
width="950"
height="600"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/02/introducing-colorpicker-max/2_hu927032dbb0fc7cdcb3c0a114f5184951_231174_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/02/introducing-colorpicker-max/2_hu927032dbb0fc7cdcb3c0a114f5184951_231174_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="The Chromatic wheel page of ColorPicker Max"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="158"
data-flex-basis="380px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Another great feature of ColorPicker Max is its Chromatic Wheel, which allows users to select a color from the wheel, with the ability to choose different chromatic wheels. The tool also includes a converter that lets users enter a color using a specified color type, and then shows the color converted in all color types, making it easy to find the color you need.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="converter">Converter&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/02/introducing-colorpicker-max/3.png"
width="950"
height="600"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/02/introducing-colorpicker-max/3_hu2366bf50cc1e2a015699cfa8ae3dd591_209552_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/02/introducing-colorpicker-max/3_hu2366bf50cc1e2a015699cfa8ae3dd591_209552_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="The Converter page of ColorPicker Max"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="158"
data-flex-basis="380px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>ColorPicker Max offers several useful tools for manipulating colors, and two of the most powerful are the Converter and Text tools.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The Converter tool allows users to easily convert colors between different color types, such as RGB, HEX, HSV, HSL, CMYK, YIQ, XYZ, and YUV. Users can enter a color using a specified color type, and the tool will automatically display the color converted into all other color types in a color detail panel. If the user enters an invalid color, a message will appear to let them know.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>For some color types, the Converter tool also displays dedicated textboxes that allow users to enter different values for each variable, such as hue, saturation, and value. The tool also provides a preview of the color specified by the user.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="text-tool">Text tool&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/02/introducing-colorpicker-max/4.png"
width="950"
height="600"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/02/introducing-colorpicker-max/4_hu2a35cdb2df6cb3fce550c51ff1e23607_172167_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/02/introducing-colorpicker-max/4_hu2a35cdb2df6cb3fce550c51ff1e23607_172167_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="The Text tool page of ColorPicker Max"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="158"
data-flex-basis="380px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The Text tool is another powerful feature of ColorPicker Max that allows users to set the font, font size, foreground color, and background color for text. The tool also includes a feature that calculates the contrast ratio between the foreground and background colors and displays it as an arrow on a scale, indicating whether the contrast is sufficient for legibility.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>With the Text tool, users can set the color for both regular text and links, and the tool includes a preview of the resulting text as it will appear on a webpage. The ability to set custom font and color styles can be incredibly useful for web designers, graphic designers, and anyone else who needs to manipulate colors and text on a regular basis.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In short, both the Converter and Text tools are powerful and flexible features that can greatly enhance a user&amp;rsquo;s ability to work with and manipulate colors. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a designer, developer, or simply someone who enjoys exploring the world of color, ColorPicker Max has everything you need to get the most out of your work.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="palette-and-gradient">Palette and Gradient&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/02/introducing-colorpicker-max/5.png"
width="950"
height="600"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/02/introducing-colorpicker-max/5_hucf0d2f99c8b6a6b35e23d5704db7547b_203459_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/02/introducing-colorpicker-max/5_hucf0d2f99c8b6a6b35e23d5704db7547b_203459_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="The Palette page of ColorPicker Max"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="158"
data-flex-basis="380px"
>
&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/02/introducing-colorpicker-max/6.png"
width="950"
height="600"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/02/introducing-colorpicker-max/6_hu3fb44c5e736c2952f11397c679738f21_178427_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/02/introducing-colorpicker-max/6_hu3fb44c5e736c2952f11397c679738f21_178427_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="The Gradient page of ColorPicker Max"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="158"
data-flex-basis="380px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>ColorPicker Max also offers a variety of tools for creating color palettes and gradients. The palette tool lets users get different shades, brightness, and hues of a specified color, and also provides the ability to bookmark and save the palette for later. The gradient tool allows users to generate a random gradient with two stops, change the rotation of the gradient, and even export the gradient as CSS.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="bookmarks">Bookmarks&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/02/introducing-colorpicker-max/7.png"
width="950"
height="600"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/02/introducing-colorpicker-max/7_hub06746961ffc8fd7365d6a1037e43423_216220_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/02/introducing-colorpicker-max/7_hub06746961ffc8fd7365d6a1037e43423_216220_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="The bookmark feature of ColorPicker Max, with the &amp;ldquo;Colors&amp;rdquo; tab selected"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="158"
data-flex-basis="380px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>ColorPicker Max allows you to bookmark your favorite colors, palettes, and gradients, making it easy to quickly access them later on. You can organize your bookmarks into different categories, such as regular colors, palettes, and gradients, and easily remove individual bookmarks or clear all bookmarks at once.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>To add a bookmark, simply navigate to the color, palette, or gradient you&amp;rsquo;d like to save and click the bookmark icon. You can access your bookmarks at any time by clicking on the Bookmarks button in the sidebar, and then selecting the category you&amp;rsquo;d like to view.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Bookmarks make it easy to keep track of your favorite color schemes and design elements, allowing you to work more efficiently and effectively.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="modern-experience">Modern experience&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/02/introducing-colorpicker-max/ColorPickerSynethia.gif"
width="1920"
height="1080"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/02/introducing-colorpicker-max/ColorPickerSynethia_hua55f41b039613a4f342957e25a05306a_272959_480x0_resize_box_1.gif 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/02/introducing-colorpicker-max/ColorPickerSynethia_hua55f41b039613a4f342957e25a05306a_272959_1024x0_resize_box_1.gif 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="The Home dashboard is dynamic and unique for each user"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="177"
data-flex-basis="426px"
>
The user interface and user experience of ColorPicker Max are both top-notch. The background is a mesh gradient with subtle colors that adapts to the light or dark theme, while the window is resizable and responsive. The tool also includes a dashboard with the most relevant features for the user and a section for least relevant features, making it easy to find what you need.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In conclusion, ColorPicker Max is an excellent tool for developers, designers, and anyone else who needs to work with colors regularly. Its range of features and ease of use make it a must-have for anyone who wants to work with colors more efficiently. &lt;a class="link" href="https://tinyurl.com/DownloadColorPickerMax" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Try ColorPicker Max today&lt;/a> and experience the difference for yourself!&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="download">Download&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>To get started with ColorPicker Max, &lt;a class="link" href="https://tinyurl.com/DownloadColorPickerMax" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>head to our website and download the installation package&lt;/a>. The app is available for Windows.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Once the installation package has finished downloading, double-click it to begin the installation process. Follow the on-screen instructions to complete the installation.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Once installed, you can launch ColorPicker Max from your applications folder or the Start menu. When you launch the app for the first time, you&amp;rsquo;ll be prompted to choose your default language, theme, and other settings.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="how-to-upgrade-from-colorpicker-4">How to upgrade from ColorPicker 4?&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>It&amp;rsquo;s important to note that ColorPicker Max is not simply an upgrade to ColorPicker 4. While it does share some similarities with its predecessor, ColorPicker Max is a standalone application that needs to be installed manually. Users of ColorPicker 4 will not be able to upgrade to ColorPicker Max through their current application and will need to download and install ColorPicker Max separately.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Despite the need for a manual installation, we believe that the new features and enhancements offered by ColorPicker Max make it worth the effort. The powerful and flexible new tools, as well as the improved user interface and user experience, are designed to help users work more efficiently and effectively with color. So, if you&amp;rsquo;re ready to take your color work to the next level, we encourage you to &lt;a class="link" href="https://tinyurl.com/DownloadColorPickerMax" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>download and install ColorPicker Max today&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="video">Video&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Check the official trailer for ColorPicker Max.&lt;/p>
&lt;center>
&lt;iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/80hluiCUA3o" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen>&lt;/iframe>
&lt;/center></description></item><item><title>A Look at the Latest Download Trends</title><link>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/02/a-look-at-the-latest-download-trends/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 10:38:15 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/02/a-look-at-the-latest-download-trends/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/02/a-look-at-the-latest-download-trends/cover.png" alt="Featured image of post A Look at the Latest Download Trends" />&lt;h2 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>The Léo Corporation is proud to announce the latest trends in software downloads for our popular applications. In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll take a closer look at the number of downloads for our various software programs between December 2022 and January 2023.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="apps">Apps&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>First up is Gavilya, which saw an impressive increase in downloads, going from 1391 in December 2022 to 1506 in January 2023. This represents a 8.27% increase and is a testament to the growing popularity of this software within the Léo Corporation portfolio.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Gerayis also saw an increase in downloads, with 735 downloads in December 2022 and 743 in January 2023. This 1.09% increase is a positive sign for the continued success of this software.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Passliss had a modest increase in downloads, going from 1251 in December 2022 to 1275 in January 2023. This 1.92% increase is a sign of the steady growth and popularity of this software.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>InternetTest Pro 7 saw a significant increase in downloads, going from 704 in December 2022 to 857 in January 2023. This 21.73% increase is a clear indication of the growing popularity of this software and its increasing importance within the Léo Corporation portfolio.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>ColorPicker 4 also saw an increase in downloads, going from 1234 in December 2022 to 1274 in January 2023. This 3.24% increase is a sign of the continued success of this software and its popularity among our users.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Xalyus Store had a small but steady increase in downloads, going from 325 in December 2022 to 331 in January 2023. This 1.85% increase is a positive sign for the continued success of this software.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Datalya saw a modest increase in downloads, going from 537 in December 2022 to 548 in January 2023. This 2.05% increase is a sign of the steady growth and popularity of this software.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Overall, the total number of software downloads increased from 6177 in December 2022 to 6534 in January 2023, a 5.78% increase. This is a positive sign for the Léo Corporation and indicates the continued success and popularity of our software portfolio.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In conclusion, the Léo Corporation is proud to announce the latest trends in software downloads for our popular applications. The data we&amp;rsquo;ve analyzed shows that there is a continued growth in software downloads, with various software programs within our portfolio seeing increases in downloads. Whether it&amp;rsquo;s a modest increase or a significant jump, every increase is a positive sign for the Léo Corporation and a testament to the growing popularity and importance of our software in the market.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="data">Data&lt;/h2>
&lt;table>
&lt;thead>
&lt;tr>
&lt;th>&lt;strong>Software&lt;/strong>&lt;/th>
&lt;th>December 2022&lt;/th>
&lt;th>January&lt;/th>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;/thead>
&lt;tbody>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>&lt;strong>Gavilya&lt;/strong>&lt;/td>
&lt;td>1391&lt;/td>
&lt;td>1506&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>&lt;strong>Gerayis&lt;/strong>&lt;/td>
&lt;td>735&lt;/td>
&lt;td>743&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>&lt;strong>Passliss&lt;/strong>&lt;/td>
&lt;td>1251&lt;/td>
&lt;td>1275&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>&lt;strong>InternetTest Pro 7&lt;/strong>&lt;/td>
&lt;td>704&lt;/td>
&lt;td>857&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>&lt;strong>ColorPicker 4&lt;/strong>&lt;/td>
&lt;td>1234&lt;/td>
&lt;td>1274&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>&lt;strong>Xalyus Store&lt;/strong>&lt;/td>
&lt;td>325&lt;/td>
&lt;td>331&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>&lt;strong>Datalya&lt;/strong>&lt;/td>
&lt;td>537&lt;/td>
&lt;td>548&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>&lt;/td>
&lt;td>&lt;/td>
&lt;td>&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>&lt;/td>
&lt;td>&lt;/td>
&lt;td>&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>&lt;strong>Total&lt;/strong>&lt;/td>
&lt;td>6177&lt;/td>
&lt;td>6534&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>&lt;strong>Increase Percentage&lt;/strong>&lt;/td>
&lt;td>&lt;/td>
&lt;td>5,779504614&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>&lt;/td>
&lt;td>&lt;/td>
&lt;td>&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>&lt;strong>Gavilya&lt;/strong>&lt;/td>
&lt;td>8,164852255&lt;/td>
&lt;td>8,267433501&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>&lt;strong>Gerayis&lt;/strong>&lt;/td>
&lt;td>5,603448276&lt;/td>
&lt;td>1,088435374&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>&lt;strong>Passliss&lt;/strong>&lt;/td>
&lt;td>4,25&lt;/td>
&lt;td>1,918465228&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>&lt;strong>InternetTest Pro 7&lt;/strong>&lt;/td>
&lt;td>21,79930796&lt;/td>
&lt;td>21,73295455&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>&lt;strong>ColorPicker 4&lt;/strong>&lt;/td>
&lt;td>12,07992734&lt;/td>
&lt;td>3,241491086&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>&lt;strong>Xalyus Store&lt;/strong>&lt;/td>
&lt;td>2,848101266&lt;/td>
&lt;td>1,846153846&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>&lt;strong>Datalya&lt;/strong>&lt;/td>
&lt;td>5,708661417&lt;/td>
&lt;td>2,048417132&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;/tbody>
&lt;/table></description></item><item><title>Introducing Devyus</title><link>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/01/introducing-devyus/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 18:58:05 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/01/introducing-devyus/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/01/introducing-devyus/cover.png" alt="Featured image of post Introducing Devyus" />&lt;h2 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Léo Corporation is excited to announce the launch of Devyus, a new division dedicated to developing products and projects for developers. As technology continues to evolve and the role of developers becomes increasingly critical to businesses and organizations, Devyus is committed to improving the workflow and productivity of developers around the world.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>At the heart of Devyus are two innovative products - PeyrSharp, a C# library designed to make developers&amp;rsquo; jobs easier, and Synethia, a basic C# algorithm that can determine the behavior of a user with an application. These products are designed to streamline the development process, helping developers work more efficiently and effectively.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>PeyrSharp is a comprehensive library that simplifies many of the common tasks developers face on a daily basis. With PeyrSharp, developers can write code faster and with fewer errors, allowing them to focus on more important tasks. And with Synethia, developers can gain valuable insights into how users interact with their applications, allowing them to make data-driven decisions and create unique experiences for each user.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>At Devyus, we understand that the role of developers is constantly evolving, and we are committed to staying ahead of the curve. Our team of experts is constantly exploring new technologies and techniques, so that we can bring the best products to market. And because we believe in the power of collaboration, we are always open to feedback and suggestions from the developer community.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>So whether you are a seasoned developer or just starting out, Devyus is here to help. With our innovative products, expert team, and commitment to improving the workflow of developers, we are confident that we can make a real difference in the lives of developers everywhere.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We look forward to working with you!&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="devyus-products">Devyus Products&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>We already have interesting product for you!&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;a class="link" href="https://peyrsharp.leocorporation.dev/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>PeyrSharp&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;a class="link" href="https://synethia.leocorporation.dev/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Synethia&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/01/introducing-devyus/synethia.png"
width="1920"
height="1080"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/01/introducing-devyus/synethia_hu6eaee102f9b00e1034b723db4d774224_497213_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/01/introducing-devyus/synethia_hu6eaee102f9b00e1034b723db4d774224_497213_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="Synethia is now part of Devyus"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="177"
data-flex-basis="426px"
>
&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/01/introducing-devyus/ps.png"
width="1920"
height="1080"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/01/introducing-devyus/ps_hu6eaee102f9b00e1034b723db4d774224_454850_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2023/01/introducing-devyus/ps_hu6eaee102f9b00e1034b723db4d774224_454850_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="PeyrSharp is now part of Devyus"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="177"
data-flex-basis="426px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="what-does-that-mean-for-léo-corporation">What does that mean for Léo Corporation?&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>As a subsidiary of Léo Corporation, Devyus will continue to be backed by the resources and expertise of our parent company. This means that all Devyus products, including PeyrSharp and Synethia, will continue to be published under the Léo Corporation name.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>However, with Devyus, we aim to streamline our development-focused offerings and create a more cohesive and dedicated platform for developers. Future products developed by Devyus will be published under the Devyus name, further solidifying our commitment to improving the workflow and experience of developers.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>For current users of PeyrSharp and Synethia, rest assured that nothing has changed. These products will continue to be supported by Léo Corporation and Devyus, ensuring that developers can continue to use them with confidence.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>A Year in Review and a Look to the Future</title><link>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/12/a-year-in-review-and-a-look-to-the-future/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 18:17:33 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/12/a-year-in-review-and-a-look-to-the-future/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/12/a-year-in-review-and-a-look-to-the-future/cover.png" alt="Featured image of post A Year in Review and a Look to the Future" />&lt;p>It&amp;rsquo;s been an exciting year at Léo Corporation! We&amp;rsquo;ve been hard at work on a number of projects and we&amp;rsquo;re thrilled to share our updates with you.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="a-recap">A recap&lt;/h2>
&lt;h3 id="experiences-made-for-you">Experiences made for you&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>First, we gave our company a fresh new look with a modern and colorful design. We wanted to bring a fresh, updated feel to our apps and services and we&amp;rsquo;re thrilled with the result.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Next, we released InternetTest Pro, a powerful connection utility for Windows. This tool can help you locate IP addresses, send ping requests, and even recover your WiFi passwords. It&amp;rsquo;s a must-have for anyone who needs to troubleshoot their internet connection.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We also redesigned our blog, with better content and exciting articles. We hope you&amp;rsquo;ve enjoyed reading our updates and learning more about our company and products.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We also released Gavilya 3, a simple game launcher with a redesigned look. This tool makes it easy to launch your favorite games, and the new design gives it a fresh, modern feel.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="focusing-on-developers">Focusing on developers&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>In addition to these updates, we released PeyrSharp, a C# library designed to make developers&amp;rsquo; lives easier. With its handy tools and features, PeyrSharp is a valuable resource for any C# developer.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Finally, we released Synethia, a basic C# algorithm that can determine the behavior of a user with an application. This tool is a great resource for developers who want to understand how their users are interacting with their apps.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="whats-next">What&amp;rsquo;s next&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Looking to the future, Léo Corporation has a number of exciting plans in the works. We&amp;rsquo;re focused on improving our existing apps and services, and we&amp;rsquo;ll be extending the features of Synethia to make it even more powerful. We&amp;rsquo;re also committed to creating new delightful experiences for our users by developing new applications and services. And of course, we&amp;rsquo;ll be evolving our existing apps to reflect our vision for the future.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We can&amp;rsquo;t wait to see what the future holds for Léo Corporation, and we&amp;rsquo;re excited to share our updates with you as we continue to grow and evolve. Stay tuned for more exciting news from us!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Introducing PeyrSharp</title><link>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/11/introducing-peyrsharp/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 11:36:34 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/11/introducing-peyrsharp/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/11/introducing-peyrsharp/cover.png" alt="Featured image of post Introducing PeyrSharp" />&lt;h2 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Léo Corporation has been committed to software development for years and has always learn to evolve and improve. We are developing apps and services in C# .NET, and we know it can be frustrating sometimes. We, as software developers, always had this though: “if only they were a library for this.” Therefore, in March 2020, we published LeoCorpLibrary, which was a C# library that contained useful methods. When we started the development of it, we didn&amp;rsquo;t know where the project will go yet. Over the releases, we&amp;rsquo;ve added more and more methods and new features. However, the meaning and the purpose of LeoCorpLibrary was becoming less clear for everyone; it was becoming a mess. This is why we decided to rather not release it fifth version, but instead, we decided to make a brand-new .NET Library, PeyrSharp.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="what-is-peyrsharp">What is PeyrSharp?&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>PeyrSharp is a C# written library designed to make developers&amp;rsquo; life easier. We&amp;rsquo;ve all written code that we wish we hadn&amp;rsquo;t. PeyrSharp is here to respond to this need; by implementing useful methods in various domains: Mathematics, Web/HTTP requests, unit converters, extensions, environment-related operations, and more!&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="a-new-way-to-use-a-library">A new way to use a library&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Unlike LeoCorpLibrary, PeyrSharp is divided in multiples packages:&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Core - the basic methods and features of PeyrSharp&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Env - methods related to the file system and to the current execution environment.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Enums - all enumerations used by PeyrSharp&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Exceptions - all exceptions used by PeyrSharp&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Extensions - extension methods that extends basic types such as string, int, double or arrays (T[]).&lt;/li>
&lt;li>UiHelpers - methods related to Windows Forms or to the Windows Presentation Framework (WPF).&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>All of these modules are included in PeyrSharp; however, PeyrSharp.UiHelpers is only included if you download the package on Windows.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="compatibility">Compatibility&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Some modules of PeyrSharp are targeting features only available in specific operating systems. Thus, some packages aren&amp;rsquo;t available on all platforms.&lt;/p>
&lt;table>
&lt;thead>
&lt;tr>
&lt;th>Package/Platform&lt;/th>
&lt;th>Windows&lt;/th>
&lt;th>macOS&lt;/th>
&lt;th>Linux + others&lt;/th>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;/thead>
&lt;tbody>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>Core&lt;/td>
&lt;td>✅&lt;/td>
&lt;td>✅&lt;/td>
&lt;td>✅&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>Env&lt;/td>
&lt;td>✅&lt;/td>
&lt;td>⚠️&lt;/td>
&lt;td>⚠️&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>Enums&lt;/td>
&lt;td>✅&lt;/td>
&lt;td>✅&lt;/td>
&lt;td>✅&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>Exceptions&lt;/td>
&lt;td>✅&lt;/td>
&lt;td>✅&lt;/td>
&lt;td>✅&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>Extensions&lt;/td>
&lt;td>✅&lt;/td>
&lt;td>✅&lt;/td>
&lt;td>✅&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>UiHelpers&lt;/td>
&lt;td>✅&lt;/td>
&lt;td>❌&lt;/td>
&lt;td>❌&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;/tbody>
&lt;/table>
&lt;p>Caption:&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>✅ Full Support&lt;/li>
&lt;li>⚠️ Partial Support&lt;/li>
&lt;li>❌ Unsupported platform&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="frameworks">Frameworks&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>PeyrSharp is designed to be a modern library, therefore, we decided to ditch support for .NET Framework and .NET Core in favor of .NET 5, 6 and 7.&lt;/p>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>Note: .NET Framework and .NET Core are not targeted by PeyrSharp, since they are no longer supported.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;h2 id="documentation">Documentation&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>PeyrSharp has a documentation, making it easy for developers to use it. &lt;a class="link" href="https://peyrsharp.leocorporation.dev/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Click here&lt;/a> to check the documentation of PeyrSharp.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="packages">Packages&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>PeyrSharp is available on NuGet and &lt;a class="link" href="https://github.com/orgs/Leo-Corporation/packages?repo_name=PeyrSharp" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>GitHub Packages&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;a class="link" href="https://www.nuget.org/packages/PeyrSharp" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>PeyrSharp&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;a class="link" href="https://www.nuget.org/packages/PeyrSharp.Core/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>PeyrSharp.Core&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;a class="link" href="https://www.nuget.org/packages/PeyrSharp.Enums/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>PeyrSharp.Enums&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;a class="link" href="https://www.nuget.org/packages/PeyrSharp.Env/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>PeyrSharp.Env&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;a class="link" href="https://www.nuget.org/packages/PeyrSharp.Exceptions/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>PeyrSharp.Exceptions&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;a class="link" href="https://www.nuget.org/packages/PeyrSharp.Extensions/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>PeyrSharp.Extensions&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;a class="link" href="https://www.nuget.org/packages/PeyrSharp.UiHelpers/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>PeyrSharp.UiHelpers&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item><item><title>Introducing Gavilya 3</title><link>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/10/introducing-gavilya-3/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 11:17:28 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/10/introducing-gavilya-3/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/10/introducing-gavilya-3/cover.png" alt="Featured image of post Introducing Gavilya 3" />&lt;p>Almost two years after its first stable release, we&amp;rsquo;re proud to introduce you Gavilya 3, the next evolution of our game launcher.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="a-new-design">A new design&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>With this new iteration of Gavilya, we decided to improve the user experience alongside with the user interface. Gavilya 3 now features a sidebar where you can find the home page, your games, those you played recently, and also your favorites. You can access you notifications directly from sidebar too. Located on the left side of the app, the sidebar gathers all of Gavilya&amp;rsquo;s features in one place. With the new sidebar, all buttons and menus in the title bar have been removed.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/10/introducing-gavilya-3/2.png"
width="1913"
height="1025"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/10/introducing-gavilya-3/2_hu819e2668b60520cfe33743a1a07197ab_614917_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/10/introducing-gavilya-3/2_hu819e2668b60520cfe33743a1a07197ab_614917_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="The new sidebar"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="186"
data-flex-basis="447px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="improved-profiles">Improved profiles&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Profiles are an important feature of Gavilya. In version 3, the profile experience has been improved; we merged your profile page with the profile switcher, making it easier than ever to create and manage profiles in Gavilya.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/10/introducing-gavilya-3/3.png"
width="1913"
height="1025"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/10/introducing-gavilya-3/3_hufeeae3064479e206e2eea974655124f7_161502_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/10/introducing-gavilya-3/3_hufeeae3064479e206e2eea974655124f7_161502_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="The profile page"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="186"
data-flex-basis="447px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="modern-settings">Modern settings&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>The settings window of Gavilya wasn&amp;rsquo;t really intuitive; therefore, we completely re-imagined the settings experience. Settings can now be access straight from the sidebar, and it will shows up in a new page instead of a window. You can now focus more on what you want to do with the new settings page design: It&amp;rsquo;s simple and intuitive. The design is similar to the one used in our other apps.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/10/introducing-gavilya-3/4.png"
width="1913"
height="1025"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/10/introducing-gavilya-3/4_huce001343679281f0ca22f9da9a68f6d9_74330_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/10/introducing-gavilya-3/4_huce001343679281f0ca22f9da9a68f6d9_74330_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="The new settings page of Gavilya"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="186"
data-flex-basis="447px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="new-card-view">New card view&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>We&amp;rsquo;ve also redesigned a key part of Gavilya: The card view. You will notice that the play button is no longer visible by default: To bring it back, simply hover the card and it will show up again. When hovering a card, you can also now see the name of the game at a glance.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/10/introducing-gavilya-3/5.png"
width="1913"
height="1025"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/10/introducing-gavilya-3/5_hu29fed4cacc38e6931e5bdb2b1db76ad6_1578028_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/10/introducing-gavilya-3/5_hu29fed4cacc38e6931e5bdb2b1db76ad6_1578028_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="The redesigned card view"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="186"
data-flex-basis="447px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="sorting-options">Sorting options&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>We&amp;rsquo;ve also added sorting options to Gavilya: You can sort your games by the alphabetical order or not.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="other-improvements">Other improvements&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>We&amp;rsquo;ve also improved the design consistency across all the pages of Gavilya. We made improvements to performances and fixed some issues. You can now disable notifications as well.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>You can find the full changelog of this release &lt;a class="link" href="https://github.com/Leo-Corporation/Gavilya/releases/tag/3.0.0.2210" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>here&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="download">Download&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;a class="link" href="https://bit.ly/Gavilya" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Click here&lt;/a> to download Gavilya.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="video">Video&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Check the official trailer for Gavilya 3.&lt;/p>
&lt;center>
&lt;iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/5oTTGhVSqlw" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen>&lt;/iframe>
&lt;/center></description></item><item><title>Introducing InternetTest Pro</title><link>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/08/introducing-internettest-pro/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2022 11:19:43 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/08/introducing-internettest-pro/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/08/introducing-internettest-pro/cover.png" alt="Featured image of post Introducing InternetTest Pro" />&lt;p>We are excited to introduce you the next generation of the InternetTest application; it is called InternetTest Pro!&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>InternetTest is one of our oldest products still maintained and has evolved during all those years, from a simple utility to check if your internet connection is working as expected, to an app that helps you to locate an IP address, check if websites are working or not, and more.
We are experience creators, and we are more than happy to share with you the pioneer of a new era, InternetTest Pro.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="a-new-and-improved-user-interface">A new and improved user interface&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/08/introducing-internettest-pro/home.png"
width="1260"
height="711"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/08/introducing-internettest-pro/home_hu2c7366a6a4a4f9eca05e2adf08b4862a_155819_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/08/introducing-internettest-pro/home_hu2c7366a6a4a4f9eca05e2adf08b4862a_155819_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="The &amp;ldquo;Home&amp;rdquo; dashboard of InternetTest"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="177"
data-flex-basis="425px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>InternetTest Pro, also called InternetTest 7, offers a new user interface; you will notice a brand-new side bar with “pinned” actions and different menus. You can access your favorite functionalities using this new side bar, or by using the “Home” dashboard; it is a place specially made for you where you can quickly find useful actions and features. We have added subtle animations as well.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/08/introducing-internettest-pro/dark_ping.png"
width="925"
height="572"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/08/introducing-internettest-pro/dark_ping_huf57da0f3ee95b9c25608874b497d475b_377156_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/08/introducing-internettest-pro/dark_ping_huf57da0f3ee95b9c25608874b497d475b_377156_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="The dark theme of InternetTest Pro"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="161"
data-flex-basis="388px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We are also introducing an improved light and dark theme; the background of the window is no longer white: Instead, there is a subtle mesh gradient with different colors. The accent color is also more used in different part of the app. Finally, you will notice that there are less shades of gray, and more shades of blue used everywhere in InternetTest.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="an-experience-conceived-for-you">An experience conceived for you&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/08/introducing-internettest-pro/gif.gif"
width="1920"
height="1080"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/08/introducing-internettest-pro/gif_hu0bfa102810c46a57b06a55741c09d3bb_505742_480x0_resize_box_1.gif 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/08/introducing-internettest-pro/gif_hu0bfa102810c46a57b06a55741c09d3bb_505742_1024x0_resize_box_1.gif 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="A GIF that shows different Synethia configurations"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="177"
data-flex-basis="426px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We want our users to have the best experience possible when they use our apps. We believe that our products should adapt to their needs, and that our users should not have to adapt to the limitations of our applications. Therefore, we want to introduce you Synethia, an algorithm that can understand your habits and which features you’d like to use. When you are using InternetTest Pro, Synethia will collect data on how you spent time with each feature, and which interactions you have made. The data is then analyzed, and this how the “Home” dashboard shows you recommended actions and features. The more you use InternetTest Pro, the more Synethia will be able to understand your needs.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Now, we are aware that this feature will raise privacy concerns about the data collected, and we want to be fully transparent with you. The data is stored on your device anonymously and is NOT send to Léo Corporation. It is NOT used by any third-party application or company other than InternetTest itself. You have full control over your data; you can reset it or erase it completely. You can, at any time, disable Synethia in the Settings. Synethia cannot interact with other apps or program.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="a-new-set-of-features">A new set of features&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>InternetTest Pro has all the features included in InternetTest 6, which are: Connection Status, Down Detector, My IP, and Locate an IP. With this new version we are introducing three new features: Ping, IP Config, and WiFi Passwords (recovery).&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="ping">Ping&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/08/introducing-internettest-pro/ping.png"
width="1259"
height="707"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/08/introducing-internettest-pro/ping_hu853d6b890bcc3dc740451ed783f201ac_168588_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/08/introducing-internettest-pro/ping_hu853d6b890bcc3dc740451ed783f201ac_168588_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="The ping page"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="178"
data-flex-basis="427px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The Ping feature allows you to send a ping request to specified IP address or URL. It works exactly like the “ping” command in Windows. You can get useful information when you make a ping, such as the maximum/minimum and average duration of each request, the number of packages sent, received, or lost, and the IP address if you provided an URL.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="ip-config">IP Config&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/08/introducing-internettest-pro/ipconfig.png"
width="1263"
height="710"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/08/introducing-internettest-pro/ipconfig_hubd67f62cf47da7ae3206913f38c55a6a_154361_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/08/introducing-internettest-pro/ipconfig_hubd67f62cf47da7ae3206913f38c55a6a_154361_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="The new IP Config feature"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="177"
data-flex-basis="426px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The IP Config feature works the same as the “ipconfig” command available in the Windows command prompt. You will be able to get a list of all the network interfaces registered on your system. By default, only the connected interfaces details are expanded. You can copy the information of each interface. This information contains: Status (connected/disconnected), the DNS Suffix, the local IPv4 and IPv6 address, the subnet mask, and the default gateway IP address (in IPv4 and IPv6).&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="wifi-passwords">WiFi Passwords&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/08/introducing-internettest-pro/wifi.png"
width="1261"
height="707"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/08/introducing-internettest-pro/wifi_huf1d30c9a5728e99bb39cb108a1f38ea4_139280_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/08/introducing-internettest-pro/wifi_huf1d30c9a5728e99bb39cb108a1f38ea4_139280_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="The new WiFi Passwords recovery feature"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="178"
data-flex-basis="428px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>This feature allows you to recover all passwords of all the WiFi networks you have already been connected to. By default, the page is empty for security reasons, you will need to click on the “Get locally stored networks” button to see all registered networks on your device. You can then expand each network details to learn more about the encryption algorithm, the authentication mode, the connection type/mode, and most importantly, the network key. The key is hidden by default; click on the “eye” icon next to it to show the key.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="a-new-history">A new history&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/08/introducing-internettest-pro/history.png"
width="1260"
height="711"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/08/introducing-internettest-pro/history_hu68096e7bd2dd89c1e7c35690166843f7_139422_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/08/introducing-internettest-pro/history_hu68096e7bd2dd89c1e7c35690166843f7_139422_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="The history page of InternetTest Pro"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="177"
data-flex-basis="425px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We are also glad to announce a unified history page. On this page you will be able to see the results of each test made using the “Status” or “Down Detector” feature. You can erase the history at any time.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="simplified-settings">Simplified settings&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>We are also committed to improvements of the settings page: Some sections are gone because we grouped them in a single category. For example, the default test website and the default HTTP protocol are now in the same “Web” category. The update system has also been reworked, so you can quickly see if InternetTest Pro is up to date or not. The theme and the default page picker have all been simplified.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/08/introducing-internettest-pro/settings.png"
width="1262"
height="708"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/08/introducing-internettest-pro/settings_huae478a23d0c943eb1125d3ede91da570_110040_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/08/introducing-internettest-pro/settings_huae478a23d0c943eb1125d3ede91da570_110040_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="The settings of InternetTest Pro"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="178"
data-flex-basis="427px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="what-is-next-for-internettest-6">What is next for InternetTest 6?&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>The support for InternetTest 6 will end; it won’t receive new features anymore. InternetTest Pro will not be offered as an upgrade of InternetTest 6 because we consider it as a different product. We will let our users choose whether they want to upgrade or not.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="download">Download&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;a class="link" href="https://tinyurl.com/DownloadITP7" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Click here&lt;/a> to explore your new experience with InternetTest Pro.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="video">Video&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Check the official trailer for InternetTest Pro.&lt;/p>
&lt;center>
&lt;iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/ozg_5TjYoZ0" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen>&lt;/iframe>
&lt;/center></description></item><item><title>Our New Blog</title><link>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/08/our-new-blog/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 09:33:41 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/08/our-new-blog/</guid><description>&lt;p>Today, we are releasing a huge update to our blog: We are switching from Blogger to Hugo, a static website generator. This change will give us more control over our content and makes it easier to publish new and exciting articles.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="what-is-new">What is new?&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>The blog is now using a modern responsive theme that support both light and dark mode. We are introducing “Categories”; it is a new way to sort articles. There is now a table of content in every article, you can also see the estimated reading time next to the date. We have added links to our socials as well, and a brand new About page too.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="what-is-gone">What is gone?&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>With this new update, we have decided it is the best time to move on, so our older articles from 2018 to 2020, are no longer available, but they still are on the old blog which will stay accessible.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="what-is-next">What is next?&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>We hope that you will like the modern design; we are excited to post new and better articles on this blog, as a big announcement is coming soon.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>A slight update on our look</title><link>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/07/a-slight-update-on-our-look/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/07/a-slight-update-on-our-look/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/07/a-slight-update-on-our-look/cover.png" alt="Featured image of post A slight update on our look" />&lt;h2 id="we-have-a-new-look">We have a new look!&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>As you may have noticed, we’ve updated our font in our logos and websites. We are announcing that we’re ditching the Montserrat font for Hauora Sans. This font gives more personality to our identity, since the old font was one of the most popular sans serif fonts used in apps, websites, and product. The new one is – indeed – like Montserrat, but it adds some small details that makes it better than the old one.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="when-will-this-change-take-effect">When will this change take effect?&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>As we said, most of our websites have already received an update. However, our apps haven’t yet. An update should roll out to them this month.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Léo Corporation is always evolving, and we would like to thank our users for taking this journey with us.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="image">Image&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/07/a-slight-update-on-our-look/cover.png"
width="3438"
height="1146"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/07/a-slight-update-on-our-look/cover_hu11d46245019c0cc4f6837ea1f8635293_782421_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/07/a-slight-update-on-our-look/cover_hu11d46245019c0cc4f6837ea1f8635293_782421_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="The Léo Corporation logo, updated with the new Hauora font."
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="300"
data-flex-basis="720px"
>&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>We've updated our visual identity</title><link>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/01/weve-updated-our-visual-identity/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/01/weve-updated-our-visual-identity/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2022/01/weve-updated-our-visual-identity/cover.png" alt="Featured image of post We've updated our visual identity" />&lt;p>2021 has been a busy year for Léo Corporation, and 2022 will be focused on how we can improve the user experience across our products.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>To start this new year, we’ve slightly updated our visual identity to a more colorful one. You may have seen on our &lt;a class="link" href="https://twitter.com/LeoCorpNews" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Twitter&lt;/a>, &lt;a class="link" href="https://www.facebook.com/LeoCorporationSoftwares/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Facebook&lt;/a>, and &lt;a class="link" href="https://www.instagram.com/leocorporation_/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Instagram&lt;/a> that a more colorful look has been adapted. These colors are – of course – colors of Léo Corporation, but they are also here to bring a more vibrant vibe to our posts. However, we haven’t changed our logo, even though there are now a black and a white variant of it. You will also notice new splash screens that will come to applications that use one on the upcoming weeks.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Introducing the new Status page</title><link>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/08/introducing-new-status-page/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/08/introducing-new-status-page/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/08/introducing-new-status-page/cover.png" alt="Featured image of post Introducing the new Status page" />&lt;p>Software development is often punctuated with bugs, issues and incidents that may impact our users. It might be hard for them to understand why is one our software, service, isn’t working, or why they can’t access our website anymore for instance. We often inform our users of any issues impacting our services on our Twitter account &lt;a class="link" href="https://twitter.com/LeoCorpNews" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>@LeoCorpNews&lt;/a>, but some people aren’t aware of the existence of this account, or don’t use Twitter. This is why we’ve created a new website dedicated to “status monitoring”.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>This new website is available at &lt;a class="link" href="https://status.leocorporation.dev" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>status.leocorporation.dev&lt;/a> and is updated every day. You can quickly see which system is operating normally, and those who don’t. If you are having an issue with one of our services that depend on others, such as our update system, Gavilya’s integration with RAWG, you can come to this website and see if everything is working correctly or not.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We hope that this website helps you to get informed when an issue is occurring.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Introducing Datalya</title><link>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/07/introducing-datalya/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/07/introducing-datalya/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/07/introducing-datalya/cover.png" alt="Featured image of post Introducing Datalya" />&lt;h2 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Last year, we’ve launched two products: GestionBiblio X and GestionPerso X. They were specialized database management tools. They provided a brand new and modern user interface at the time. The goal was to rewrite the codebase from Visual Basic to C#, to introduce new features and a new design language. However, these two softwares were only available in French, not in English, and they weren’t receiving updates as much as other Léo Corporation’s softwares. This is why we are today introducing the next generation of database management at Léo Corporation: Datalya.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/07/introducing-datalya/cover.png"
width="1100"
height="650"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/07/introducing-datalya/cover_hu585b845bac6b9b98f4e385dce7b37f4b_23177_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/07/introducing-datalya/cover_hu585b845bac6b9b98f4e385dce7b37f4b_23177_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="The home page of Datalya."
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="169"
data-flex-basis="406px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="whats-datalya">What&amp;rsquo;s Datalya?&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Datalya is a modern and yet simple database management software for Windows. The main innovation of Datalya is Blocks. Blocks are different types of input for a user. For instance, you can have a simple text input, to a checkbox input, without forgetting the dropdown input. These Blocks are customizable, you can name theme, add choices, and more. You can even export your Blocks as a Template, so you can reuse them quickly in other databases. In a nutshell, Blocks are used to create your Database.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>You can find Blocks in the “Creator” part. Talking about parts, Datalya is divided into two parts: The Creator part, and the Database part. We’ve talked about the Creator part already, so let’s move on to the Database part.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/07/introducing-datalya/2.png"
width="1100"
height="650"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/07/introducing-datalya/2_hu2eef5c95aec75c556b3140a77e649b6b_53904_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/07/introducing-datalya/2_hu2eef5c95aec75c556b3140a77e649b6b_53904_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="The Creator part of Datalya."
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="169"
data-flex-basis="406px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The Database part is where the database is. You’ll notice a ribbon UI at the top, and the database’s content filling the rest of the window. By default, it’s empty: Indeed, we need to add an item to the database first. You can go to “Edit” tab in the ribbon, and then click on “Add”. You’ll see that a window with your Blocks has appeared, and in this window, you can fill the fields and then add the item.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/07/introducing-datalya/3.png"
width="1100"
height="650"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/07/introducing-datalya/3_hue7a0290966fbba52ed17248da6e91028_30750_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/07/introducing-datalya/3_hue7a0290966fbba52ed17248da6e91028_30750_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="The Database part of Datalya."
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="169"
data-flex-basis="406px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Once you’ve added the item, you can edit it, delete it, etc.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The other new feature is the possibility to export a database to an Excel spreadsheet. You can go to the “Export” tab of the ribbon and click on “Export to Excel”. Note that Datalya only supports .xlsx files.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/07/introducing-datalya/4.png"
width="1100"
height="650"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/07/introducing-datalya/4_hu585b845bac6b9b98f4e385dce7b37f4b_23177_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/07/introducing-datalya/4_hu585b845bac6b9b98f4e385dce7b37f4b_23177_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="The home page of Datalya."
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="169"
data-flex-basis="406px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>When launching Datalya, you’ll see the home screen, this is where all your recent files are shown for you to jump into a database quickly. You can even pin your most important databases if you have a lot of them.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Datalya is also customizable: it is available in English and French, and it has a dark mode! You can also change update settings and reset them anytime.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/07/introducing-datalya/5.png"
width="1100"
height="650"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/07/introducing-datalya/5_huad7e4adbac23ae106fcf61238f387534_36323_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/07/introducing-datalya/5_huad7e4adbac23ae106fcf61238f387534_36323_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="The dark theme of Datalya."
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="169"
data-flex-basis="406px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>There is still a lot of features that we didn’t covered in this article, but we will let you discover them by yourself. We’ve been working on Datalya for a few months now, and we focused on the design and on the user experience with the product, to deliver you an enjoyable experience while working on a database.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>As always, Datalya will be free and Open-Source.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="whats-next-for-gestionbiblio-x-and-gestionperso-x">What’s next for GestionBiblio X and GestionPerso X&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>The release of Datalya also means that our old GestionBiblio X and GestionPerso X softwares are now deprecated, and we recommend that the users of theses products switch to Datalya. If you are a user of one of these products, you can create a new database in Datalya by selecting ether the “Books” template or the “People” template.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="website">Website&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;a class="link" href="https://datalya.leocorporation.dev/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Click here&lt;/a> to go the website of Datalya.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="download">Download&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;a class="link" href="https://tinyurl.com/DownloadDatalya" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Click here&lt;/a> to download Datalya.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The next chapter for Educ'Maths</title><link>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/07/the-next-chapter-for-educmaths/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/07/the-next-chapter-for-educmaths/</guid><description>&lt;p>Educ’Maths was a game to test your knowledge in math. It was developed back in 2018, and was released under the name “Educ’Maths”, and later renamed “Educ’Maths 2018”. At the time, Educ’Maths was one of our first and biggest software we’ve ever released. Then, Educ’Maths became a series of games: Educ’Maths 2019, 2020, and finally, 2021. For each edition, we tried to push the limit of the previous one, and we went from a simple quiz game to an interactive and fun game in 2021. In June 2021, 23% of downloaded softwares were Educ’Maths games.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>However, we have decided to end the Educ’Maths series here.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In previous blog articles, we told you that 2021 is going to be a big year for Léo Corporation, and indeed, we’ve release in 2021 more softwares and software updates than ever. Our vision has through the years evolved, and today, we want to focus on software creation, not games. This doesn’t mean that we will never release games again, but for now, we want to follow a new path for Léo Corporation. This path is impacted by global changes: We are living in an era where computers are now the center of our lives. The vision of Léo Corporation is to improve people’s productivity. We are doing this by releasing each year, new softwares and new experiences.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>This means that there won’t be an “Educ’Maths 2022”, and the support of Educ’Maths games is going end sooner.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>For players of Educ’Maths 2020, the end of support date is unchanged: On the 1st of December 2021, the support will end. This implies that Educ’Maths 2020 will no longer receive any updates, or patches.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>If you are also a player of Educ’Maths 2021, the end of support has changed, and it will be the same as Educ’Maths 2020’s, the 1st of December 2021, a year earlier. Like Educ’Maths 2020, Educ’Maths 2021 will no longer receive any updates or patches, but you will still be able to play the game of course.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The end of support also means that you will no longer be able to download Educ’Maths from our website, or from Xalyus Store. About Xalyus Store, the “Games” category is also going away.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We would like to thank again everyone who played Educ’Maths games.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Introducing The new Xalyus Store</title><link>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/05/introducing-new-xalyus-store/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/05/introducing-new-xalyus-store/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/05/introducing-new-xalyus-store/cover.png" alt="Featured image of post Introducing The new Xalyus Store" />&lt;p>Last year, we have launched the successor of the “Léo Corporation Store”, Xalyus Store. It came out with a brand-new design and brand features. Today, we are happy to introduce the next evolution of Xalyus Store.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>When we started creating softwares, we always wanted a place where people could download them. We thought making a website was great, and we did so. But we also wanted a place on desktop, where we could showcase and display our apps. Therefore, we create a software called “Store”. With it, you could download any of our softwares directly from your computer. Then, we wanted to have a complete redesign of this app, and so we decided to modernize it by building a brand-new one: Xalyus Store.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Xalyus Store was our redesigned tore, with the same concepts but more polished. However, we encountered the same problem with the “Store”: If we want to add new softwares, update any informations, we needed to update Xalyus Store, which isn’t a great way of distributing new softwares. This is why we are here today, introducing the second major version of Xalyus Store.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="completely-autonomous">Completely autonomous&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/05/introducing-new-xalyus-store/cover.png"
width="1200"
height="700"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/05/introducing-new-xalyus-store/cover_hu7f09eeae559180f24b6b08c0accbe99d_69880_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/05/introducing-new-xalyus-store/cover_hu7f09eeae559180f24b6b08c0accbe99d_69880_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="The &amp;ldquo;Home&amp;rdquo; page of Xalyus Store"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="171"
data-flex-basis="411px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>This next evolution of Xalyus Store is complete autonomous: You don’t have to update it to check if new softwares are available, everything is automatic! You may not see a lot of changes compared to the first version, but they are massive since it is about an entire new infrastructure and delivering system.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="modern-design">Modern design&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/05/introducing-new-xalyus-store/2.png"
width="1200"
height="700"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/05/introducing-new-xalyus-store/2_huf051724bd68539e5d868d511866d11f8_69473_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/05/introducing-new-xalyus-store/2_huf051724bd68539e5d868d511866d11f8_69473_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="The &amp;ldquo;Apps&amp;rdquo; page of Xalyus Store"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="171"
data-flex-basis="411px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>To keep our softwares consistent, the new Xalyus Store has a new and modern user interface, alongside with new themes. You can choose between light and dark theme or stick to your system’s default theme if you are using Windows 10.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="trust-and-secure">Trust and secure&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>As you may now, most of our softwares are Open-Source on GitHub. This means that the code of our softwares is available to anyone, even malicious people who may try to inject malicious code in our softwares and distribute an infected copy to you. Xalyus Store is one of our trusted sources for downloading softwares, the risk of having a virus using it, is almost inexistent.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="upgrading">Upgrading&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>The new Xalyus Store is not an update of the first version of Xalyus Store, you’ll need to remove the old Xalyus Store and download the new one.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="download">Download&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;a class="link" href="https://tinyurl.com/DownloadXalyusStore" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Click here&lt;/a> to download Xalyus Store.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>New website</title><link>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/05/new-website/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/05/new-website/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/05/new-website/cover.png" alt="Featured image of post New website" />&lt;p>Starting today, leocorp.fr will no longer be our main website, and will be replace by leocorporation.dev.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>After a few years using a Wix website, we have made the decision to stop using Wix services and build instead our own website ourselves. We wanted a more personal website that entirely belongs to us, and this is now the case.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>For a few weeks now, we have been working on a new website using GitHub Pages for the hosting. You could access the website by entering the “https://leo-corporation.github.io/Leo-Corporation-Web/” URL, but you can now access it by typing “leocorporation.dev” in your browser.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>You will notice that the forum is no longer present.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>With this change, we also changed the blog URL, you can type “blog.leocorporation.dev” to access the blog quicker.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The new website is – of course – &lt;a class="link" href="https://github.com/Leo-Corporation/Leo-Corporation-Web" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Open-Source&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>As we said earlier, this year is going to be a big one for Léo Corporation, so stay tuned for more exciting announcements in the next months, and thanks to everyone supporting Léo Corporation.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Introducing ColorPicker 3</title><link>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/04/introducing-colorpicker-3/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/04/introducing-colorpicker-3/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/04/introducing-colorpicker-3/cover.png" alt="Featured image of post Introducing ColorPicker 3" />&lt;p>A year ago, we have announced the second major version of ColorPicker, which was a big step forward for ColorPicker. Today, we are proud to announce the third version of ColorPicker, with a new design and new features.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>ColorPicker was the first software for developers. Its goal was to empower a part of the development and/or design process: Color selection. Sometimes, when you want to use a color in a project, and you do not know any information about it, like the RGB values, or the HEX color code, it is very frustrating. Therefore, we created ColorPicker. ColorPicker’s main goal was to solve this problem. Using your mouse pointer, you could point a place on your screen, and get information about the color, at the time, you could only get RGB values. Then, we have released ColorPicker 2, with a new design and new features, like the new manual color-picking tool, and the possibility to get HEX color code. With ColorPicker 3, we wanted to put all this features you love, and make them even better.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="what-is-new">What is new?&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>ColorPicker 3 introduces a brand-new design like &lt;a class="link" href="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/02/introducing-passliss.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Passliss’&lt;/a> design, with a navigation bar on the left, and the content on the other side. This minimalist approach is aiming to improve the user experience overall.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/04/introducing-colorpicker-3/cover.png"
width="800"
height="450"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/04/introducing-colorpicker-3/cover_hu6d49e402343e0aa203165af3337feeff_37446_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/04/introducing-colorpicker-3/cover_hu6d49e402343e0aa203165af3337feeff_37446_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="The &amp;ldquo;Picker&amp;rdquo; page of ColorPicker"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="177"
data-flex-basis="426px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>ColorPicker 3 also adds a new “Converter” page, to help you convert different color types easier. For instance, you can convert a RGB color to HEX and HSV.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/04/introducing-colorpicker-3/2.png"
width="800"
height="450"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/04/introducing-colorpicker-3/2_huec19de53eabf445f82e1e5f5c1aa50b6_38186_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/04/introducing-colorpicker-3/2_huec19de53eabf445f82e1e5f5c1aa50b6_38186_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="The &amp;ldquo;Converter&amp;rdquo; page of ColorPicker"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="177"
data-flex-basis="426px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>ColorPicker 1 was only available in light mode, ColorPicker 2 was only available in dark mode, and ColorPicker is available in both. You can now set in ColorPicker’s settings if you want to use light or dark mode.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/04/introducing-colorpicker-3/3.png"
width="800"
height="450"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/04/introducing-colorpicker-3/3_hu53e4d7e9ab39922d2f2e2ef1d202128d_40172_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/04/introducing-colorpicker-3/3_hu53e4d7e9ab39922d2f2e2ef1d202128d_40172_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="The dark mode of ColorPicker"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="177"
data-flex-basis="426px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="open-source">Open Source&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>With this third version, we have decided to open-source ColorPicker 3, and the Git repository is – of course – available on &lt;a class="link" href="https://github.com/Leo-Corporation/ColorPicker" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>GitHub&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="upgrading">Upgrading&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>ColorPicker 3 is not an update and will not be proposed as an update of ColorPicker 2. If you want to upgrade to ColorPicker 3, you will need to download and install ColorPicker 3. Also, ColorPicker 2’s support will end soon, so no more updates will be delivered to it.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="download">Download&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;a class="link" href="https://tinyurl.com/DownloadColorPicker" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Click here&lt;/a> to download ColorPicker 3.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Introducing InternetTest 5</title><link>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/03/introducing-internettest-5/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/03/introducing-internettest-5/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/03/introducing-internettest-5/cover.png" alt="Featured image of post Introducing InternetTest 5" />&lt;p>Approximately a year ago, we have announced the fourth version of InternetTest. Today, we are proud to announce the InternetTest 5, the next evolution of the utility.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>InternetTest was one of our first software and is also one of the first open-sourced project that we have published on GitHub. InternetTest main purpose was to enable users to check if they are connected to Internet. Why? Because even if you can check it directly by looking to the icon in the Windows system tray, this icon can sometimes be misleading, and therefore we have created InternetTest.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Today, InternetTest features have diversified and now, you can also localize IPs, check if a website is down, and you can also customize features, such as dark theme and the default test site.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="version-5-codename-syghroni">Version 5 (Codename Syghroni)&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>As you lately saw, we are redesigning a lot of our current software, and we are not done yet! InternetTest is now exception, and this fifth version does not include brand new features, but focuses on the user experience and user interface, to make you love InternetTest.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>As you can see in the pictures below, the new design follows the same guidelines that Passliss or Gerayis uses.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/03/introducing-internettest-5/cover.png"
width="800"
height="450"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/03/introducing-internettest-5/cover_hu6af9ea77f70ccf042c79c7fbd9e100f3_34252_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/03/introducing-internettest-5/cover_hu6af9ea77f70ccf042c79c7fbd9e100f3_34252_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="The main window of InternetTest 5"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="177"
data-flex-basis="426px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/03/introducing-internettest-5/cover.png"
width="800"
height="450"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/03/introducing-internettest-5/cover_hu6af9ea77f70ccf042c79c7fbd9e100f3_34252_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/03/introducing-internettest-5/cover_hu6af9ea77f70ccf042c79c7fbd9e100f3_34252_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="The main window of InternetTest 5, in dark theme"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="177"
data-flex-basis="426px"
>
&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/03/introducing-internettest-5/cover.png"
width="800"
height="450"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/03/introducing-internettest-5/cover_hu6af9ea77f70ccf042c79c7fbd9e100f3_34252_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/03/introducing-internettest-5/cover_hu6af9ea77f70ccf042c79c7fbd9e100f3_34252_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="The Locate IP page of InternetTest 5"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="177"
data-flex-basis="426px"
>
&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/03/introducing-internettest-5/cover.png"
width="800"
height="450"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/03/introducing-internettest-5/cover_hu6af9ea77f70ccf042c79c7fbd9e100f3_34252_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/03/introducing-internettest-5/cover_hu6af9ea77f70ccf042c79c7fbd9e100f3_34252_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="The DownDetector page of InternetTest 5"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="177"
data-flex-basis="426px"
>
&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/03/introducing-internettest-5/cover.png"
width="800"
height="450"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/03/introducing-internettest-5/cover_hu6af9ea77f70ccf042c79c7fbd9e100f3_34252_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/03/introducing-internettest-5/cover_hu6af9ea77f70ccf042c79c7fbd9e100f3_34252_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="The settings of InternetTest 5"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="177"
data-flex-basis="426px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>InternetTest 5 is also using darker colors for dark theme.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="upgrading">Upgrading&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Be aware that InternetTest 5 will not be proposed as an update of InternetTest 4, if you want to upgrade, you will have to do it manually by downloading InternetTest 5. After installing InternetTest 5, you can remove InternetTest 4, since no updates will be delivered to it.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="download">Download&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;a class="link" href="https://tinyurl.com/DownloadInternetTest" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Click here&lt;/a> to download InternetTest 5.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Introducing Gerayis</title><link>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/03/introducing-gerayis/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/03/introducing-gerayis/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/03/introducing-gerayis/cover.png" alt="Featured image of post Introducing Gerayis" />&lt;p>We are starting this month with the release of a new software: Gerayis. Gerayis is the next evolution of Bar Code Generator 2.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>It&amp;rsquo;s been a few years already since we&amp;rsquo;ve released the first version of Bar Code Generator (at the time, named in french &amp;ldquo;Générateur de codes barre&amp;rdquo;). Then, last year, 2020, we&amp;rsquo;ve released Bar Code Generator 2, with a brand new design, and the possibility to generate QR Codes.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The second version main purpose was to deliver to our users, a brand new user experience, while also adding new features.
Gerayis is the next of evolution of Bar Code Generator, with a design and user experience similar to &lt;a class="link" href="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/02/introducing-passliss.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Passliss&lt;/a>'.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/03/introducing-gerayis/cover.png"
width="800"
height="450"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/03/introducing-gerayis/cover_hu0b071e93705d6c2f85cb089c7ad7697e_32262_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/03/introducing-gerayis/cover_hu0b071e93705d6c2f85cb089c7ad7697e_32262_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="The &amp;ldquo;Bar Code&amp;rdquo; page of Gerayis"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="177"
data-flex-basis="426px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="features">Features&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Gerayis has the same features than Bar Code Generator 2, but they are improved, like the QR Code generator which is using a different library than Bar Code Generator 2: &lt;a class="link" href="https://www.nuget.org/packages/QRCoder" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>QRCoder&lt;/a>.
Gerayis also includes an improved dark theme and an updated language system.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/03/introducing-gerayis/2.png"
width="800"
height="450"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/03/introducing-gerayis/2_huda3afdd284a24668dc6717a232a58de1_34035_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/03/introducing-gerayis/2_huda3afdd284a24668dc6717a232a58de1_34035_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="The &amp;ldquo;QR Code&amp;rdquo; page of Gerayis"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="177"
data-flex-basis="426px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="open-source">Open Source&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Gerayis is Open-Source, and you can check the GitHub repo by &lt;a class="link" href="https://github.com/Leo-Corporation/Gerayis" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>clicking here&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="download">Download&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;a class="link" href="https://bit.ly/DownloadGerayis" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Click here&lt;/a> to download Gerayis.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Password Generator 3: The last release is out</title><link>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/03/password-generator-3-last-release-is-out/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/03/password-generator-3-last-release-is-out/</guid><description>&lt;p>The release of Password Generator 3 is out, and it&amp;rsquo;s the version 3.7.1.2103.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="changelog">Changelog&lt;/h2>
&lt;h3 id="new">New&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Added a link to download Passliss&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Added a message to download Passliss&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="updated">Updated&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Updated version and copyright&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Updated logo&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="download">Download&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;a class="link" href="https://www.mediafire.com/file/jkgl5tsmf4us0x1/G%C3%A9n%C3%A9rateur&amp;#43;de&amp;#43;mots&amp;#43;de&amp;#43;passe&amp;#43;3&amp;#43;Setup.msi/file" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Click here&lt;/a> to download Password Generator 3.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a class="link" href="https://www.mediafire.com/file/ohcs00n2nv6zocn/PasslissSetup.exe/file" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Click here&lt;/a> to download Passliss.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Introducing Passliss</title><link>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/02/introducing-passliss/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/02/introducing-passliss/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/02/introducing-passliss/cover.png" alt="Featured image of post Introducing Passliss" />&lt;p>After a month of developpment, Passliss, the successor of Password Generator 3 is out and generaly available for the public.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Password Generator is part of our most popular softwares since the launch of the third version. This third version was designed to be built on a more modern platform (C# - Windows Forms) and also to deliver a more modern UI (Guna.UI) For Passliss, we chose to focus on one thing: innovation. Passliss is our second software to be built using WPF, and our first software to use our new design guidelines, which mainely focus on User eXperience (UX) but also on User Interface (UI). Thanks to this guidelines, Passliss is offering to our users an intuitive and modern experience.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/02/introducing-passliss/cover.png"
width="800"
height="450"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/02/introducing-passliss/cover_huffb5f60309ff2ea485e3f5e3b98d2e90_38472_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/02/introducing-passliss/cover_huffb5f60309ff2ea485e3f5e3b98d2e90_38472_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="Passliss&amp;rsquo; main window"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="177"
data-flex-basis="426px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="features">Features&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Passliss offers a few useful features to make password generation easier. Let&amp;rsquo;s start with the password generation customization system, the main page. You an easily customize the password that isgoing to be generated, you can choose if the password will include lower case, upper case, numbers and special caracters. You can also choose the length of the password. You can save your configuration by using Password Configurations, which allows you to save a specific password generation configuration.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/02/introducing-passliss/2.png"
width="800"
height="450"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/02/introducing-passliss/2_huf93430e73d63529cf08e5a397cb6c34a_44478_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/02/introducing-passliss/2_huf93430e73d63529cf08e5a397cb6c34a_44478_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="Passliss&amp;rsquo; Password configuration feature"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="177"
data-flex-basis="426px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Passliss can also evaluate the strenght of a password. There is multiples levels of strenght:&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Low, you should change your password&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Medium, adding more complexity to your password would be a nice addition&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Good, you can safely use this password&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Excellent, the chances of someone finding your password are near inexistant.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>Passliss also has an auto-update system and a dark mode!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/02/introducing-passliss/3.png"
width="800"
height="450"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/02/introducing-passliss/3_hua77fc20e2ccb0faeebea776ab6a1568e_42317_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/02/introducing-passliss/3_hua77fc20e2ccb0faeebea776ab6a1568e_42317_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="Passliss, in dark mode"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="177"
data-flex-basis="426px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="open-source">Open Source&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Passliss is also Open Source on &lt;a class="link" href="https://github.com/Leo-Corporation/Passliss" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>GitHub&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="download">Download&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;a class="link" href="https://tinyurl.com/Passliss" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Click here&lt;/a> to download Passliss.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>A new look</title><link>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/02/a-new-look/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/02/a-new-look/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/02/a-new-look/cover.png" alt="Featured image of post A new look" />&lt;p>2021 is going to be a big year for Léo Corporation. And one of the big announcement this year is our new graphic identity. You may notice, but we&amp;rsquo;ve got a new logo and a new &lt;a class="link" href="https://leocorporation.dev/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>website&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/02/a-new-look/cover.png"
width="1920"
height="1080"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/02/a-new-look/cover_hu3fa0d624947acb53576bf457d0684c1d_54799_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/02/a-new-look/cover_hu3fa0d624947acb53576bf457d0684c1d_54799_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="Our new logo"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="177"
data-flex-basis="426px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>It is a part of our new direction for this year. The new logo is more coloful than the older one, and has a new font that we are starting to roll out to our customers: Montserrat.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>But this is not only this. We&amp;rsquo;ve also updated some icons of our softwares:&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/02/a-new-look/2.png"
width="1000"
height="1000"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/02/a-new-look/2_hu5e5743b854f82d16a5f0c05765f4eab5_236801_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/02/a-new-look/2_hu5e5743b854f82d16a5f0c05765f4eab5_236801_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="Bar Code Generator 2 Logo"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="100"
data-flex-basis="240px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/02/a-new-look/3.png"
width="1000"
height="1000"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/02/a-new-look/3_hua143cc6c98a4e9a9609db0061ab0decc_131706_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/02/a-new-look/3_hua143cc6c98a4e9a9609db0061ab0decc_131706_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="ColorPicker 2 Logo"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="100"
data-flex-basis="240px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/02/a-new-look/4.png"
width="1000"
height="1000"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/02/a-new-look/4_hud74d484df1a19483567eb4f95c2386e0_194777_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/02/a-new-look/4_hud74d484df1a19483567eb4f95c2386e0_194777_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="InternetTest Logo"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="100"
data-flex-basis="240px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/02/a-new-look/5.png"
width="2000"
height="2000"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/02/a-new-look/5_hu5325c5e40b6fa01ba016a035212ae06a_78519_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/02/a-new-look/5_hu5325c5e40b6fa01ba016a035212ae06a_78519_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="Passliss Logo"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="100"
data-flex-basis="240px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/02/a-new-look/6.png"
width="1000"
height="1000"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/02/a-new-look/6_hu6ea7d05127779493a3b07ef85ea17abc_264783_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/02/a-new-look/6_hu6ea7d05127779493a3b07ef85ea17abc_264783_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="Xalyus Store Logo"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="100"
data-flex-basis="240px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/02/a-new-look/7.png"
width="1000"
height="1000"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/02/a-new-look/7_hu5254a9c7ffc4bdcc763c54643b1fbfc0_178940_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/02/a-new-look/7_hu5254a9c7ffc4bdcc763c54643b1fbfc0_178940_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="Xalyus Updater Logo"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="100"
data-flex-basis="240px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>These new logos are going to roll out progressively to our users.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The end of the "Tooly Suite"</title><link>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/02/the-end-of-tooly-suite/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2021/02/the-end-of-tooly-suite/</guid><description>&lt;p>Despite many attempts to create the concept of &amp;ldquo;Suite&amp;rdquo;, we annonce that starting the end of Febuary 2021, the Tooly Suite will no longer be maintained or supported.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="a-look-back">A look back&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>We created the concept of &amp;ldquo;Suite&amp;rdquo; back in 2019, a vision to regroup our different softwares inside a &amp;ldquo;Hub&amp;rdquo;. There was two suite at the time: &amp;ldquo;Essential&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Gestion&amp;rdquo;. The &amp;ldquo;Hub&amp;rdquo; is similar to an app launcher. The first attempt failed, and so did the second. It failed because mainly of this two reasons:&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Bad UI/UX (User Interface/User eXperience)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Not enough promotion&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>This is why, during summer 2020, we recreated completely the Essential suite under a new name, the Tooly Suite. This third version was shiped along a brand new design and user experience. Unfortunately, this third attempt also failed, mainly because there wasn&amp;rsquo;t a lot of updates, and also because the concept wasn&amp;rsquo;t being promoted. This third attempt will be our last one as Leo Corporation is going in a new direction.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="what-does-the-end-of-support-means">What does the end of support means?&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>It means that there won&amp;rsquo;t be any updates anymore, and you won&amp;rsquo;t be able to download the Tooly Suite.
It will be removed from our website and Xalyus Store later this month.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="does-this-mean-that-i-wont-be-able-to-use-tooly-suite">Does this mean that I won&amp;rsquo;t be able to use Tooly Suite?&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>No. You can still continue to use it, but some features may not work in the future, like the auto-update system.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="are-you-going-to-open-source-tooly-suite">Are you going to Open Source Tooly Suite?&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>There is no plans yet to do so.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="moving-forward">Moving forward&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>We acknowledge the failure of this concept, and we hope that we will learn from the mistakes made so this won&amp;rsquo;t reproduce in the future again.
Thank you to everyone who supported this project.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Introducing Gavilya</title><link>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2020/12/introducing-gavilya/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2020/12/introducing-gavilya/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2020/12/introducing-gavilya/cover.png" alt="Featured image of post Introducing Gavilya" />&lt;p>We&amp;rsquo;ve been working on a new project for a few months, and if you follow us on GitHub, you may already know what it is, but let&amp;rsquo;s introduce what Gavilya is.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Gavilya is a software that brings all your video games together in one place. Today, there is a lot of game launcher that you need to use depending on the game you wanna play. This is often annoying and this is why we created Gavilya.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="integrations-and-features">Integrations and Features&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Gavilya uses the RAWG.io video games database to get all your games informations automatically. Gavilya uses the RAWG API to get the background image of a game, the game&amp;rsquo;s description and even on wich platforms the game is available on. If you think that the game found by Gavilya in the RAWG database is wrong, you can change the associated game in the &amp;ldquo;Edit&amp;rdquo; window.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>You can also know which games you played recently, or even know how long you&amp;rsquo;ve played a specific game. Gavilya uses a system that can detect if you are playing a game and count the time you&amp;rsquo;ve been playing it. Sometimes this system doesn&amp;rsquo;t works with games that have a different process name than it&amp;rsquo;s executable file (like Minecraft). This is why you can manually set the process to look for (for Minecraft it&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;javaw&amp;rdquo;).&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="open-source">Open Source&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Gavilya is also one of our open-source projects. You can contribute to the code, report issues and bugs with Gavilya and more. Click here to go to the GitHub repo.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="download">Download&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;a class="link" href="https://bit.ly/Gavilya" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Click here&lt;/a> to download Gavilya.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="screenshots">Screenshots&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2020/12/introducing-gavilya/cover.png"
width="960"
height="610"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2020/12/introducing-gavilya/cover_hu31c6bb9887c2453f9b181d6f4b8f0637_198112_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2020/12/introducing-gavilya/cover_hu31c6bb9887c2453f9b181d6f4b8f0637_198112_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="The &amp;ldquo;Your Games&amp;rdquo; page of Gavilya."
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="157"
data-flex-basis="377px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2020/12/introducing-gavilya/2.png"
width="960"
height="610"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2020/12/introducing-gavilya/2_hu1956a95ffff0923f57af8ca295105d09_344354_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2020/12/introducing-gavilya/2_hu1956a95ffff0923f57af8ca295105d09_344354_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="The &amp;ldquo;Game Information&amp;rdquo; page of Gavilya."
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="157"
data-flex-basis="377px"
>
&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2020/12/introducing-gavilya/3.png"
width="960"
height="610"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2020/12/introducing-gavilya/3_hu1956a95ffff0923f57af8ca295105d09_205061_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2020/12/introducing-gavilya/3_hu1956a95ffff0923f57af8ca295105d09_205061_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="The &amp;ldquo;Games recently played&amp;rdquo; page of Gavilya."
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="157"
data-flex-basis="377px"
>
&lt;img src="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2020/12/introducing-gavilya/4.png"
width="960"
height="610"
srcset="https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2020/12/introducing-gavilya/4_hu1956a95ffff0923f57af8ca295105d09_264185_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://blog.leocorporation.dev/2020/12/introducing-gavilya/4_hu1956a95ffff0923f57af8ca295105d09_264185_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="The &amp;ldquo;Your Games - List&amp;rdquo; page of Gavilya."
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="157"
data-flex-basis="377px"
>&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>